
{
    "sentence": "British hurdler Sarah Claxton is confident she can win her first major medal at next month's European Indoor Championships in Madrid.\r\n\"As long as I keep up my training but not do too much I think there is a chance of a medal.\" Claxton has won the national 60m hurdles title for the past three years but has struggled to translate her domestic success to the international stage.",
    "id": "N_0",
    "features": {
        "noun": "hurdler",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "long"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "British hurdler Sarah Claxton is confident she can win her first major medal at next month's European Indoor Championships in which location.\r\n\"As long as I keep up my training but not do too much I think there is a chance of a medal.\" Claxton has won the national 60m hurdles title for the past three years but has struggled to translate her domestic success to the international stage.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "O'Sullivan will also take part in the Bupa Great Ireland Run on 9 April in Dublin.",
    "id": "N_1",
    "features": {
        "noun": "O'Sullivan",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "take",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who will also take part in the Bupa Great Ireland Run on 9 April in Dublin.?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Maurice Greene aims to wipe out the pain of losing his Olympic 100m title in Athens by winning a fourth World Championship crown this summer.\r\nMy goal - I'm going to win the worlds.\" Greene crossed the line just 0.02 seconds behind Gatlin, who won in 9.87 seconds in one of the closest and fastest sprints of all time.\r\nBut Greene believes he lost the race and his title in the semi-finals.\r\n\"I believe if I was in the middle of the race I would have been able to react to people that came ahead of me.\" Greene was also denied Olympic gold in the 4x100m men's relay when he could not catch Britain's Mark Lewis-Francis on the final leg.",
    "id": "N_2",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Maurice",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "aims",
        "adjective": "fourth",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Maurice Greene aims to wipe out the pain of losing his Olympic 100m title in which location by winning a fourth World Championship crown this summer.\r\nMy goal - I'm going to win the worlds.\" Greene crossed the line just 0.02 seconds behind Gatlin, who won in 9.87 seconds in one of the closest and fastest sprints of all time.\r\nBut Greene believes he lost the race and his title in the semi-finals.\r\n\"I believe if I was in the middle of the race I would have been able to react to people that came ahead of me.\" Greene was also denied Olympic gold in the 4x100m men's relay when he could not catch Britain's Mark Lewis-Francis on the final leg.?",
        "answer": "Athens"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I am very happy to see you all, members of the athletics family, respond positively to the IAAF call to sit together and discuss what more we can do in the fight against doping,\" said Diack.",
    "id": "N_3",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"I",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "am",
        "adjective": "happy",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Iwhoamwhoverywhohappywhotowhoseewhoyouwhoall,whomemberswhoofwhothewhoathleticswhofamily,whorespondwhopositivelywhotowhothewhoIAAFwhocallwhotowhositwhotogetherwhoandwhodiscusswhowhatwhomorewhowewhocanwhodowhoinwhothewhofightwhoagainstwhodoping,\"whosaidwhoDiack.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ethiopia's Tirunesh Dibaba set a new world record in winning the women's 5,000m at the Boston Indoor Games.\r\nIreland's Alistair Cragg won in 7:39.89 as Bekele battled to second in 7:41.42.",
    "id": "N_4",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ethiopia's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "set",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ethiopia's Tirunesh who set a new world record in winning the women's 5,000m at the Boston Indoor Games.\r\nIreland's Alistair Cragg won in 7:39.89 as Bekele battled to second in 7:41.42.?",
        "answer": "Dibaba"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "In the men's 60m, former Olympic 100m champion Maurice Greene could only finish second to Leonard Scott.",
    "id": "N_5",
    "features": {
        "noun": "men's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "finish",
        "adjective": "former",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "In the men's 60m, former Olympic 100m champion Maurice who could only finish second to Leonard Scott.?",
        "answer": "Greene"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "O'Sullivan commits to Dublin race",
    "id": "N_6",
    "features": {
        "noun": "O'Sullivan",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who commits to Dublin race?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Her coach Aston Moore told the Times: \"We're not looking at any sooner than 2006, not as a triple jumper.\" Moore said Hansen may be able to return to sprinting and long jumping sooner, but there is no short-term prospect of her being involved again in her specialist event.",
    "id": "N_7",
    "features": {
        "noun": "coach",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "sooner",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Her coach Aston Moore told the Times: \"who're not looking at any sooner than 2006, not as a triple jumper.\" Moore said Hansen may be able to return to sprinting and long jumping sooner, but there is no short-term prospect of her being involved again in her specialist event.?",
        "answer": "We"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Britain's Jason Gardener shook off an upset stomach to win the 60m at Sunday's Leipzig International meeting.\r\nGardener clocked 6.56 seconds to equal the meeting record and finished well ahead of Germany's Marc Blume, who crossed the line in 6.67 secs.\r\nThen everything went perfectly.\" Gardener, part of the Great Britain 4x100m quartet that won gold at the Athens Olympics, will now turn his attention to next weekend's Norwich Union European Indoor trials in Sheffield.\r\n, who broke onto the international scene at the Olympic Games last season, set an indoor personal best of 16.50m in the triple jump at a meeting in Ghent.",
    "id": "N_8",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Britain's",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "shook",
        "adjective": "upset",
        "adverb": "well"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Britain's Jason who shook off an upset stomach to win the 60m at Sunday's Leipzig International meeting.\r\nwho clocked 6.56 seconds to equal the meeting record and finished well ahead of Germany's Marc Blume, who crossed the line in 6.67 secs.\r\nThen everything went perfectly.\" who, part of the Great Britain 4x100m quartet that won gold at the Athens Olympics, will now turn his attention to next weekend's Norwich Union European Indoor trials in Sheffield.\r\n, who broke onto the international scene at the Olympic Games last season, set an indoor personal best of 16.50m in the triple jump at a meeting in Ghent.?",
        "answer": "Gardener"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Jason Gardener and Mark Lewis-Francis are Olympic gold medallists now and I'm sure they'll be aiming to win in front of their home supporters.\r\n\"I'm looking forward to competing against Britain's best sprinters and I'm sure the 60 metres will be one of the most exciting races of the evening.\" Collins was sixth in the Olympic final in Athens but is hoping for a better result at the World Championships in Finland this summer.",
    "id": "N_9",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"Jason",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "gold",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"JasonwhoGardenerwhoandwhoMarkwhoLewis-FranciswhoarewhoOlympicwhogoldwhomedallistswhonowwhoandwhoI'mwhosurewhothey'llwhobewhoaimingwhotowhowinwhoinwhofrontwhoofwhotheirwhohomewhosupporters.\r\n\"I'mwholookingwhoforwardwhotowhocompetingwhoagainstwhoBritain'swhobestwhosprinterswhoandwhoI'mwhosurewhothewho60whometreswhowillwhobewhoonewhoofwhothewhomostwhoexcitingwhoraceswhoofwhothewhoevening.\"whoCollinswhowaswhosixthwhoinwhothewhoOlympicwhofinalwhoinwhoAthenswhobutwhoiswhohopingwhoforwhoawhobetterwhoresultwhoatwhothewhoWorldwhoChampionshipswhoinwhoFinlandwhothiswhosummer.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"It would be fantastic to have Paula in the team,\" said the European cross-country champion.\r\nWe all understand the problem.\" Radcliffe was world cross-country champion in 2001 and 2002 but missed last year's event because of injury.",
    "id": "N_10",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"It",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "fantastic",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"It would be fantastic to have Paula in the team,\" said the European cross-country what.\r\nWe all understand the problem.\" Radcliffe was world cross-country what in 2001 and 2002 but missed last year's event because of injury.?",
        "answer": "champion"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World outdoor triple jump record holder and BBC pundit Jonathan Edwards believes Phillips Idowu can take gold at the European Indoor Championships.\r\n\"It's all down to him, but if he jumps as well as he did in Sheffield he could win the gold medal,\" said Edwards.",
    "id": "N_11",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "triple",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhatoutdoorwhattriplewhatjumpwhatrecordwhatholderwhatandwhatBBCwhatpunditwhatJonathanwhatEdwardswhatbelieveswhatPhillipswhatIdowuwhatcanwhattakewhatgoldwhatatwhatthewhatEuropeanwhatIndoorwhatChampionships.\r\n\"It'swhatallwhatdownwhattowhathim,whatbutwhatifwhathewhatjumpswhataswhatwellwhataswhathewhatdidwhatinwhatSheffieldwhathewhatcouldwhatwinwhatthewhatgoldwhatmedal,\"whatsaidwhatEdwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenya's athletics body has reversed a ban on marathon runner Susan Chepkemei after she made an official apology.\r\nAthletics Kenya (AK) had suspended the two-time London Marathon runner-up for failing to turn up to a cross-country team training camp in Embu.\r\n\"I will be disappointed if I am not given a chance to compete at the world cross country championships.\" AK had insisted it was making an example of Chepkemei by banning her from competition until the end of 2005.",
    "id": "N_12",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenya's",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "official",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kenya's athletics body has reversed a ban on marathon runner Susan Chepkemei after who made an official apology.\r\nAthletics Kenya (AK) had suspended the two-time London Marathon runner-up for failing to turn up to a cross-country team training camp in Embu.\r\n\"I will be disappointed if I am not given a chance to compete at the world cross country championships.\" AK had insisted it was making an example of Chepkemei by banning her from competition until the end of 2005.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Northern Ireland man James McIlroy is confident he can win his first major title at this weekend's Spar European Indoor Championships in Madrid.\r\nLester is better known for his work with 400m runners Roger Black and Mark Richardson in the past but under his guidance McIlroy has secured five wins this indoor season.\r\n\"That was my last decent year,\" said McIlroy, who temporarily retired last August before returning to the sport under Lester's shrewd guidance.\r\nRussian Dmitriy Bogdanov won at the same Madrid venue last week and then claimed the European Championship race would be between himself, Dutchman Arnoud Okken and Antonio Reina of Spain but McIlroy is unfazed.",
    "id": "N_13",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Northern",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "confident",
        "adverb": "better"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Northern Ireland man James McIlroy is confident he can win his first major title at this weekend's Spar European Indoor Championships in which location.\r\nLester is better known for his work with 400m runners Roger Black and Mark Richardson in the past but under his guidance McIlroy has secured five wins this indoor season.\r\n\"That was my last decent year,\" said McIlroy, who temporarily retired last August before returning to the sport under Lester's shrewd guidance.\r\nRussian Dmitriy Bogdanov won at the same which location venue last week and then claimed the European Championship race would be between himself, Dutchman Arnoud Okken and Antonio Reina of Spain but McIlroy is unfazed.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "We are delighted.\" Moorcroft added: \"It is hugely beneficial to the sport that the adidas commitment will also provide for officials and other personnel at our world-class series of live televised events.\" This week, UK Athletics also agreed a four-year deal with energy drink company, Red Bull, who will be supplying the product to athletics at major domestic meetings and in high performance centres.",
    "id": "N_14",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Moorcroft",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "delighted.\"",
        "adverb": "hugely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who are delighted.\" Moorcroft added: \"It is hugely beneficial to the sport that the adidas commitment will also provide for officials and other personnel at our world-class series of live televised events.\" This week, UK Athletics also agreed a four-year deal with energy drink company, Red Bull, who will be supplying the product to athletics at major domestic meetings and in high performance centres.?",
        "answer": "We"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek athletics' governing body has postponed by two weeks the judgement on sprinters Costas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou for missing doping tests.\r\nThe IAAF said the sprinters had failed to provide samples for tests in Tel Aviv, Chicago and Athens and ordered Greek athletic's governing body, Segas, to hold a disciplinary inquiry.",
    "id": "N_15",
    "features": {
        "noun": "athletics'",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "governing",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenteris and compatriot Katerina Thanou were given provisional suspensions in December for failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nKenteris and Thanou withdrew from the Athens Olympics last August after missing drugs tests on the eve of the opening ceremony.",
    "id": "N_16",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenteris",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "compatriot",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "KenteriswhoandwhocompatriotwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhowerewhogivenwhoprovisionalwhosuspensionswhoinwhoDecemberwhoforwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nKenteriswhoandwhoThanouwhowithdrewwhofromwhothewhoAthenswhoOlympicswholastwhoAugustwhoafterwhomissingwhodrugswhotestswhoonwhothewhoevewhoofwhothewhoopeningwhoceremony.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Teenager LaShawn Merritt ran the third fastest indoor 400m of all time at the Fayetteville Invitational meeting.\r\nKenyan Bernard Lagat missed out on the world record by 1.45secs as he ran the third quickest indoor mile ever to beat Canada's Nate Brannen by almost 10secs.\r\nThe Olympic silver medallist's time of three minutes 49.89secs was inferior only to the 1997 world record of Moroccan Hicham El Guerrouj and former world record holder Eamonn Coghlan of Ireland's 3:49.78.",
    "id": "N_17",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Teenager",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "ran",
        "adjective": "third",
        "adverb": "ever"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Teenager LaShawn who ran the third fastest indoor 400m of all time at the Fayetteville Invitational meeting.\r\nKenyan Bernard Lagat missed out on the world record by 1.45secs as he ran the third quickest indoor mile ever to beat Canada's Nate Brannen by almost 10secs.\r\nThe Olympic silver medallist's time of three minutes 49.89secs was inferior only to the 1997 world record of Moroccan Hicham El Guerrouj and former world record holder Eamonn Coghlan of Ireland's 3:49.78.?",
        "answer": "Merritt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "London Marathon organisers are hoping that banned athlete Susan Chepkemei will still take part in this year's race on 17 April.",
    "id": "N_18",
    "features": {
        "noun": "London",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "athlete",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "London Marathon organisers are hoping that banned athlete Susan who will still take part in this year's race on 17 April.?",
        "answer": "Chepkemei"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World outdoor triple jump record holder and BBC pundit Jonathan Edwards believes Phillips Idowu can take gold at the European Indoor Championships.\r\n\"It's all down to him, but if he jumps as well as he did in Sheffield he could win the gold medal,\" said Edwards.",
    "id": "N_19",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "triple",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhatoutdoorwhattriplewhatjumpwhatrecordwhatholderwhatandwhatBBCwhatpunditwhatJonathanwhatEdwardswhatbelieveswhatPhillipswhatIdowuwhatcanwhattakewhatgoldwhatatwhatthewhatEuropeanwhatIndoorwhatChampionships.\r\n\"It'swhatallwhatdownwhattowhathim,whatbutwhatifwhathewhatjumpswhataswhatwellwhataswhathewhatdidwhatinwhatSheffieldwhathewhatcouldwhatwinwhatthewhatgoldwhatmedal,\"whatsaidwhatEdwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenya's athletics body has suspended two-time London Marathon runner-up Susan Chepkemei from all competition until the end of the year.\r\nGlobal Sports Communications, Chepkemei's management company, said she had wanted to run in the World Cross Country Championships in March.",
    "id": "N_20",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenya's",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "two-time",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kenya's athletics what has suspended two-time London Marathon runner-up Susan Chepkemei from all competition until the end of the year.\r\nGlobal Sports Communications, Chepkemei's management company, said she had wanted to run in the World Cross Country Championships in March.?",
        "answer": "body"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Britain's Kelly Holmes marked her first appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold with 1500m victory at the Norwich Union International.\r\nHolmes hit the front just before the bell in front of a sell-out crowd in Glasgow and cruised to victory in a time of four minutes 14.74 seconds.",
    "id": "N_21",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Britain's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "marked",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Britain's Kelly who marked her first appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold with 1500m victory at the Norwich Union International.\r\nwho hit the front just before the bell in front of a sell-out crowd in Glasgow and cruised to victory in a time of four minutes 14.74 seconds.?",
        "answer": "Holmes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek sprinters Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou have appeared before an independent tribunal which will decide if their bans should stand.\r\nThey were given provisional suspensions by athletics' ruling body the IAAF in December for failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nYiannis Papadoyiannakis, who was head of the Greek Olympic team at the Athens Games last year, also testified at the tribunal, along with other Greek sports officials and athletes.\r\nThe five-member tribunal, assembled by the Hellenic Association of Amateur Athletics, is also examining allegations that Kenteris and Thanou avoided tests in Tel Aviv and Chicago before the Games.",
    "id": "N_22",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinters",
        "pronoun": "They",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "GreekwhosprinterswhoKostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhohavewhoappearedwhobeforewhoanwhoindependentwhotribunalwhowhichwhowillwhodecidewhoifwhotheirwhobanswhoshouldwhostand.\r\nTheywhowerewhogivenwhoprovisionalwhosuspensionswhobywhoathletics'whorulingwhobodywhothewhoIAAFwhoinwhoDecemberwhoforwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nYianniswhoPapadoyiannakis,whowhowhowaswhoheadwhoofwhothewhoGreekwhoOlympicwhoteamwhoatwhothewhoAthenswhoGameswholastwhoyear,whoalsowhotestifiedwhoatwhothewhotribunal,whoalongwhowithwhootherwhoGreekwhosportswhoofficialswhoandwhoathletes.\r\nThewhofive-memberwhotribunal,whoassembledwhobywhothewhoHellenicwhoAssociationwhoofwhoAmateurwhoAthletics,whoiswhoalsowhoexaminingwhoallegationswhothatwhoKenteriswhoandwhoThanouwhoavoidedwhotestswhoinwhoTelwhoAvivwhoandwhoChicagowhobeforewhothewhoGames.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Race director Matthew Turnbull said: \"Susan will add even more strength in depth to the world-class line up.\" Chepkemei, who won the six kilometre event three years ago when it was staged in Newcastle, endured an epic battle with Radcliffe in the Big Apple until the Briton outsprinted her in the final 400m.",
    "id": "N_23",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Race",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "add",
        "adjective": "more",
        "adverb": "even"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Race director Matthew Turnbull said: \"who will add even more strength in depth to the world-class line up.\" Chepkemei, who won the six kilometre event three years ago when it was staged in Newcastle, endured an epic battle with Radcliffe in the Big Apple until the Briton outsprinted her in the final 400m.?",
        "answer": "Susan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Double Olympic champion Hicham El Guerrouj is set to make a rare appearance at the World Cross Country Championships in France.\r\nBut the Moroccan, who has not raced over cross country for 15 years, will not decide until two weeks before the event which starts on 19 March.",
    "id": "N_24",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "Double",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Double Olympic champion Hicham El Guerrouj is set to make a rare appearance at the World Cross Country Championships in which location.\r\nBut the Moroccan, who has not raced over cross country for 15 years, will not decide until two weeks before the event which starts on 19 March.?",
        "answer": "France"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "British hurdler Sarah Claxton is confident she can win her first major medal at next month's European Indoor Championships in Madrid.\r\n\"As long as I keep up my training but not do too much I think there is a chance of a medal.\" Claxton has won the national 60m hurdles title for the past three years but has struggled to translate her domestic success to the international stage.",
    "id": "N_0",
    "features": {
        "noun": "hurdler",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "long"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "British hurdler Sarah Claxton is confident she can win her first major medal at next month's European Indoor Championships in which location.\r\n\"As long as I keep up my training but not do too much I think there is a chance of a medal.\" Claxton has won the national 60m hurdles title for the past three years but has struggled to translate her domestic success to the international stage.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "O'Sullivan will also take part in the Bupa Great Ireland Run on 9 April in Dublin.",
    "id": "N_1",
    "features": {
        "noun": "O'Sullivan",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "take",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who will also take part in the Bupa Great Ireland Run on 9 April in Dublin.?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Maurice Greene aims to wipe out the pain of losing his Olympic 100m title in Athens by winning a fourth World Championship crown this summer.\r\nMy goal - I'm going to win the worlds.\" Greene crossed the line just 0.02 seconds behind Gatlin, who won in 9.87 seconds in one of the closest and fastest sprints of all time.\r\nBut Greene believes he lost the race and his title in the semi-finals.\r\n\"I believe if I was in the middle of the race I would have been able to react to people that came ahead of me.\" Greene was also denied Olympic gold in the 4x100m men's relay when he could not catch Britain's Mark Lewis-Francis on the final leg.",
    "id": "N_2",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Maurice",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "aims",
        "adjective": "fourth",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Maurice Greene aims to wipe out the pain of losing his Olympic 100m title in which location by winning a fourth World Championship crown this summer.\r\nMy goal - I'm going to win the worlds.\" Greene crossed the line just 0.02 seconds behind Gatlin, who won in 9.87 seconds in one of the closest and fastest sprints of all time.\r\nBut Greene believes he lost the race and his title in the semi-finals.\r\n\"I believe if I was in the middle of the race I would have been able to react to people that came ahead of me.\" Greene was also denied Olympic gold in the 4x100m men's relay when he could not catch Britain's Mark Lewis-Francis on the final leg.?",
        "answer": "Athens"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I am very happy to see you all, members of the athletics family, respond positively to the IAAF call to sit together and discuss what more we can do in the fight against doping,\" said Diack.",
    "id": "N_3",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"I",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "am",
        "adjective": "happy",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Iwhoamwhoverywhohappywhotowhoseewhoyouwhoall,whomemberswhoofwhothewhoathleticswhofamily,whorespondwhopositivelywhotowhothewhoIAAFwhocallwhotowhositwhotogetherwhoandwhodiscusswhowhatwhomorewhowewhocanwhodowhoinwhothewhofightwhoagainstwhodoping,\"whosaidwhoDiack.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ethiopia's Tirunesh Dibaba set a new world record in winning the women's 5,000m at the Boston Indoor Games.\r\nIreland's Alistair Cragg won in 7:39.89 as Bekele battled to second in 7:41.42.",
    "id": "N_4",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ethiopia's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "set",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ethiopia's Tirunesh who set a new world record in winning the women's 5,000m at the Boston Indoor Games.\r\nIreland's Alistair Cragg won in 7:39.89 as Bekele battled to second in 7:41.42.?",
        "answer": "Dibaba"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "In the men's 60m, former Olympic 100m champion Maurice Greene could only finish second to Leonard Scott.",
    "id": "N_5",
    "features": {
        "noun": "men's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "finish",
        "adjective": "former",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "In the men's 60m, former Olympic 100m champion Maurice who could only finish second to Leonard Scott.?",
        "answer": "Greene"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "O'Sullivan commits to Dublin race",
    "id": "N_6",
    "features": {
        "noun": "O'Sullivan",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who commits to Dublin race?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Her coach Aston Moore told the Times: \"We're not looking at any sooner than 2006, not as a triple jumper.\" Moore said Hansen may be able to return to sprinting and long jumping sooner, but there is no short-term prospect of her being involved again in her specialist event.",
    "id": "N_7",
    "features": {
        "noun": "coach",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "sooner",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Her coach Aston Moore told the Times: \"who're not looking at any sooner than 2006, not as a triple jumper.\" Moore said Hansen may be able to return to sprinting and long jumping sooner, but there is no short-term prospect of her being involved again in her specialist event.?",
        "answer": "We"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Britain's Jason Gardener shook off an upset stomach to win the 60m at Sunday's Leipzig International meeting.\r\nGardener clocked 6.56 seconds to equal the meeting record and finished well ahead of Germany's Marc Blume, who crossed the line in 6.67 secs.\r\nThen everything went perfectly.\" Gardener, part of the Great Britain 4x100m quartet that won gold at the Athens Olympics, will now turn his attention to next weekend's Norwich Union European Indoor trials in Sheffield.\r\n, who broke onto the international scene at the Olympic Games last season, set an indoor personal best of 16.50m in the triple jump at a meeting in Ghent.",
    "id": "N_8",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Britain's",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "shook",
        "adjective": "upset",
        "adverb": "well"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Britain's Jason who shook off an upset stomach to win the 60m at Sunday's Leipzig International meeting.\r\nwho clocked 6.56 seconds to equal the meeting record and finished well ahead of Germany's Marc Blume, who crossed the line in 6.67 secs.\r\nThen everything went perfectly.\" who, part of the Great Britain 4x100m quartet that won gold at the Athens Olympics, will now turn his attention to next weekend's Norwich Union European Indoor trials in Sheffield.\r\n, who broke onto the international scene at the Olympic Games last season, set an indoor personal best of 16.50m in the triple jump at a meeting in Ghent.?",
        "answer": "Gardener"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Jason Gardener and Mark Lewis-Francis are Olympic gold medallists now and I'm sure they'll be aiming to win in front of their home supporters.\r\n\"I'm looking forward to competing against Britain's best sprinters and I'm sure the 60 metres will be one of the most exciting races of the evening.\" Collins was sixth in the Olympic final in Athens but is hoping for a better result at the World Championships in Finland this summer.",
    "id": "N_9",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"Jason",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "gold",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"JasonwhoGardenerwhoandwhoMarkwhoLewis-FranciswhoarewhoOlympicwhogoldwhomedallistswhonowwhoandwhoI'mwhosurewhothey'llwhobewhoaimingwhotowhowinwhoinwhofrontwhoofwhotheirwhohomewhosupporters.\r\n\"I'mwholookingwhoforwardwhotowhocompetingwhoagainstwhoBritain'swhobestwhosprinterswhoandwhoI'mwhosurewhothewho60whometreswhowillwhobewhoonewhoofwhothewhomostwhoexcitingwhoraceswhoofwhothewhoevening.\"whoCollinswhowaswhosixthwhoinwhothewhoOlympicwhofinalwhoinwhoAthenswhobutwhoiswhohopingwhoforwhoawhobetterwhoresultwhoatwhothewhoWorldwhoChampionshipswhoinwhoFinlandwhothiswhosummer.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"It would be fantastic to have Paula in the team,\" said the European cross-country champion.\r\nWe all understand the problem.\" Radcliffe was world cross-country champion in 2001 and 2002 but missed last year's event because of injury.",
    "id": "N_10",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"It",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "fantastic",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"It would be fantastic to have Paula in the team,\" said the European cross-country what.\r\nWe all understand the problem.\" Radcliffe was world cross-country what in 2001 and 2002 but missed last year's event because of injury.?",
        "answer": "champion"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World outdoor triple jump record holder and BBC pundit Jonathan Edwards believes Phillips Idowu can take gold at the European Indoor Championships.\r\n\"It's all down to him, but if he jumps as well as he did in Sheffield he could win the gold medal,\" said Edwards.",
    "id": "N_11",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "triple",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhatoutdoorwhattriplewhatjumpwhatrecordwhatholderwhatandwhatBBCwhatpunditwhatJonathanwhatEdwardswhatbelieveswhatPhillipswhatIdowuwhatcanwhattakewhatgoldwhatatwhatthewhatEuropeanwhatIndoorwhatChampionships.\r\n\"It'swhatallwhatdownwhattowhathim,whatbutwhatifwhathewhatjumpswhataswhatwellwhataswhathewhatdidwhatinwhatSheffieldwhathewhatcouldwhatwinwhatthewhatgoldwhatmedal,\"whatsaidwhatEdwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenya's athletics body has reversed a ban on marathon runner Susan Chepkemei after she made an official apology.\r\nAthletics Kenya (AK) had suspended the two-time London Marathon runner-up for failing to turn up to a cross-country team training camp in Embu.\r\n\"I will be disappointed if I am not given a chance to compete at the world cross country championships.\" AK had insisted it was making an example of Chepkemei by banning her from competition until the end of 2005.",
    "id": "N_12",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenya's",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "official",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kenya's athletics body has reversed a ban on marathon runner Susan Chepkemei after who made an official apology.\r\nAthletics Kenya (AK) had suspended the two-time London Marathon runner-up for failing to turn up to a cross-country team training camp in Embu.\r\n\"I will be disappointed if I am not given a chance to compete at the world cross country championships.\" AK had insisted it was making an example of Chepkemei by banning her from competition until the end of 2005.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Northern Ireland man James McIlroy is confident he can win his first major title at this weekend's Spar European Indoor Championships in Madrid.\r\nLester is better known for his work with 400m runners Roger Black and Mark Richardson in the past but under his guidance McIlroy has secured five wins this indoor season.\r\n\"That was my last decent year,\" said McIlroy, who temporarily retired last August before returning to the sport under Lester's shrewd guidance.\r\nRussian Dmitriy Bogdanov won at the same Madrid venue last week and then claimed the European Championship race would be between himself, Dutchman Arnoud Okken and Antonio Reina of Spain but McIlroy is unfazed.",
    "id": "N_13",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Northern",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "confident",
        "adverb": "better"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Northern Ireland man James McIlroy is confident he can win his first major title at this weekend's Spar European Indoor Championships in which location.\r\nLester is better known for his work with 400m runners Roger Black and Mark Richardson in the past but under his guidance McIlroy has secured five wins this indoor season.\r\n\"That was my last decent year,\" said McIlroy, who temporarily retired last August before returning to the sport under Lester's shrewd guidance.\r\nRussian Dmitriy Bogdanov won at the same which location venue last week and then claimed the European Championship race would be between himself, Dutchman Arnoud Okken and Antonio Reina of Spain but McIlroy is unfazed.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "We are delighted.\" Moorcroft added: \"It is hugely beneficial to the sport that the adidas commitment will also provide for officials and other personnel at our world-class series of live televised events.\" This week, UK Athletics also agreed a four-year deal with energy drink company, Red Bull, who will be supplying the product to athletics at major domestic meetings and in high performance centres.",
    "id": "N_14",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Moorcroft",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "delighted.\"",
        "adverb": "hugely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who are delighted.\" Moorcroft added: \"It is hugely beneficial to the sport that the adidas commitment will also provide for officials and other personnel at our world-class series of live televised events.\" This week, UK Athletics also agreed a four-year deal with energy drink company, Red Bull, who will be supplying the product to athletics at major domestic meetings and in high performance centres.?",
        "answer": "We"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek athletics' governing body has postponed by two weeks the judgement on sprinters Costas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou for missing doping tests.\r\nThe IAAF said the sprinters had failed to provide samples for tests in Tel Aviv, Chicago and Athens and ordered Greek athletic's governing body, Segas, to hold a disciplinary inquiry.",
    "id": "N_15",
    "features": {
        "noun": "athletics'",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "governing",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenteris and compatriot Katerina Thanou were given provisional suspensions in December for failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nKenteris and Thanou withdrew from the Athens Olympics last August after missing drugs tests on the eve of the opening ceremony.",
    "id": "N_16",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenteris",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "compatriot",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "KenteriswhoandwhocompatriotwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhowerewhogivenwhoprovisionalwhosuspensionswhoinwhoDecemberwhoforwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nKenteriswhoandwhoThanouwhowithdrewwhofromwhothewhoAthenswhoOlympicswholastwhoAugustwhoafterwhomissingwhodrugswhotestswhoonwhothewhoevewhoofwhothewhoopeningwhoceremony.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Teenager LaShawn Merritt ran the third fastest indoor 400m of all time at the Fayetteville Invitational meeting.\r\nKenyan Bernard Lagat missed out on the world record by 1.45secs as he ran the third quickest indoor mile ever to beat Canada's Nate Brannen by almost 10secs.\r\nThe Olympic silver medallist's time of three minutes 49.89secs was inferior only to the 1997 world record of Moroccan Hicham El Guerrouj and former world record holder Eamonn Coghlan of Ireland's 3:49.78.",
    "id": "N_17",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Teenager",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "ran",
        "adjective": "third",
        "adverb": "ever"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Teenager LaShawn who ran the third fastest indoor 400m of all time at the Fayetteville Invitational meeting.\r\nKenyan Bernard Lagat missed out on the world record by 1.45secs as he ran the third quickest indoor mile ever to beat Canada's Nate Brannen by almost 10secs.\r\nThe Olympic silver medallist's time of three minutes 49.89secs was inferior only to the 1997 world record of Moroccan Hicham El Guerrouj and former world record holder Eamonn Coghlan of Ireland's 3:49.78.?",
        "answer": "Merritt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "London Marathon organisers are hoping that banned athlete Susan Chepkemei will still take part in this year's race on 17 April.",
    "id": "N_18",
    "features": {
        "noun": "London",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "athlete",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "London Marathon organisers are hoping that banned athlete Susan who will still take part in this year's race on 17 April.?",
        "answer": "Chepkemei"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World outdoor triple jump record holder and BBC pundit Jonathan Edwards believes Phillips Idowu can take gold at the European Indoor Championships.\r\n\"It's all down to him, but if he jumps as well as he did in Sheffield he could win the gold medal,\" said Edwards.",
    "id": "N_19",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "triple",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhatoutdoorwhattriplewhatjumpwhatrecordwhatholderwhatandwhatBBCwhatpunditwhatJonathanwhatEdwardswhatbelieveswhatPhillipswhatIdowuwhatcanwhattakewhatgoldwhatatwhatthewhatEuropeanwhatIndoorwhatChampionships.\r\n\"It'swhatallwhatdownwhattowhathim,whatbutwhatifwhathewhatjumpswhataswhatwellwhataswhathewhatdidwhatinwhatSheffieldwhathewhatcouldwhatwinwhatthewhatgoldwhatmedal,\"whatsaidwhatEdwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenya's athletics body has suspended two-time London Marathon runner-up Susan Chepkemei from all competition until the end of the year.\r\nGlobal Sports Communications, Chepkemei's management company, said she had wanted to run in the World Cross Country Championships in March.",
    "id": "N_20",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenya's",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "two-time",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kenya's athletics what has suspended two-time London Marathon runner-up Susan Chepkemei from all competition until the end of the year.\r\nGlobal Sports Communications, Chepkemei's management company, said she had wanted to run in the World Cross Country Championships in March.?",
        "answer": "body"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Britain's Kelly Holmes marked her first appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold with 1500m victory at the Norwich Union International.\r\nHolmes hit the front just before the bell in front of a sell-out crowd in Glasgow and cruised to victory in a time of four minutes 14.74 seconds.",
    "id": "N_21",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Britain's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "marked",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Britain's Kelly who marked her first appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold with 1500m victory at the Norwich Union International.\r\nwho hit the front just before the bell in front of a sell-out crowd in Glasgow and cruised to victory in a time of four minutes 14.74 seconds.?",
        "answer": "Holmes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek sprinters Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou have appeared before an independent tribunal which will decide if their bans should stand.\r\nThey were given provisional suspensions by athletics' ruling body the IAAF in December for failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nYiannis Papadoyiannakis, who was head of the Greek Olympic team at the Athens Games last year, also testified at the tribunal, along with other Greek sports officials and athletes.\r\nThe five-member tribunal, assembled by the Hellenic Association of Amateur Athletics, is also examining allegations that Kenteris and Thanou avoided tests in Tel Aviv and Chicago before the Games.",
    "id": "N_22",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinters",
        "pronoun": "They",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "GreekwhosprinterswhoKostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhohavewhoappearedwhobeforewhoanwhoindependentwhotribunalwhowhichwhowillwhodecidewhoifwhotheirwhobanswhoshouldwhostand.\r\nTheywhowerewhogivenwhoprovisionalwhosuspensionswhobywhoathletics'whorulingwhobodywhothewhoIAAFwhoinwhoDecemberwhoforwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nYianniswhoPapadoyiannakis,whowhowhowaswhoheadwhoofwhothewhoGreekwhoOlympicwhoteamwhoatwhothewhoAthenswhoGameswholastwhoyear,whoalsowhotestifiedwhoatwhothewhotribunal,whoalongwhowithwhootherwhoGreekwhosportswhoofficialswhoandwhoathletes.\r\nThewhofive-memberwhotribunal,whoassembledwhobywhothewhoHellenicwhoAssociationwhoofwhoAmateurwhoAthletics,whoiswhoalsowhoexaminingwhoallegationswhothatwhoKenteriswhoandwhoThanouwhoavoidedwhotestswhoinwhoTelwhoAvivwhoandwhoChicagowhobeforewhothewhoGames.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Race director Matthew Turnbull said: \"Susan will add even more strength in depth to the world-class line up.\" Chepkemei, who won the six kilometre event three years ago when it was staged in Newcastle, endured an epic battle with Radcliffe in the Big Apple until the Briton outsprinted her in the final 400m.",
    "id": "N_23",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Race",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "add",
        "adjective": "more",
        "adverb": "even"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Race director Matthew Turnbull said: \"who will add even more strength in depth to the world-class line up.\" Chepkemei, who won the six kilometre event three years ago when it was staged in Newcastle, endured an epic battle with Radcliffe in the Big Apple until the Briton outsprinted her in the final 400m.?",
        "answer": "Susan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Double Olympic champion Hicham El Guerrouj is set to make a rare appearance at the World Cross Country Championships in France.\r\nBut the Moroccan, who has not raced over cross country for 15 years, will not decide until two weeks before the event which starts on 19 March.",
    "id": "N_24",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "Double",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Double Olympic champion Hicham El Guerrouj is set to make a rare appearance at the World Cross Country Championships in which location.\r\nBut the Moroccan, who has not raced over cross country for 15 years, will not decide until two weeks before the event which starts on 19 March.?",
        "answer": "France"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sprinter Michelle Collins has lodged an appeal against her eight-year doping ban with the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).",
    "id": "N_25",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sprinter",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "eight-year",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Sprinter Michelle who has lodged an appeal against her eight-year doping ban with the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).?",
        "answer": "Collins"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Briton, made a dame in the New Year Honours List for taking 800m and 1,500m gold, won vital votes from the public, press and EAA member federations.",
    "id": "N_26",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Briton,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "made",
        "adjective": "vital",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoBriton,whomadewhoawhodamewhoinwhothewhoNewwhoYearwhoHonourswhoListwhoforwhotakingwho800mwhoandwho1,500mwhogold,whowonwhovitalwhovoteswhofromwhothewhopublic,whopresswhoandwhoEAAwhomemberwhofederations.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The 31-year-old, who won Olympic 200m silver in Sydney in 2000, said during the Games that a hamstring injury had stopped him from running at his best.\r\n\"To go to Athens and finally get the gold I've been trying to get for 24 years was a big relief,\" said Campbell.\r\n\"It's just unfortunate that I picked up that injury just before the Olympics.\" Campbell set his 100m personal best of 10.04secs when he won the European title in Budapest in 1998.",
    "id": "N_27",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "won",
        "adjective": "31-year-old,",
        "adverb": "finally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The 31-year-old, who won Olympic 200m silver in Sydney in 2000, said during the Games that a hamstring what had stopped him from running at his best.\r\n\"To go to Athens and finally get the gold I've been trying to get for 24 years was a big relief,\" said Campbell.\r\n\"It's just unfortunate that I picked up that what just before the Olympics.\" Campbell set his 100m personal best of 10.04secs when he won the European title in Budapest in 1998.?",
        "answer": "injury"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Olympic pole vault champion Yelena Isinbayeva has confirmed she will take part in the 2005 Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham on 18 February.",
    "id": "N_28",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Olympic pole vault champion Yelena Isinbayeva has confirmed who will take part in the 2005 Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham on 18 February.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But come late August, a few hot days in the magnificent stadium in Athens told us of the true strength of Irish athletics - or to be more accurate, the lack of it.\r\nSonia O'Sullivan's Olympic farewell apart, there was little to stir the emotions of Irish athletics watchers.\r\nAt the start of the year, an O'Sullivan had been earmarked as Ireland's best medal prospect but as it turned out, walker Gillian never even made it to the start line because of injury.\r\nOnce the track and field action began in Athens, a familiar pattern of underachievement emerged although Alistair Cragg's performance in being the only athlete from a European nation to qualify for the 5,000m final did offer hope for the future.\r\nAt the start of the year, several Northern Ireland athletes had genuine hopes of qualifying for the Games but come August, an out-of-form and injured Paul Brizzel was the lone standard bearer for the province.",
    "id": "N_29",
    "features": {
        "noun": "August,",
        "pronoun": "us",
        "verb": "come",
        "adjective": "few",
        "adverb": "late"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He told the Herald newspaper: \"I'm not in great shape, after missing about a month of training.",
    "id": "N_30",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Herald",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "great",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "He told the Herald newspaper: \"who'm not in great shape, after missing about a month of training.?",
        "answer": "I"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Olympic 10,000m champion Kenenisa Bekele is determined to add the world indoor two mile record at February's Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham.\r\nThe 22-year-old will again be chasing a record held by his compatriot and mentor Haile Gebrselassie, who set the mark at the same meeting in 2003.",
    "id": "N_31",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "22-year-old",
        "adverb": "again"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Olympic 10,000m champion Kenenisa who is determined to add the world indoor two mile record at February's Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham.\r\nThe 22-year-old will again be chasing a record held by his compatriot and mentor Haile Gebrselassie, who set the mark at the same meeting in 2003.?",
        "answer": "Bekele"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek sprinters Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou have been suspended after failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nAthletics' ruling body the IAAF said explanations from the pair and their former coach as to why they missed the tests were \"unacceptable\".\r\nKenteris, the 2000 Olympic 200m champion, and Thanou, the women's 100m silver medallist from the same Games in Sydney, also face a criminal hearing in Greece over the missed tests.",
    "id": "N_32",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinters",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "why"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "GreekwhosprinterswhoKostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhohavewhobeenwhosuspendedwhoafterwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nAthletics'whorulingwhobodywhothewhoIAAFwhosaidwhoexplanationswhofromwhothewhopairwhoandwhotheirwhoformerwhocoachwhoaswhotowhowhywhotheywhomissedwhothewhotestswhowerewho\"unacceptable\".\r\nKenteris,whothewho2000whoOlympicwho200mwhochampion,whoandwhoThanou,whothewhowomen'swho100mwhosilverwhomedallistwhofromwhothewhosamewhoGameswhoinwhoSydney,whoalsowhofacewhoawhocriminalwhohearingwhoinwhoGreecewhooverwhothewhomissedwhotests.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Well, it's goodbye to another Olympic year and as usual there were plenty of highs and lows in Athens.\r\nThe victory for the British men's 4x100m relay team was a bit of a surprise but a great climax to the Games.\r\nWhat happened to Paula in Athens this year is the obvious low on a personal level and for the expectations of the nation as well.\r\nAnd if even the smallest thing doesn't feel right when you are preparing to race a marathon, 10 miles down the road it will hit you like a brick wall.\r\nThe positive thing to take from Paula's Olympics it that she will have learned a lot from it and so will a lot of people - including me.\r\nPurely as a race, Paula's victory in the New York Marathon has to go down as one of the most thrilling.\r\nAnd that's where things begin to look even gloomier for British athletics as we did not win any medals at the world junior championships in Italy.\r\nThe thing is if we don't have athletes getting into the finals at junior level then it really doesn't look good for the Beijing Olympics and beyond.\r\nAnd one of the positive things to come out of Balco is people are starting to blow the whistle.",
    "id": "N_33",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Well,",
        "pronoun": "What",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "usual",
        "adverb": "even"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Well,whoit'swhogoodbyewhotowhoanotherwhoOlympicwhoyearwhoandwhoaswhousualwhotherewhowerewhoplentywhoofwhohighswhoandwholowswhoinwhoAthens.\r\nThewhovictorywhoforwhothewhoBritishwhomen'swho4x100mwhorelaywhoteamwhowaswhoawhobitwhoofwhoawhosurprisewhobutwhoawhogreatwhoclimaxwhotowhothewhoGames.\r\nWhatwhohappenedwhotowhoPaulawhoinwhoAthenswhothiswhoyearwhoiswhothewhoobviouswholowwhoonwhoawhopersonalwholevelwhoandwhoforwhothewhoexpectationswhoofwhothewhonationwhoaswhowell.\r\nAndwhoifwhoevenwhothewhosmallestwhothingwhodoesn'twhofeelwhorightwhowhenwhoyouwhoarewhopreparingwhotowhoracewhoawhomarathon,who10whomileswhodownwhothewhoroadwhoitwhowillwhohitwhoyouwholikewhoawhobrickwhowall.\r\nThewhopositivewhothingwhotowhotakewhofromwhoPaula'swhoOlympicswhoitwhothatwhoshewhowillwhohavewholearnedwhoawholotwhofromwhoitwhoandwhosowhowillwhoawholotwhoofwhopeoplewho-whoincludingwhome.\r\nPurelywhoaswhoawhorace,whoPaula'swhovictorywhoinwhothewhoNewwhoYorkwhoMarathonwhohaswhotowhogowhodownwhoaswhoonewhoofwhothewhomostwhothrilling.\r\nAndwhothat'swhowherewhothingswhobeginwhotowholookwhoevenwhogloomierwhoforwhoBritishwhoathleticswhoaswhowewhodidwhonotwhowinwhoanywhomedalswhoatwhothewhoworldwhojuniorwhochampionshipswhoinwhoItaly.\r\nThewhothingwhoiswhoifwhowewhodon'twhohavewhoathleteswhogettingwhointowhothewhofinalswhoatwhojuniorwholevelwhothenwhoitwhoreallywhodoesn'twholookwhogoodwhoforwhothewhoBeijingwhoOlympicswhoandwhobeyond.\r\nAndwhoonewhoofwhothewhopositivewhothingswhotowhocomewhooutwhoofwhoBalcowhoiswhopeoplewhoarewhostartingwhotowhoblowwhothewhowhistle.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sprinter Michelle Collins has received an eight-year ban for doping offences after a hearing at the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).\r\nCollins' ban is a result of her connection to the federal inquiry into the Balco doping scandal.\r\n\"Collins used these substances to enhance her performance and elude the drug testing that was available at the time.\" So far a total of 13 athletes have been sanctioned for violations involving drugs associated with the Balco doping scandal.",
    "id": "N_34",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sprinter",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "eight-year",
        "adverb": "far"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Sprinter Michelle who has received an eight-year ban for doping offences after a hearing at the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).\r\nwho' ban is a result of her connection to the federal inquiry into the Balco doping scandal.\r\n\"who used these substances to enhance her performance and elude the drug testing that was available at the time.\" So far a total of 13 athletes have been sanctioned for violations involving drugs associated with the Balco doping scandal.?",
        "answer": "Collins"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jones, who says she is innocent, could lose all her Olympic medals after Conte said he gave her performance-enhancing drugs before the Sydney Olympics.\r\nThe Sydney Olympics ended more than four years ago, but World Anti-Doping Agency chief Dick Pound said the rule may not apply because the allegations are only coming out now.",
    "id": "N_35",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jones,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "innocent,",
        "adverb": "more"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jones, who says swho is innocent, could lose all whor Olympic medals after Conte said who gave whor performance-enhancing drugs before twho Sydney Olympics.\r\nTwho Sydney Olympics ended more than four years ago, but World Anti-Doping Agency chief Dick Pound said twho rule may not apply because twho allegations are only coming out now.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former Olympic champion Michael Johnson has accused Britain's top sprinters of lacking pride and ambition.\r\n\"Athletics at the moment is all about international competitions and they need to show a little more pride.\" However, Linford Christie countered: \"It's easy to criticise when you haven't gone through the system here.\" Johnson was involved in a verbal spat with Britain's Darren Campbell earlier this year.",
    "id": "N_36",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "top",
        "adverb": "little"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "FormerwhoOlympicwhochampionwhoMichaelwhoJohnsonwhohaswhoaccusedwhoBritain'swhotopwhosprinterswhoofwholackingwhopridewhoandwhoambition.\r\n\"Athleticswhoatwhothewhomomentwhoiswhoallwhoaboutwhointernationalwhocompetitionswhoandwhotheywhoneedwhotowhoshowwhoawholittlewhomorewhopride.\"whoHowever,whoLinfordwhoChristiewhocountered:who\"It'swhoeasywhotowhocriticisewhowhenwhoyouwhohaven'twhogonewhothroughwhothewhosystemwhohere.\"whoJohnsonwhowaswhoinvolvedwhoinwhoawhoverbalwhospatwhowithwhoBritain'swhoDarrenwhoCampbellwhoearlierwhothiswhoyear.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A win in the New York marathon doesn't make up for the disappointment of Athens in any shape or form, but it will offer hope and reassurance for next year.\r\nIf Paula's last experience of the year had been Athens, it would have been very difficult to look forward with any optimism.\r\nAnd a lot of people were wondering what would happen if Paula was forced to drop out of this race, as she did in the marathon and 10,000m in Athens.\r\nNow Paula will take part in the Run London 10km race in London at the end of the year, have a well-earned rest over Christmas and go into next year with a lot of optimism.",
    "id": "N_37",
    "features": {
        "noun": "win",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA) chief Dick Pound says Marion Jones should be stripped of all her medals if found guilty of taking banned substances.",
    "id": "N_38",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "guilty",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA) chief Dick Pound says Marion who should be stripped of all her medals if found guilty of taking banned substances.?",
        "answer": "Jones"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "British hurdler Sarah Claxton is confident she can win her first major medal at next month's European Indoor Championships in Madrid.\r\n\"As long as I keep up my training but not do too much I think there is a chance of a medal.\" Claxton has won the national 60m hurdles title for the past three years but has struggled to translate her domestic success to the international stage.",
    "id": "N_0",
    "features": {
        "noun": "hurdler",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "long"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "British hurdler Sarah Claxton is confident she can win her first major medal at next month's European Indoor Championships in which location.\r\n\"As long as I keep up my training but not do too much I think there is a chance of a medal.\" Claxton has won the national 60m hurdles title for the past three years but has struggled to translate her domestic success to the international stage.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "O'Sullivan will also take part in the Bupa Great Ireland Run on 9 April in Dublin.",
    "id": "N_1",
    "features": {
        "noun": "O'Sullivan",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "take",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who will also take part in the Bupa Great Ireland Run on 9 April in Dublin.?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Maurice Greene aims to wipe out the pain of losing his Olympic 100m title in Athens by winning a fourth World Championship crown this summer.\r\nMy goal - I'm going to win the worlds.\" Greene crossed the line just 0.02 seconds behind Gatlin, who won in 9.87 seconds in one of the closest and fastest sprints of all time.\r\nBut Greene believes he lost the race and his title in the semi-finals.\r\n\"I believe if I was in the middle of the race I would have been able to react to people that came ahead of me.\" Greene was also denied Olympic gold in the 4x100m men's relay when he could not catch Britain's Mark Lewis-Francis on the final leg.",
    "id": "N_2",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Maurice",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "aims",
        "adjective": "fourth",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Maurice Greene aims to wipe out the pain of losing his Olympic 100m title in which location by winning a fourth World Championship crown this summer.\r\nMy goal - I'm going to win the worlds.\" Greene crossed the line just 0.02 seconds behind Gatlin, who won in 9.87 seconds in one of the closest and fastest sprints of all time.\r\nBut Greene believes he lost the race and his title in the semi-finals.\r\n\"I believe if I was in the middle of the race I would have been able to react to people that came ahead of me.\" Greene was also denied Olympic gold in the 4x100m men's relay when he could not catch Britain's Mark Lewis-Francis on the final leg.?",
        "answer": "Athens"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I am very happy to see you all, members of the athletics family, respond positively to the IAAF call to sit together and discuss what more we can do in the fight against doping,\" said Diack.",
    "id": "N_3",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"I",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "am",
        "adjective": "happy",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Iwhoamwhoverywhohappywhotowhoseewhoyouwhoall,whomemberswhoofwhothewhoathleticswhofamily,whorespondwhopositivelywhotowhothewhoIAAFwhocallwhotowhositwhotogetherwhoandwhodiscusswhowhatwhomorewhowewhocanwhodowhoinwhothewhofightwhoagainstwhodoping,\"whosaidwhoDiack.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ethiopia's Tirunesh Dibaba set a new world record in winning the women's 5,000m at the Boston Indoor Games.\r\nIreland's Alistair Cragg won in 7:39.89 as Bekele battled to second in 7:41.42.",
    "id": "N_4",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ethiopia's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "set",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ethiopia's Tirunesh who set a new world record in winning the women's 5,000m at the Boston Indoor Games.\r\nIreland's Alistair Cragg won in 7:39.89 as Bekele battled to second in 7:41.42.?",
        "answer": "Dibaba"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "In the men's 60m, former Olympic 100m champion Maurice Greene could only finish second to Leonard Scott.",
    "id": "N_5",
    "features": {
        "noun": "men's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "finish",
        "adjective": "former",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "In the men's 60m, former Olympic 100m champion Maurice who could only finish second to Leonard Scott.?",
        "answer": "Greene"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "O'Sullivan commits to Dublin race",
    "id": "N_6",
    "features": {
        "noun": "O'Sullivan",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who commits to Dublin race?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Her coach Aston Moore told the Times: \"We're not looking at any sooner than 2006, not as a triple jumper.\" Moore said Hansen may be able to return to sprinting and long jumping sooner, but there is no short-term prospect of her being involved again in her specialist event.",
    "id": "N_7",
    "features": {
        "noun": "coach",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "sooner",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Her coach Aston Moore told the Times: \"who're not looking at any sooner than 2006, not as a triple jumper.\" Moore said Hansen may be able to return to sprinting and long jumping sooner, but there is no short-term prospect of her being involved again in her specialist event.?",
        "answer": "We"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Britain's Jason Gardener shook off an upset stomach to win the 60m at Sunday's Leipzig International meeting.\r\nGardener clocked 6.56 seconds to equal the meeting record and finished well ahead of Germany's Marc Blume, who crossed the line in 6.67 secs.\r\nThen everything went perfectly.\" Gardener, part of the Great Britain 4x100m quartet that won gold at the Athens Olympics, will now turn his attention to next weekend's Norwich Union European Indoor trials in Sheffield.\r\n, who broke onto the international scene at the Olympic Games last season, set an indoor personal best of 16.50m in the triple jump at a meeting in Ghent.",
    "id": "N_8",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Britain's",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "shook",
        "adjective": "upset",
        "adverb": "well"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Britain's Jason who shook off an upset stomach to win the 60m at Sunday's Leipzig International meeting.\r\nwho clocked 6.56 seconds to equal the meeting record and finished well ahead of Germany's Marc Blume, who crossed the line in 6.67 secs.\r\nThen everything went perfectly.\" who, part of the Great Britain 4x100m quartet that won gold at the Athens Olympics, will now turn his attention to next weekend's Norwich Union European Indoor trials in Sheffield.\r\n, who broke onto the international scene at the Olympic Games last season, set an indoor personal best of 16.50m in the triple jump at a meeting in Ghent.?",
        "answer": "Gardener"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Jason Gardener and Mark Lewis-Francis are Olympic gold medallists now and I'm sure they'll be aiming to win in front of their home supporters.\r\n\"I'm looking forward to competing against Britain's best sprinters and I'm sure the 60 metres will be one of the most exciting races of the evening.\" Collins was sixth in the Olympic final in Athens but is hoping for a better result at the World Championships in Finland this summer.",
    "id": "N_9",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"Jason",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "gold",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"JasonwhoGardenerwhoandwhoMarkwhoLewis-FranciswhoarewhoOlympicwhogoldwhomedallistswhonowwhoandwhoI'mwhosurewhothey'llwhobewhoaimingwhotowhowinwhoinwhofrontwhoofwhotheirwhohomewhosupporters.\r\n\"I'mwholookingwhoforwardwhotowhocompetingwhoagainstwhoBritain'swhobestwhosprinterswhoandwhoI'mwhosurewhothewho60whometreswhowillwhobewhoonewhoofwhothewhomostwhoexcitingwhoraceswhoofwhothewhoevening.\"whoCollinswhowaswhosixthwhoinwhothewhoOlympicwhofinalwhoinwhoAthenswhobutwhoiswhohopingwhoforwhoawhobetterwhoresultwhoatwhothewhoWorldwhoChampionshipswhoinwhoFinlandwhothiswhosummer.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"It would be fantastic to have Paula in the team,\" said the European cross-country champion.\r\nWe all understand the problem.\" Radcliffe was world cross-country champion in 2001 and 2002 but missed last year's event because of injury.",
    "id": "N_10",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"It",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "fantastic",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"It would be fantastic to have Paula in the team,\" said the European cross-country what.\r\nWe all understand the problem.\" Radcliffe was world cross-country what in 2001 and 2002 but missed last year's event because of injury.?",
        "answer": "champion"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World outdoor triple jump record holder and BBC pundit Jonathan Edwards believes Phillips Idowu can take gold at the European Indoor Championships.\r\n\"It's all down to him, but if he jumps as well as he did in Sheffield he could win the gold medal,\" said Edwards.",
    "id": "N_11",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "triple",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhatoutdoorwhattriplewhatjumpwhatrecordwhatholderwhatandwhatBBCwhatpunditwhatJonathanwhatEdwardswhatbelieveswhatPhillipswhatIdowuwhatcanwhattakewhatgoldwhatatwhatthewhatEuropeanwhatIndoorwhatChampionships.\r\n\"It'swhatallwhatdownwhattowhathim,whatbutwhatifwhathewhatjumpswhataswhatwellwhataswhathewhatdidwhatinwhatSheffieldwhathewhatcouldwhatwinwhatthewhatgoldwhatmedal,\"whatsaidwhatEdwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenya's athletics body has reversed a ban on marathon runner Susan Chepkemei after she made an official apology.\r\nAthletics Kenya (AK) had suspended the two-time London Marathon runner-up for failing to turn up to a cross-country team training camp in Embu.\r\n\"I will be disappointed if I am not given a chance to compete at the world cross country championships.\" AK had insisted it was making an example of Chepkemei by banning her from competition until the end of 2005.",
    "id": "N_12",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenya's",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "official",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kenya's athletics body has reversed a ban on marathon runner Susan Chepkemei after who made an official apology.\r\nAthletics Kenya (AK) had suspended the two-time London Marathon runner-up for failing to turn up to a cross-country team training camp in Embu.\r\n\"I will be disappointed if I am not given a chance to compete at the world cross country championships.\" AK had insisted it was making an example of Chepkemei by banning her from competition until the end of 2005.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Northern Ireland man James McIlroy is confident he can win his first major title at this weekend's Spar European Indoor Championships in Madrid.\r\nLester is better known for his work with 400m runners Roger Black and Mark Richardson in the past but under his guidance McIlroy has secured five wins this indoor season.\r\n\"That was my last decent year,\" said McIlroy, who temporarily retired last August before returning to the sport under Lester's shrewd guidance.\r\nRussian Dmitriy Bogdanov won at the same Madrid venue last week and then claimed the European Championship race would be between himself, Dutchman Arnoud Okken and Antonio Reina of Spain but McIlroy is unfazed.",
    "id": "N_13",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Northern",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "confident",
        "adverb": "better"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Northern Ireland man James McIlroy is confident he can win his first major title at this weekend's Spar European Indoor Championships in which location.\r\nLester is better known for his work with 400m runners Roger Black and Mark Richardson in the past but under his guidance McIlroy has secured five wins this indoor season.\r\n\"That was my last decent year,\" said McIlroy, who temporarily retired last August before returning to the sport under Lester's shrewd guidance.\r\nRussian Dmitriy Bogdanov won at the same which location venue last week and then claimed the European Championship race would be between himself, Dutchman Arnoud Okken and Antonio Reina of Spain but McIlroy is unfazed.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "We are delighted.\" Moorcroft added: \"It is hugely beneficial to the sport that the adidas commitment will also provide for officials and other personnel at our world-class series of live televised events.\" This week, UK Athletics also agreed a four-year deal with energy drink company, Red Bull, who will be supplying the product to athletics at major domestic meetings and in high performance centres.",
    "id": "N_14",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Moorcroft",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "delighted.\"",
        "adverb": "hugely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who are delighted.\" Moorcroft added: \"It is hugely beneficial to the sport that the adidas commitment will also provide for officials and other personnel at our world-class series of live televised events.\" This week, UK Athletics also agreed a four-year deal with energy drink company, Red Bull, who will be supplying the product to athletics at major domestic meetings and in high performance centres.?",
        "answer": "We"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek athletics' governing body has postponed by two weeks the judgement on sprinters Costas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou for missing doping tests.\r\nThe IAAF said the sprinters had failed to provide samples for tests in Tel Aviv, Chicago and Athens and ordered Greek athletic's governing body, Segas, to hold a disciplinary inquiry.",
    "id": "N_15",
    "features": {
        "noun": "athletics'",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "governing",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenteris and compatriot Katerina Thanou were given provisional suspensions in December for failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nKenteris and Thanou withdrew from the Athens Olympics last August after missing drugs tests on the eve of the opening ceremony.",
    "id": "N_16",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenteris",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "compatriot",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "KenteriswhoandwhocompatriotwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhowerewhogivenwhoprovisionalwhosuspensionswhoinwhoDecemberwhoforwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nKenteriswhoandwhoThanouwhowithdrewwhofromwhothewhoAthenswhoOlympicswholastwhoAugustwhoafterwhomissingwhodrugswhotestswhoonwhothewhoevewhoofwhothewhoopeningwhoceremony.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Teenager LaShawn Merritt ran the third fastest indoor 400m of all time at the Fayetteville Invitational meeting.\r\nKenyan Bernard Lagat missed out on the world record by 1.45secs as he ran the third quickest indoor mile ever to beat Canada's Nate Brannen by almost 10secs.\r\nThe Olympic silver medallist's time of three minutes 49.89secs was inferior only to the 1997 world record of Moroccan Hicham El Guerrouj and former world record holder Eamonn Coghlan of Ireland's 3:49.78.",
    "id": "N_17",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Teenager",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "ran",
        "adjective": "third",
        "adverb": "ever"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Teenager LaShawn who ran the third fastest indoor 400m of all time at the Fayetteville Invitational meeting.\r\nKenyan Bernard Lagat missed out on the world record by 1.45secs as he ran the third quickest indoor mile ever to beat Canada's Nate Brannen by almost 10secs.\r\nThe Olympic silver medallist's time of three minutes 49.89secs was inferior only to the 1997 world record of Moroccan Hicham El Guerrouj and former world record holder Eamonn Coghlan of Ireland's 3:49.78.?",
        "answer": "Merritt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "London Marathon organisers are hoping that banned athlete Susan Chepkemei will still take part in this year's race on 17 April.",
    "id": "N_18",
    "features": {
        "noun": "London",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "athlete",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "London Marathon organisers are hoping that banned athlete Susan who will still take part in this year's race on 17 April.?",
        "answer": "Chepkemei"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World outdoor triple jump record holder and BBC pundit Jonathan Edwards believes Phillips Idowu can take gold at the European Indoor Championships.\r\n\"It's all down to him, but if he jumps as well as he did in Sheffield he could win the gold medal,\" said Edwards.",
    "id": "N_19",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "triple",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhatoutdoorwhattriplewhatjumpwhatrecordwhatholderwhatandwhatBBCwhatpunditwhatJonathanwhatEdwardswhatbelieveswhatPhillipswhatIdowuwhatcanwhattakewhatgoldwhatatwhatthewhatEuropeanwhatIndoorwhatChampionships.\r\n\"It'swhatallwhatdownwhattowhathim,whatbutwhatifwhathewhatjumpswhataswhatwellwhataswhathewhatdidwhatinwhatSheffieldwhathewhatcouldwhatwinwhatthewhatgoldwhatmedal,\"whatsaidwhatEdwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kenya's athletics body has suspended two-time London Marathon runner-up Susan Chepkemei from all competition until the end of the year.\r\nGlobal Sports Communications, Chepkemei's management company, said she had wanted to run in the World Cross Country Championships in March.",
    "id": "N_20",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kenya's",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "two-time",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kenya's athletics what has suspended two-time London Marathon runner-up Susan Chepkemei from all competition until the end of the year.\r\nGlobal Sports Communications, Chepkemei's management company, said she had wanted to run in the World Cross Country Championships in March.?",
        "answer": "body"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Britain's Kelly Holmes marked her first appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold with 1500m victory at the Norwich Union International.\r\nHolmes hit the front just before the bell in front of a sell-out crowd in Glasgow and cruised to victory in a time of four minutes 14.74 seconds.",
    "id": "N_21",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Britain's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "marked",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Britain's Kelly who marked her first appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold with 1500m victory at the Norwich Union International.\r\nwho hit the front just before the bell in front of a sell-out crowd in Glasgow and cruised to victory in a time of four minutes 14.74 seconds.?",
        "answer": "Holmes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek sprinters Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou have appeared before an independent tribunal which will decide if their bans should stand.\r\nThey were given provisional suspensions by athletics' ruling body the IAAF in December for failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nYiannis Papadoyiannakis, who was head of the Greek Olympic team at the Athens Games last year, also testified at the tribunal, along with other Greek sports officials and athletes.\r\nThe five-member tribunal, assembled by the Hellenic Association of Amateur Athletics, is also examining allegations that Kenteris and Thanou avoided tests in Tel Aviv and Chicago before the Games.",
    "id": "N_22",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinters",
        "pronoun": "They",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "GreekwhosprinterswhoKostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhohavewhoappearedwhobeforewhoanwhoindependentwhotribunalwhowhichwhowillwhodecidewhoifwhotheirwhobanswhoshouldwhostand.\r\nTheywhowerewhogivenwhoprovisionalwhosuspensionswhobywhoathletics'whorulingwhobodywhothewhoIAAFwhoinwhoDecemberwhoforwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nYianniswhoPapadoyiannakis,whowhowhowaswhoheadwhoofwhothewhoGreekwhoOlympicwhoteamwhoatwhothewhoAthenswhoGameswholastwhoyear,whoalsowhotestifiedwhoatwhothewhotribunal,whoalongwhowithwhootherwhoGreekwhosportswhoofficialswhoandwhoathletes.\r\nThewhofive-memberwhotribunal,whoassembledwhobywhothewhoHellenicwhoAssociationwhoofwhoAmateurwhoAthletics,whoiswhoalsowhoexaminingwhoallegationswhothatwhoKenteriswhoandwhoThanouwhoavoidedwhotestswhoinwhoTelwhoAvivwhoandwhoChicagowhobeforewhothewhoGames.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Race director Matthew Turnbull said: \"Susan will add even more strength in depth to the world-class line up.\" Chepkemei, who won the six kilometre event three years ago when it was staged in Newcastle, endured an epic battle with Radcliffe in the Big Apple until the Briton outsprinted her in the final 400m.",
    "id": "N_23",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Race",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "add",
        "adjective": "more",
        "adverb": "even"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Race director Matthew Turnbull said: \"who will add even more strength in depth to the world-class line up.\" Chepkemei, who won the six kilometre event three years ago when it was staged in Newcastle, endured an epic battle with Radcliffe in the Big Apple until the Briton outsprinted her in the final 400m.?",
        "answer": "Susan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Double Olympic champion Hicham El Guerrouj is set to make a rare appearance at the World Cross Country Championships in France.\r\nBut the Moroccan, who has not raced over cross country for 15 years, will not decide until two weeks before the event which starts on 19 March.",
    "id": "N_24",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "Double",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Double Olympic champion Hicham El Guerrouj is set to make a rare appearance at the World Cross Country Championships in which location.\r\nBut the Moroccan, who has not raced over cross country for 15 years, will not decide until two weeks before the event which starts on 19 March.?",
        "answer": "France"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sprinter Michelle Collins has lodged an appeal against her eight-year doping ban with the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).",
    "id": "N_25",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sprinter",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "eight-year",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Sprinter Michelle who has lodged an appeal against her eight-year doping ban with the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).?",
        "answer": "Collins"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Briton, made a dame in the New Year Honours List for taking 800m and 1,500m gold, won vital votes from the public, press and EAA member federations.",
    "id": "N_26",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Briton,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "made",
        "adjective": "vital",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoBriton,whomadewhoawhodamewhoinwhothewhoNewwhoYearwhoHonourswhoListwhoforwhotakingwho800mwhoandwho1,500mwhogold,whowonwhovitalwhovoteswhofromwhothewhopublic,whopresswhoandwhoEAAwhomemberwhofederations.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The 31-year-old, who won Olympic 200m silver in Sydney in 2000, said during the Games that a hamstring injury had stopped him from running at his best.\r\n\"To go to Athens and finally get the gold I've been trying to get for 24 years was a big relief,\" said Campbell.\r\n\"It's just unfortunate that I picked up that injury just before the Olympics.\" Campbell set his 100m personal best of 10.04secs when he won the European title in Budapest in 1998.",
    "id": "N_27",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "won",
        "adjective": "31-year-old,",
        "adverb": "finally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The 31-year-old, who won Olympic 200m silver in Sydney in 2000, said during the Games that a hamstring what had stopped him from running at his best.\r\n\"To go to Athens and finally get the gold I've been trying to get for 24 years was a big relief,\" said Campbell.\r\n\"It's just unfortunate that I picked up that what just before the Olympics.\" Campbell set his 100m personal best of 10.04secs when he won the European title in Budapest in 1998.?",
        "answer": "injury"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Olympic pole vault champion Yelena Isinbayeva has confirmed she will take part in the 2005 Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham on 18 February.",
    "id": "N_28",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Olympic pole vault champion Yelena Isinbayeva has confirmed who will take part in the 2005 Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham on 18 February.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But come late August, a few hot days in the magnificent stadium in Athens told us of the true strength of Irish athletics - or to be more accurate, the lack of it.\r\nSonia O'Sullivan's Olympic farewell apart, there was little to stir the emotions of Irish athletics watchers.\r\nAt the start of the year, an O'Sullivan had been earmarked as Ireland's best medal prospect but as it turned out, walker Gillian never even made it to the start line because of injury.\r\nOnce the track and field action began in Athens, a familiar pattern of underachievement emerged although Alistair Cragg's performance in being the only athlete from a European nation to qualify for the 5,000m final did offer hope for the future.\r\nAt the start of the year, several Northern Ireland athletes had genuine hopes of qualifying for the Games but come August, an out-of-form and injured Paul Brizzel was the lone standard bearer for the province.",
    "id": "N_29",
    "features": {
        "noun": "August,",
        "pronoun": "us",
        "verb": "come",
        "adjective": "few",
        "adverb": "late"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He told the Herald newspaper: \"I'm not in great shape, after missing about a month of training.",
    "id": "N_30",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Herald",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "great",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "He told the Herald newspaper: \"who'm not in great shape, after missing about a month of training.?",
        "answer": "I"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Olympic 10,000m champion Kenenisa Bekele is determined to add the world indoor two mile record at February's Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham.\r\nThe 22-year-old will again be chasing a record held by his compatriot and mentor Haile Gebrselassie, who set the mark at the same meeting in 2003.",
    "id": "N_31",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "22-year-old",
        "adverb": "again"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Olympic 10,000m champion Kenenisa who is determined to add the world indoor two mile record at February's Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham.\r\nThe 22-year-old will again be chasing a record held by his compatriot and mentor Haile Gebrselassie, who set the mark at the same meeting in 2003.?",
        "answer": "Bekele"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek sprinters Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou have been suspended after failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nAthletics' ruling body the IAAF said explanations from the pair and their former coach as to why they missed the tests were \"unacceptable\".\r\nKenteris, the 2000 Olympic 200m champion, and Thanou, the women's 100m silver medallist from the same Games in Sydney, also face a criminal hearing in Greece over the missed tests.",
    "id": "N_32",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinters",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "why"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "GreekwhosprinterswhoKostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhohavewhobeenwhosuspendedwhoafterwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nAthletics'whorulingwhobodywhothewhoIAAFwhosaidwhoexplanationswhofromwhothewhopairwhoandwhotheirwhoformerwhocoachwhoaswhotowhowhywhotheywhomissedwhothewhotestswhowerewho\"unacceptable\".\r\nKenteris,whothewho2000whoOlympicwho200mwhochampion,whoandwhoThanou,whothewhowomen'swho100mwhosilverwhomedallistwhofromwhothewhosamewhoGameswhoinwhoSydney,whoalsowhofacewhoawhocriminalwhohearingwhoinwhoGreecewhooverwhothewhomissedwhotests.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Well, it's goodbye to another Olympic year and as usual there were plenty of highs and lows in Athens.\r\nThe victory for the British men's 4x100m relay team was a bit of a surprise but a great climax to the Games.\r\nWhat happened to Paula in Athens this year is the obvious low on a personal level and for the expectations of the nation as well.\r\nAnd if even the smallest thing doesn't feel right when you are preparing to race a marathon, 10 miles down the road it will hit you like a brick wall.\r\nThe positive thing to take from Paula's Olympics it that she will have learned a lot from it and so will a lot of people - including me.\r\nPurely as a race, Paula's victory in the New York Marathon has to go down as one of the most thrilling.\r\nAnd that's where things begin to look even gloomier for British athletics as we did not win any medals at the world junior championships in Italy.\r\nThe thing is if we don't have athletes getting into the finals at junior level then it really doesn't look good for the Beijing Olympics and beyond.\r\nAnd one of the positive things to come out of Balco is people are starting to blow the whistle.",
    "id": "N_33",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Well,",
        "pronoun": "What",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "usual",
        "adverb": "even"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Well,whoit'swhogoodbyewhotowhoanotherwhoOlympicwhoyearwhoandwhoaswhousualwhotherewhowerewhoplentywhoofwhohighswhoandwholowswhoinwhoAthens.\r\nThewhovictorywhoforwhothewhoBritishwhomen'swho4x100mwhorelaywhoteamwhowaswhoawhobitwhoofwhoawhosurprisewhobutwhoawhogreatwhoclimaxwhotowhothewhoGames.\r\nWhatwhohappenedwhotowhoPaulawhoinwhoAthenswhothiswhoyearwhoiswhothewhoobviouswholowwhoonwhoawhopersonalwholevelwhoandwhoforwhothewhoexpectationswhoofwhothewhonationwhoaswhowell.\r\nAndwhoifwhoevenwhothewhosmallestwhothingwhodoesn'twhofeelwhorightwhowhenwhoyouwhoarewhopreparingwhotowhoracewhoawhomarathon,who10whomileswhodownwhothewhoroadwhoitwhowillwhohitwhoyouwholikewhoawhobrickwhowall.\r\nThewhopositivewhothingwhotowhotakewhofromwhoPaula'swhoOlympicswhoitwhothatwhoshewhowillwhohavewholearnedwhoawholotwhofromwhoitwhoandwhosowhowillwhoawholotwhoofwhopeoplewho-whoincludingwhome.\r\nPurelywhoaswhoawhorace,whoPaula'swhovictorywhoinwhothewhoNewwhoYorkwhoMarathonwhohaswhotowhogowhodownwhoaswhoonewhoofwhothewhomostwhothrilling.\r\nAndwhothat'swhowherewhothingswhobeginwhotowholookwhoevenwhogloomierwhoforwhoBritishwhoathleticswhoaswhowewhodidwhonotwhowinwhoanywhomedalswhoatwhothewhoworldwhojuniorwhochampionshipswhoinwhoItaly.\r\nThewhothingwhoiswhoifwhowewhodon'twhohavewhoathleteswhogettingwhointowhothewhofinalswhoatwhojuniorwholevelwhothenwhoitwhoreallywhodoesn'twholookwhogoodwhoforwhothewhoBeijingwhoOlympicswhoandwhobeyond.\r\nAndwhoonewhoofwhothewhopositivewhothingswhotowhocomewhooutwhoofwhoBalcowhoiswhopeoplewhoarewhostartingwhotowhoblowwhothewhowhistle.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sprinter Michelle Collins has received an eight-year ban for doping offences after a hearing at the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).\r\nCollins' ban is a result of her connection to the federal inquiry into the Balco doping scandal.\r\n\"Collins used these substances to enhance her performance and elude the drug testing that was available at the time.\" So far a total of 13 athletes have been sanctioned for violations involving drugs associated with the Balco doping scandal.",
    "id": "N_34",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sprinter",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "eight-year",
        "adverb": "far"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Sprinter Michelle who has received an eight-year ban for doping offences after a hearing at the North American Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS).\r\nwho' ban is a result of her connection to the federal inquiry into the Balco doping scandal.\r\n\"who used these substances to enhance her performance and elude the drug testing that was available at the time.\" So far a total of 13 athletes have been sanctioned for violations involving drugs associated with the Balco doping scandal.?",
        "answer": "Collins"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jones, who says she is innocent, could lose all her Olympic medals after Conte said he gave her performance-enhancing drugs before the Sydney Olympics.\r\nThe Sydney Olympics ended more than four years ago, but World Anti-Doping Agency chief Dick Pound said the rule may not apply because the allegations are only coming out now.",
    "id": "N_35",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jones,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "innocent,",
        "adverb": "more"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jones, who says swho is innocent, could lose all whor Olympic medals after Conte said who gave whor performance-enhancing drugs before twho Sydney Olympics.\r\nTwho Sydney Olympics ended more than four years ago, but World Anti-Doping Agency chief Dick Pound said twho rule may not apply because twho allegations are only coming out now.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former Olympic champion Michael Johnson has accused Britain's top sprinters of lacking pride and ambition.\r\n\"Athletics at the moment is all about international competitions and they need to show a little more pride.\" However, Linford Christie countered: \"It's easy to criticise when you haven't gone through the system here.\" Johnson was involved in a verbal spat with Britain's Darren Campbell earlier this year.",
    "id": "N_36",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "top",
        "adverb": "little"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "FormerwhoOlympicwhochampionwhoMichaelwhoJohnsonwhohaswhoaccusedwhoBritain'swhotopwhosprinterswhoofwholackingwhopridewhoandwhoambition.\r\n\"Athleticswhoatwhothewhomomentwhoiswhoallwhoaboutwhointernationalwhocompetitionswhoandwhotheywhoneedwhotowhoshowwhoawholittlewhomorewhopride.\"whoHowever,whoLinfordwhoChristiewhocountered:who\"It'swhoeasywhotowhocriticisewhowhenwhoyouwhohaven'twhogonewhothroughwhothewhosystemwhohere.\"whoJohnsonwhowaswhoinvolvedwhoinwhoawhoverbalwhospatwhowithwhoBritain'swhoDarrenwhoCampbellwhoearlierwhothiswhoyear.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A win in the New York marathon doesn't make up for the disappointment of Athens in any shape or form, but it will offer hope and reassurance for next year.\r\nIf Paula's last experience of the year had been Athens, it would have been very difficult to look forward with any optimism.\r\nAnd a lot of people were wondering what would happen if Paula was forced to drop out of this race, as she did in the marathon and 10,000m in Athens.\r\nNow Paula will take part in the Run London 10km race in London at the end of the year, have a well-earned rest over Christmas and go into next year with a lot of optimism.",
    "id": "N_37",
    "features": {
        "noun": "win",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA) chief Dick Pound says Marion Jones should be stripped of all her medals if found guilty of taking banned substances.",
    "id": "N_38",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "guilty",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "World Anti-Doping Agency (WADA) chief Dick Pound says Marion who should be stripped of all her medals if found guilty of taking banned substances.?",
        "answer": "Jones"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Paula Radcliffe faces arguably the biggest test of her career in the New York City Marathon on Sunday.\r\nBack under the spotlight of public scrutiny she will attempt to erase the double disappointment of the Athens Olympics, where she failed to finish the marathon and then the 10,000m.\r\n\"She must not get caught up in someone else's agenda.\" Radcliffe's best friend and fellow distance runner Liz Yelling revealed the 30-year-old is already aware she will be exposing herself to more public scrutiny in New York.\r\nRadcliffe described her decision to enter the New York marathon as \"impulsive\" but she is certain to have a tick-list of personal goals.\r\nRadcliffe has never raced there before and will enter the unknown just 77 days after the Athens marathon.\r\nSo physically it is possible for Paula.\" Richards also points out conditions in New York will be more conducive to a strong physical display from Radcliffe.\r\nAnd Richards and Yelling agree she could turn the trauma to her advantage, starting in New York.",
    "id": "N_39",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Paula",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "faces",
        "adjective": "biggest",
        "adverb": "arguably"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Paula who faces arguably the biggest test of her career in the New York City Marathon on Sunday.\r\nBack under the spotlight of public scrutiny she will attempt to erase the double disappointment of the Athens Olympics, where she failed to finish the marathon and then the 10,000m.\r\n\"She must not get caught up in someone else's agenda.\" who's best friend and fellow distance runner Liz Yelling revealed the 30-year-old is already aware she will be exposing herself to more public scrutiny in New York.\r\nwho described her decision to enter the New York marathon as \"impulsive\" but she is certain to have a tick-list of personal goals.\r\nwho has never raced there before and will enter the unknown just 77 days after the Athens marathon.\r\nSo physically it is possible for Paula.\" Richards also points out conditions in New York will be more conducive to a strong physical display from who.\r\nAnd Richards and Yelling agree she could turn the trauma to her advantage, starting in New York.?",
        "answer": "Radcliffe"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "American Olympic stars Justin Gatlin and Joanna Hayes have been named the winners of the 2004 Jesse Owens Awards, USA Track & Field's (USATF) top honour.\r\nEstablished in 1981, the Jesse Owens Awards - named in honour of the late Olympic great who won four gold medals at the 1936 Berlin Games - are presented annually to the outstanding US male and female track and field performers.",
    "id": "N_40",
    "features": {
        "noun": "American",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "stars",
        "adjective": "top",
        "adverb": "annually"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "AmericanwhoOlympicwhostarswhoJustinwhoGatlinwhoandwhoJoannawhoHayeswhohavewhobeenwhonamedwhothewhowinnerswhoofwhothewho2004whoJessewhoOwenswhoAwards,whoUSAwhoTrackwho&whoField'swho(USATF)whotopwhohonour.\r\nEstablishedwhoinwho1981,whothewhoJessewhoOwenswhoAwardswho-whonamedwhoinwhohonourwhoofwhothewholatewhoOlympicwhogreatwhowhowhowonwhofourwhogoldwhomedalswhoatwhothewho1936whoBerlinwhoGameswho-whoarewhopresentedwhoannuallywhotowhothewhooutstandingwhoUSwhomalewhoandwhofemalewhotrackwhoandwhofieldwhoperformers.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Briton, running for the first time since dropping out of the Olympic marathon and 10,000m, held off Kenyan Susan Chepkemei in a thrilling finish.\r\nBut it was Radcliffe who managed to dredge up a final sprint to see off Chepkemei in the closest finish in the race's history and in the process make a huge step in erasing the disappointment she suffered in Athens.",
    "id": "N_41",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Briton,",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "dropping",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoBriton,whorunningwhoforwhothewhofirstwhotimewhosincewhodroppingwhooutwhoofwhothewhoOlympicwhomarathonwhoandwho10,000m,whoheldwhooffwhoKenyanwhoSusanwhoChepkemeiwhoinwhoawhothrillingwhofinish.\r\nButwhoitwhowaswhoRadcliffewhowhowhomanagedwhotowhodredgewhoupwhoawhofinalwhosprintwhotowhoseewhooffwhoChepkemeiwhoinwhothewhoclosestwhofinishwhoinwhothewhorace'swhohistorywhoandwhoinwhothewhoprocesswhomakewhoawhohugewhostepwhoinwhoerasingwhothewhodisappointmentwhoshewhosufferedwhoinwhoAthens.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "UK Athletics has ended its search for a new performance director by appointing psychologist Dave Collins.\r\nSix candidates were interviewed for the job, including Denise Lewis' coach Charles van Commenee and former British triple jumper Keith Connor.\r\nHe is currently professor of physical education and sport performance at Edinburgh University, where he helps competitors across many sports, including rugby, athletics, judo and football.\r\nHe has specialised in helping competitors fulfil their potential through psychology and has worked with the Great Britain women's curling team, who won gold at the 2002 Winter Olympics.",
    "id": "N_42",
    "features": {
        "noun": "UK",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": "currently"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "UK who has ended its search for a new performance director by appointing psychologist Dave Collins.\r\nSix candidates were interviewed for the job, including Denise Lewis' coach Charles van Commenee and former British triple jumper Keith Connor.\r\nHe is currently professor of physical education and sport performance at Edinburgh University, where he helps competitors across many sports, including rugby, athletics, judo and football.\r\nHe has specialised in helping competitors fulfil their potential through psychology and has worked with the Great Britain women's curling team, who won gold at the 2002 Winter Olympics.?",
        "answer": "Athletics"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Banned American sprinter Kelli White says she knowingly took steroids given to her by Bay Area Lab Co-Operative (Balco) president Victor Conte.\r\nBut she added: \"It was my decision to go to him, not anybody else's.\" White said Conte at first told her the substance was flaxseed oil, only to change his story later.",
    "id": "N_43",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinter",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "Banned",
        "adjective": "American",
        "adverb": "knowingly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Banned American sprinter Kelli White says who knowingly took steroids given to her by Bay Area Lab Co-Operative (Balco) president Victor Conte.\r\nBut who added: \"It was my decision to go to him, not anybody else's.\" White said Conte at first told her the substance was flaxseed oil, only to change his story later.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A US judge has set a preliminary trial date for the Balco steroid distribution case which has rocked athletics.\r\nAnd she set a March date for the case of the four men accused of distributing illegal performance-enhancing drugs to elite athletes to be heard.\r\nThe judge said that she may conduct hearings in January into whether federal agents illegally searched the Balco headquarters and wrongfully obtained statements from the company's founder Victor Conte and its vice-president James Valente.",
    "id": "N_44",
    "features": {
        "noun": "US",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "preliminary",
        "adverb": "illegally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "which"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Paula Radcliffe has called for all athletes found guilty on drugs charges to be treated as criminals.\r\nThe marathon world record holder believes more needs to be done to rid athletics of the \"suspicions and innuendoes\" which greet any fast time.",
    "id": "N_45",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Paula",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "guilty",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Paula who has called for all athletes found guilty on drugs charges to be treated as criminals.\r\nThe marathon world record holder believes more needs to be done to rid athletics of the \"suspicions and innuendoes\" which greet any fast time.?",
        "answer": "Radcliffe"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek sprinter Kostas Kenteris has denied claims that he faked a motorbike crash to avoid a doping test days before the start of the Olympics.\r\nI want to go to the end and then we'll see who's right and who isn't.\" Kenteris, a Greek hero after winning gold in the 200m at the 2000 Olympics in Sydney, also confirmed that he was due to light the flame at the Athens opening ceremony.",
    "id": "N_46",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinter",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Greek sprinter Kostas Kenteris has denied claims that who faked a motorbike crash to avoid a doping test days before twho start of twho Olympics.\r\nI want to go to twho end and twhon we'll see who's right and who isn't.\" Kenteris, a Greek whoro after winning gold in twho 200m at twho 2000 Olympics in Sydney, also confirmed that who was due to light twho flame at twho Atwhons opening ceremony.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou will fight the provisional two-year bans imposed on them by the IAAF at an independent tribunal this weekend.\r\nAthletics' ruling body took action against the pair for failing to take drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\nKenteris and Thanou also face criminal charges in Greece for allegedly faking the motorcycle accident.",
    "id": "N_47",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kostas",
        "pronoun": "them",
        "verb": "fight",
        "adjective": "provisional",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "KostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhowillwhofightwhothewhoprovisionalwhotwo-yearwhobanswhoimposedwhoonwhothemwhobywhothewhoIAAFwhoatwhoanwhoindependentwhotribunalwhothiswhoweekend.\r\nAthletics'whorulingwhobodywhotookwhoactionwhoagainstwhothewhopairwhoforwhofailingwhotowhotakewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\nKenteriswhoandwhoThanouwhoalsowhofacewhocriminalwhochargeswhoinwhoGreecewhoforwhoallegedlywhofakingwhothewhomotorcyclewhoaccident.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Marion Jones has filed a lawsuit for defamation against Balco boss Victor Conte following his allegations that he gave her performance-enhancing drugs.\r\nHer lawsuit, filed in the US District Court in San Francisco, said the sprinter had passed a lie detector test and that she \"has never taken banned performance-enhancing drugs\".\r\n\"Mr Conte chose to make unsubstantiated allegations on television, while Marion Jones demanded to take and then passed a lie detector examination.\r\nWe challenge him to submit to the same lie detector procedure that Marion Jones passed.\" The sport's ruling body, the IAAF, is taking a cautious approach to Conte's allegations but contacted the US Anti-Doping Agency.",
    "id": "N_48",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Marion",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "performance-enhancing",
        "adverb": "never"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Marion Jones has filed a lawsuit for defamation against Balco boss Victor Conte following his allegations that who gave whor performance-enhancing drugs.\r\nHer lawsuit, filed in twho US District Court in San Francisco, said twho sprinter had passed a lie detector test and that swho \"has never taken banned performance-enhancing drugs\".\r\n\"Mr Conte chose to make unsubstantiated allegations on television, while Marion Jones demanded to take and twhon passed a lie detector examination.\r\nWe challenge him to submit to twho same lie detector procedure that Marion Jones passed.\" Twho sport's ruling body, twho IAAF, is taking a cautious approach to Conte's allegations but contacted twho US Anti-Doping Agency.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Greek pair were charged after missing a series of routine drugs tests in Tel Aviv, Chicago and Athens.\r\nKenteris and Thanou already face a criminal trial after being charged with avoiding a drug test on the eve of the Athens Olympics and then faking a motorcyle crash.",
    "id": "N_49",
    "features": {
        "noun": "pair",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "already"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhatGreekwhatpairwhatwerewhatchargedwhatafterwhatmissingwhatawhatserieswhatofwhatroutinewhatdrugswhattestswhatinwhatTelwhatAviv,whatChicagowhatandwhatAthens.\r\nKenteriswhatandwhatThanouwhatalreadywhatfacewhatawhatcriminalwhattrialwhatafterwhatbeingwhatchargedwhatwithwhatavoidingwhatawhatdrugwhattestwhatonwhatthewhatevewhatofwhatthewhatAthenswhatOlympicswhatandwhatthenwhatfakingwhatawhatmotorcylewhatcrash.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greek sprinters Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou are expected to find out on Wednesday if they will be banned for missing drugs tests this summer.\r\nThe Greek authorities have also brought criminal charges against the sprinters for avoiding a drugs test and faking an accident.\r\nThe sport's ruling body is expected to direct the Greek federation in what action it should take against the sprinters.",
    "id": "N_50",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sprinters",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "GreekwhosprinterswhoKostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhoarewhoexpectedwhotowhofindwhooutwhoonwhoWednesdaywhoifwhotheywhowillwhobewhobannedwhoforwhomissingwhodrugswhotestswhothiswhosummer.\r\nThewhoGreekwhoauthoritieswhohavewhoalsowhobroughtwhocriminalwhochargeswhoagainstwhothewhosprinterswhoforwhoavoidingwhoawhodrugswhotestwhoandwhofakingwhoanwhoaccident.\r\nThewhosport'swhorulingwhobodywhoiswhoexpectedwhotowhodirectwhothewhoGreekwhofederationwhoinwhowhatwhoactionwhoitwhoshouldwhotakewhoagainstwhothewhosprinters.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Holmes will make her first track appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold in January's Norwich Union International in Glasgow.",
    "id": "N_51",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Holmes",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who will make her first track appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold in January's Norwich Union International in Glasgow.?",
        "answer": "Holmes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Double Olympic 10,000m champion Haile Gebrselassie will race in the London Marathon for the next three years.",
    "id": "N_52",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Double",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Double Olympic 10,000m champion Haile who will race in the London Marathon for the next three years.?",
        "answer": "Gebrselassie"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Katerina Thanou is confident she and fellow sprinter Kostas Kenteris will not be punished for missing drugs tests before the Athens Olympics.\r\n\"We believe that we have presented [a case] that the charges are unreasonable.\" Thanou, the 2000 Olympic women's 100m silver medallist, and Sydney 200m champion Kenteris were suspended by the IAAF for missing three drugs tests.\r\nAs far as I am concerned there is no such issue [of refusing to be tested], and I am very optimistic.\" Tzekos, Thanou and Kenteris, who have all denied the charges, can expect a decision within a month.",
    "id": "N_53",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Katerina",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "confident",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "KaterinawhoThanouwhoiswhoconfidentwhoshewhoandwhofellowwhosprinterwhoKostaswhoKenteriswhowillwhonotwhobewhopunishedwhoforwhomissingwhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoOlympics.\r\n\"Wewhobelievewhothatwhowewhohavewhopresentedwho[awhocase]whothatwhothewhochargeswhoarewhounreasonable.\"whoThanou,whothewho2000whoOlympicwhowomen'swho100mwhosilverwhomedallist,whoandwhoSydneywho200mwhochampionwhoKenteriswhowerewhosuspendedwhobywhothewhoIAAFwhoforwhomissingwhothreewhodrugswhotests.\r\nAswhofarwhoaswhoIwhoamwhoconcernedwhotherewhoiswhonowhosuchwhoissuewho[ofwhorefusingwhotowhobewhotested],whoandwhoIwhoamwhoverywhooptimistic.\"whoTzekos,whoThanouwhoandwhoKenteris,whowhowhohavewhoallwhodeniedwhothewhocharges,whocanwhoexpectwhoawhodecisionwhowithinwhoawhomonth.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kelly Holmes has been forced out of this weekend's European Indoor Athletics Championships after picking up a hamstring injury during training.\r\nAfter that race and more progress in training, Holmes revealed she had decided to compete at the European Indoors before her plans were wrecked last weekend.",
    "id": "N_54",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kelly",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "weekend's",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kelly who has been forced out of this weekend's European Indoor Athletics Championships after picking up a hamstring injury during training.\r\nAfter that race and more progress in training, who revealed she had decided to compete at the European Indoors before her plans were wrecked last weekend.?",
        "answer": "Holmes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"She looked very good early in the season and was competing really well.\" Kluft showed impressive early-season form on Tuesday in Stockholm's GE Galan meeting, winning the sprint hurdles, the long jump and the 400m.",
    "id": "N_55",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"She",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "looked",
        "adjective": "good",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Shewholookedwhoverywhogoodwhoearlywhoinwhothewhoseasonwhoandwhowaswhocompetingwhoreallywhowell.\"whoKluftwhoshowedwhoimpressivewhoearly-seasonwhoformwhoonwhoTuesdaywhoinwhoStockholm'swhoGEwhoGalanwhomeeting,whowinningwhothewhosprintwhohurdles,whothewholongwhojumpwhoandwhothewho400m.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Last April, Kelly Holmes spoke to the BBC Sport website about her loneliness, her fight to stay fit and her decision not to contest both the 800m and 1500m at the Olympics.\r\nFour months later, Holmes stormed to double Olympic gold and has since been made a Dame, won the BBC Sport Personality of the Year and written a book whilst still finding time to coach aspiring athletes.\r\nBut should we be surprised if the Olympic champion over both those distances decides she just does not feel like racing anymore?\r\n\"Well, it's a lot easier being the double Olympic champion, being feted by everybody, than training to be at the top in middle distance running,\" points out former Olympian and BBC pundit Steve Cram.\r\nThe physical demands of the day-to-day grind will only get harder for Holmes, who has already admitted she \"doesn't like the training anymore.\" Whilst out on the circuit the allure of defeating a double Olympic champion will spur her opponents on.\r\n\"You don't get the chance very often in your career to step onto the track as the double Olympic champion,\" agreed Cram.\r\nAthletics fans had every reason to believe they would see the new-look Kelly Holmes tearing up the track again.",
    "id": "N_56",
    "features": {
        "noun": "April,",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "spoke",
        "adjective": "Last",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "LastwhoApril,whoKellywhoHolmeswhospokewhotowhothewhoBBCwhoSportwhowebsitewhoaboutwhoherwholoneliness,whoherwhofightwhotowhostaywhofitwhoandwhoherwhodecisionwhonotwhotowhocontestwhobothwhothewho800mwhoandwho1500mwhoatwhothewhoOlympics.\r\nFourwhomonthswholater,whoHolmeswhostormedwhotowhodoublewhoOlympicwhogoldwhoandwhohaswhosincewhobeenwhomadewhoawhoDame,whowonwhothewhoBBCwhoSportwhoPersonalitywhoofwhothewhoYearwhoandwhowrittenwhoawhobookwhowhilstwhostillwhofindingwhotimewhotowhocoachwhoaspiringwhoathletes.\r\nButwhoshouldwhowewhobewhosurprisedwhoifwhothewhoOlympicwhochampionwhooverwhobothwhothosewhodistanceswhodecideswhoshewhojustwhodoeswhonotwhofeelwholikewhoracingwhoanymore?\r\n\"Well,whoit'swhoawholotwhoeasierwhobeingwhothewhodoublewhoOlympicwhochampion,whobeingwhofetedwhobywhoeverybody,whothanwhotrainingwhotowhobewhoatwhothewhotopwhoinwhomiddlewhodistancewhorunning,\"whopointswhooutwhoformerwhoOlympianwhoandwhoBBCwhopunditwhoStevewhoCram.\r\nThewhophysicalwhodemandswhoofwhothewhoday-to-daywhogrindwhowillwhoonlywhogetwhoharderwhoforwhoHolmes,whowhowhohaswhoalreadywhoadmittedwhoshewho\"doesn'twholikewhothewhotrainingwhoanymore.\"whoWhilstwhooutwhoonwhothewhocircuitwhothewhoallurewhoofwhodefeatingwhoawhodoublewhoOlympicwhochampionwhowillwhospurwhoherwhoopponentswhoon.\r\n\"Youwhodon'twhogetwhothewhochancewhoverywhooftenwhoinwhoyourwhocareerwhotowhostepwhoontowhothewhotrackwhoaswhothewhodoublewhoOlympicwhochampion,\"whoagreedwhoCram.\r\nAthleticswhofanswhohadwhoeverywhoreasonwhotowhobelievewhotheywhowouldwhoseewhothewhonew-lookwhoKellywhoHolmeswhotearingwhoupwhothewhotrackwhoagain.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jason Gardener fought all the way to the line to narrowly claim the men's 60m title at the Norwich Union Indoor trials and AAAs Championships.\r\nThe world 60m champion got off to a rolling start and had to dig deep to dip ahead of Mark Findlay and Darren Chin, who both set personal bests.\r\n\"I still feel there's more life in me and I believe I can go faster.\" Gardener's performance in Sheffield could have been affected by the news, which he heard before his semi-final, that his European record had been broken Frenchman Ronald Pognon, who will be a real threat at the European Championships, set a new time of 6.45, one-hundreth of a second faster than Gardener's previous mark.\r\nThe 25-year-old set a new British record for the second time in seven days, clocking 7.96 seconds to finish ahead of rival Diane Allahgreen.\r\n\"All the years I've been running and I'm getting recognition.\" Claxton's time was also good enough to qualify for the European Championships.\r\nalso set a new championship mark in the men's triple jump title in Sheffield.\r\nThe 21-year-old ran a personal best of 53.45 seconds to win her first indoor title.\r\ncleared the required 1.90m to qualify for the European championships and claim the AAAs title in the women's high jump.\r\npowered to a new personal best of seven minutes, 56.86 seconds to defend his AAAs title in style.\r\nIt was the first time in 11 years the eight-minute barrier has been broken at the championships and was just within the European mark.",
    "id": "N_57",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jason",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "fought",
        "adjective": "rolling",
        "adverb": "narrowly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "JasonwhoGardenerwhofoughtwhoallwhothewhowaywhotowhothewholinewhotowhonarrowlywhoclaimwhothewhomen'swho60mwhotitlewhoatwhothewhoNorwichwhoUnionwhoIndoorwhotrialswhoandwhoAAAswhoChampionships.\r\nThewhoworldwho60mwhochampionwhogotwhooffwhotowhoawhorollingwhostartwhoandwhohadwhotowhodigwhodeepwhotowhodipwhoaheadwhoofwhoMarkwhoFindlaywhoandwhoDarrenwhoChin,whowhowhobothwhosetwhopersonalwhobests.\r\n\"Iwhostillwhofeelwhothere'swhomorewholifewhoinwhomewhoandwhoIwhobelievewhoIwhocanwhogowhofaster.\"whoGardener'swhoperformancewhoinwhoSheffieldwhocouldwhohavewhobeenwhoaffectedwhobywhothewhonews,whowhichwhohewhoheardwhobeforewhohiswhosemi-final,whothatwhohiswhoEuropeanwhorecordwhohadwhobeenwhobrokenwhoFrenchmanwhoRonaldwhoPognon,whowhowhowillwhobewhoawhorealwhothreatwhoatwhothewhoEuropeanwhoChampionships,whosetwhoawhonewwhotimewhoofwho6.45,whoone-hundrethwhoofwhoawhosecondwhofasterwhothanwhoGardener'swhopreviouswhomark.\r\nThewho25-year-oldwhosetwhoawhonewwhoBritishwhorecordwhoforwhothewhosecondwhotimewhoinwhosevenwhodays,whoclockingwho7.96whosecondswhotowhofinishwhoaheadwhoofwhorivalwhoDianewhoAllahgreen.\r\n\"AllwhothewhoyearswhoI'vewhobeenwhorunningwhoandwhoI'mwhogettingwhorecognition.\"whoClaxton'swhotimewhowaswhoalsowhogoodwhoenoughwhotowhoqualifywhoforwhothewhoEuropeanwhoChampionships.\r\nalsowhosetwhoawhonewwhochampionshipwhomarkwhoinwhothewhomen'swhotriplewhojumpwhotitlewhoinwhoSheffield.\r\nThewho21-year-oldwhoranwhoawhopersonalwhobestwhoofwho53.45whosecondswhotowhowinwhoherwhofirstwhoindoorwhotitle.\r\nclearedwhothewhorequiredwho1.90mwhotowhoqualifywhoforwhothewhoEuropeanwhochampionshipswhoandwhoclaimwhothewhoAAAswhotitlewhoinwhothewhowomen'swhohighwhojump.\r\npoweredwhotowhoawhonewwhopersonalwhobestwhoofwhosevenwhominutes,who56.86whosecondswhotowhodefendwhohiswhoAAAswhotitlewhoinwhostyle.\r\nItwhowaswhothewhofirstwhotimewhoinwho11whoyearswhothewhoeight-minutewhobarrierwhohaswhobeenwhobrokenwhoatwhothewhochampionshipswhoandwhowaswhojustwhowithinwhothewhoEuropeanwhomark.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "It was good to see athletes beginning to make steps forward, to see a few new faces and there were lots of personal bests kicking around.\r\nRunning sub-eight seconds twice in a week puts her right up there and if she repeats that in Madrid she will be close to picking up a medal.\r\nDiane Allahgreen has been our best hurdler for some time now and I think she was surprised to be beaten by Sarah.\r\nAnd knowing that she got the better of Diane in a head-to-head race will give Sarah confidence.\r\nIn fact, the men's 60m hurdles is so strong, I think the selectors will pick three hurdlers to go to Madrid.\r\nA lot of the athletes said the runway was not very helpful, so for Phillips to jump like that is a good performance.\r\nShe picked up three personal bests in the long jump, high jump and 60m hurdles and you can't ask for more than that.",
    "id": "N_58",
    "features": {
        "noun": "athletes",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "good",
        "adverb": "twice"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Meanwhile, Paul Brizzel and Anna Boyle reached the semi-finals of the 60m hurdles with Boyle setting a season's best of 7.48.\r\nGillick was more than half-a-second clear when taking gold in 46.45 - .02 outside his personal best set in Saturday's semi-finals.\r\nJames Nolan (3:46.04) took second in the men's 1500m behind Neil Speaight (3:45.86) but the Offaly man was outside the European Indoor standard.",
    "id": "N_59",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Meanwhile,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "reached",
        "adjective": "season's",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Meanwhile,whoPaulwhoBrizzelwhoandwhoAnnawhoBoylewhoreachedwhothewhosemi-finalswhoofwhothewho60mwhohurdleswhowithwhoBoylewhosettingwhoawhoseason'swhobestwhoofwho7.48.\r\nGillickwhowaswhomorewhothanwhohalf-a-secondwhoclearwhowhenwhotakingwhogoldwhoinwho46.45who-who.02whooutsidewhohiswhopersonalwhobestwhosetwhoinwhoSaturday'swhosemi-finals.\r\nJameswhoNolanwho(3:46.04)whotookwhosecondwhoinwhothewhomen'swho1500mwhobehindwhoNeilwhoSpeaightwho(3:45.86)whobutwhothewhoOffalywhomanwhowaswhooutsidewhothewhoEuropeanwhoIndoorwhostandard.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jade Johnson edged out rival Kelly Sotherton with her last effort to claim the AAAs long jump title at the Norwich Union European Indoor trials.\r\ncomfortably defended her 3,000m title, clocking eight minutes, 49.87 seconds to easily surpass the European qualifying mark.\r\nHelen Clitheroe was agonisingly close to the 9:05.00 qualifying mark as she claimed the runners-up spot in a personal best of 9:05.73.\r\nFraser became the fastest British woman over the distance this season when she qualified for the final in 23.68 seconds - though that time is outside the European standard.\r\nBut Deacon claimed her first AAAs title over the distance, edging Fraser into second in 23.67.\r\nclaimed the men's shot put title with a throw of 17.64m, which was below the qualifying mark.\r\nSale's Robert Mitchell climbed to a season's best of 2.20m - just 3cm short of the European standard - to claim the British indoor high jump title.",
    "id": "N_60",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jade",
        "pronoun": "her",
        "verb": "edged",
        "adjective": "rival",
        "adverb": "comfortably"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jade who edged out rival Kelly Sotherton with her last effort to claim the AAAs long jump title at the Norwich Union European Indoor trials.\r\ncomfortably defended her 3,000m title, clocking eight minutes, 49.87 seconds to easily surpass the European qualifying mark.\r\nHelen Clitheroe was agonisingly close to the 9:05.00 qualifying mark as she claimed the runners-up spot in a personal best of 9:05.73.\r\nFraser became the fastest British woman over the distance this season when she qualified for the final in 23.68 seconds - though that time is outside the European standard.\r\nBut Deacon claimed her first AAAs title over the distance, edging Fraser into second in 23.67.\r\nclaimed the men's shot put title with a throw of 17.64m, which was below the qualifying mark.\r\nSale's Robert Mitchell climbed to a season's best of 2.20m - just 3cm short of the European standard - to claim the British indoor high jump title.?",
        "answer": "Johnson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ballymena sprinter Paul Brizzel will be among eight of Ireland's European Indoor hopefuls competing in this weekend's AAA's Championships.\r\nIn-form James McIlroy will hope to confirm his place in the British team for Madrid by winning the 800m title.",
    "id": "N_61",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ballymena",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ballymena sprinter Paul who will be among eight of Ireland's European Indoor hopefuls competing in this weekend's AAA's Championships.\r\nIn-form James McIlroy will hope to confirm his place in the British team for Madrid by winning the 800m title.?",
        "answer": "Brizzel"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Double Olympic gold medallist Holmes has strongly hinted she will not run in this year's Worlds and is undecided about next month's European Indoors.\r\nBut the controversy has since been forgotten, with Ceplak acting as pacemaker for Holmes' failed attempt on the British Indoor 1500m record at the Norwich Union Grand Prix in Birmingham in 2003.",
    "id": "N_62",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Double",
        "adverb": "strongly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "DoublewhoOlympicwhogoldwhomedallistwhoHolmeswhohaswhostronglywhohintedwhoshewhowillwhonotwhorunwhoinwhothiswhoyear'swhoWorldswhoandwhoiswhoundecidedwhoaboutwhonextwhomonth'swhoEuropeanwhoIndoors.\r\nButwhothewhocontroversywhohaswhosincewhobeenwhoforgotten,whowithwhoCeplakwhoactingwhoaswhopacemakerwhoforwhoHolmes'whofailedwhoattemptwhoonwhothewhoBritishwhoIndoorwho1500mwhorecordwhoatwhothewhoNorwichwhoUnionwhoGrandwhoPrixwhoinwhoBirminghamwhoinwho2003.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "James McIlroy stormed to his second international victory in less than a week, claiming the men's 800m at the TEAG indoor meeting in Erfurt.\r\nThe Northern Ireland runner set a new personal best of one minute, 46.68 seconds - a time good enough to qualify for the European Indoor Championships.",
    "id": "N_63",
    "features": {
        "noun": "James",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "stormed",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": "enough"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "James who stormed to his second international victory in less than a week, claiming the men's 800m at the TEAG indoor meeting in Erfurt.\r\nThe Northern Ireland runner set a new personal best of one minute, 46.68 seconds - a time good enough to qualify for the European Indoor Championships.?",
        "answer": "McIlroy"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Bedford star returned to London 12 months later, lowering her mixed-race world record of 2:17:18, which she set in Chicago in October 2003, by one minute 53 secs.\r\nBut the 31-year-old bounced back to win the New York Marathon in November.\r\n\"Boston is definitely a race I want to do at some point, but London is very special to me,\" said Radcliffe.",
    "id": "N_64",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Bedford",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "returned",
        "adjective": "later,",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The Bedford star returned to London 12 months later, lowering her mixed-race world record of 2:17:18, which who set in Chicago in October 2003, by one minute 53 secs.\r\nBut the 31-year-old bounced back to win the New York Marathon in November.\r\n\"Boston is definitely a race I want to do at some point, but London is very special to me,\" said Radcliffe.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kelly Holmes finally fulfilled her potential by storming to double gold on the track at the Olympic Games.\r\nHolmes helped erase the gloom hanging over Team GB after their biggest medal hope, Paula Radcliffe, dropped out of the marathon and then the 10,000m.\r\nHolmes had started the year in disappointing style, falling over in the final of 1500m at the World Indoor Championships where she was favourite.\r\nThe 30-year-old marathon world record holder went into the Athens event as favourite but an exhausted Radcliffe dropped out after 23 miles in tears.\r\nGardener added the Olympic relay crown to his World Indoor title over 60m and, just like Holmes, finally lived up to his promise in 2004.\r\nKelly Sotherton completed Team GB's athletics medal haul in Athens with a surprise bronze in the heptathlon.\r\nThe battling 35-year-old leaves the sport with a vast medal haul including two silvers and one Olympic bronze.\r\nBritain's 4x100m team took gold without the services of Dwain Chambers, who was handed a two-year ban in February after testing positive for steroid THG.",
    "id": "N_65",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Holmes",
        "pronoun": "her",
        "verb": "fulfilled",
        "adjective": "potential",
        "adverb": "Kelly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kelly who finally fulfilled her potential by storming to double gold on the track at the Olympic Games.\r\nwho helped erase the gloom hanging over Team GB after their biggest medal hope, Paula Radcliffe, dropped out of the marathon and then the 10,000m.\r\nwho had started the year in disappointing style, falling over in the final of 1500m at the World Indoor Championships where she was favourite.\r\nThe 30-year-old marathon world record holder went into the Athens event as favourite but an exhausted Radcliffe dropped out after 23 miles in tears.\r\nGardener added the Olympic relay crown to his World Indoor title over 60m and, just like who, finally lived up to his promise in 2004.\r\nKelly Sotherton completed Team GB's athletics medal haul in Athens with a surprise bronze in the heptathlon.\r\nThe battling 35-year-old leaves the sport with a vast medal haul including two silvers and one Olympic bronze.\r\nBritain's 4x100m team took gold without the services of Dwain Chambers, who was handed a two-year ban in February after testing positive for steroid THG.?",
        "answer": "Holmes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Lewis-Francis eyeing world gold",
    "id": "N_66",
    "features": {
        "noun": "eyeing",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "",
        "adjective": "Lewis-Francis",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": ""
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kelly Holmes has been chosen for both the 800m and 1500m at next month's European Indoor Championships - despite not yet confirming her availability.\r\nThe double-Olympic champion is still undecided about whether to compete in her first European Indoors in Madrid.\r\nIt could depend on how training goes and she will have to be close to top form.\" And he admitted Holmes' presence would be a great boost to the rest of the Norwich Union GB team.\r\n60m: D Chin (Belgrave Harriers), J Gardener (Wessex and Bath), M Lewis-Francis (Birchfield Harriers).\r\nT Abeyie (Woodford Green with Essex Ladies), C Lambert (Belgrave Harriers).\r\nD Cossins (Birchfield Harriers), R Davenport (Gloucester AC), D Garland (Channel Islands AC), R Preddy (Gloucester AC), G Warburton (Cardiff AAC).\r\nH Clitheroe (Preston Harriers), K Holmes (Ealing, Southall and Middlesex AC).\r\nJ Crane (Sale Harriers Manchester), S Jones (Trafford AC).\r\nK Sotherton (Birchfield Harriers).",
    "id": "N_67",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kelly",
        "pronoun": "her",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "KellywhoHolmeswhohaswhobeenwhochosenwhoforwhobothwhothewho800mwhoandwho1500mwhoatwhonextwhomonth'swhoEuropeanwhoIndoorwhoChampionshipswho-whodespitewhonotwhoyetwhoconfirmingwhoherwhoavailability.\r\nThewhodouble-OlympicwhochampionwhoiswhostillwhoundecidedwhoaboutwhowhetherwhotowhocompetewhoinwhoherwhofirstwhoEuropeanwhoIndoorswhoinwhoMadrid.\r\nItwhocouldwhodependwhoonwhohowwhotrainingwhogoeswhoandwhoshewhowillwhohavewhotowhobewhoclosewhotowhotopwhoform.\"whoAndwhohewhoadmittedwhoHolmes'whopresencewhowouldwhobewhoawhogreatwhoboostwhotowhothewhorestwhoofwhothewhoNorwichwhoUnionwhoGBwhoteam.\r\n60m:whoDwhoChinwho(BelgravewhoHarriers),whoJwhoGardenerwho(WessexwhoandwhoBath),whoMwhoLewis-Franciswho(BirchfieldwhoHarriers).\r\nTwhoAbeyiewho(WoodfordwhoGreenwhowithwhoEssexwhoLadies),whoCwhoLambertwho(BelgravewhoHarriers).\r\nDwhoCossinswho(BirchfieldwhoHarriers),whoRwhoDavenportwho(GloucesterwhoAC),whoDwhoGarlandwho(ChannelwhoIslandswhoAC),whoRwhoPreddywho(GloucesterwhoAC),whoGwhoWarburtonwho(CardiffwhoAAC).\r\nHwhoClitheroewho(PrestonwhoHarriers),whoKwhoHolmeswho(Ealing,whoSouthallwhoandwhoMiddlesexwhoAC).\r\nJwhoCranewho(SalewhoHarrierswhoManchester),whoSwhoJoneswho(TraffordwhoAC).\r\nKwhoSothertonwho(BirchfieldwhoHarriers).?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Double Olympic champion Kelly Holmes was back to her best as she comfortably won the 1,000m at the Norwich Union Birmingham Indoor Grand Prix.\r\nThe 34-year-old, running only her second competitive race of the season, shook off the rust to win in two minutes, 35.39 seconds.\r\nThe Olympic champion set a new world mark of 4.88m to break her own record - which she set just six days ago - and beat Russian rival Svetlana Feofanova.\r\nThe Olympic champion set a new indoor personal best of 22.38 seconds - the fastest time in the world this season.\r\nThe 25-year-old Briton clocked 7.98 seconds while pre-European Championships favourite Russian Irina Shevchenko finished down in sixth.\r\nThe Olympic 5,000m champion was inside record pace but dropped off over the final third, finishing in eight minutes, 33.05 seconds - the fourth fastest time ever recorded for the event.\r\nWorld indoor champion, Alleyne Francique, faded badly and finished in fourth while American duo Jerry Harris and James Davis took second and third respectively.\r\nThe Olympic heptathlon gold medallist reached 6.66m to better Johnson's mark of 6.52m - her second personal best inside a week.\r\nwon the men's event with a season's best of 7.95m, taking the scalp of world indoor champion Savante Stringfellow of the USA.",
    "id": "N_68",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "Double",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Double Olympic champion Kelly Holmes was back to her best as who comfortably won the 1,000m at the Norwich Union Birmingham Indoor Grand Prix.\r\nThe 34-year-old, running only her second competitive race of the season, shook off the rust to win in two minutes, 35.39 seconds.\r\nThe Olympic champion set a new world mark of 4.88m to break her own record - which who set just six days ago - and beat Russian rival Svetlana Feofanova.\r\nThe Olympic champion set a new indoor personal best of 22.38 seconds - the fastest time in the world this season.\r\nThe 25-year-old Briton clocked 7.98 seconds while pre-European Championships favourite Russian Irina Shevchenko finiwhod down in sixth.\r\nThe Olympic 5,000m champion was inside record pace but dropped off over the final third, finishing in eight minutes, 33.05 seconds - the fourth fastest time ever recorded for the event.\r\nWorld indoor champion, Alleyne Francique, faded badly and finiwhod in fourth while American duo Jerry Harris and James Davis took second and third respectively.\r\nThe Olympic heptathlon gold medallist reached 6.66m to better Johnson's mark of 6.52m - her second personal best inside a week.\r\nwon the men's event with a season's best of 7.95m, taking the scalp of world indoor champion Savante Stringfellow of the USA.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Yelena Isinbayeva may have produced another world pole vault record, but her achievement could not hide the fact it was not the best meet we have ever seen in Birmingham.\r\nAnd hey, there are not many meets that go by without the Russian breaking a world record.\r\nAgnes Samaria, who came second, is in very good shape and is in the world's top three 800m runners this season.\r\nOn the other hand, I think Jason Gardener is struggling to come near what is going to be required to win the men's 60m in Madrid.\r\nBut I haven't seen anything from Mark or Jason yet which suggests France's Ronald Pognon - who has run 6.45 seconds - will be under threat at the Europeans.\r\nBut he has only just come over from the USA, so he may not be that sharp and I still think he is in great shape.",
    "id": "N_69",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Yelena",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "best",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "YelenawhoIsinbayevawhomaywhohavewhoproducedwhoanotherwhoworldwhopolewhovaultwhorecord,whobutwhoherwhoachievementwhocouldwhonotwhohidewhothewhofactwhoitwhowaswhonotwhothewhobestwhomeetwhowewhohavewhoeverwhoseenwhoinwhoBirmingham.\r\nAndwhohey,whotherewhoarewhonotwhomanywhomeetswhothatwhogowhobywhowithoutwhothewhoRussianwhobreakingwhoawhoworldwhorecord.\r\nAgneswhoSamaria,whowhowhocamewhosecond,whoiswhoinwhoverywhogoodwhoshapewhoandwhoiswhoinwhothewhoworld'swhotopwhothreewho800mwhorunnerswhothiswhoseason.\r\nOnwhothewhootherwhohand,whoIwhothinkwhoJasonwhoGardenerwhoiswhostrugglingwhotowhocomewhonearwhowhatwhoiswhogoingwhotowhobewhorequiredwhotowhowinwhothewhomen'swho60mwhoinwhoMadrid.\r\nButwhoIwhohaven'twhoseenwhoanythingwhofromwhoMarkwhoorwhoJasonwhoyetwhowhichwhosuggestswhoFrance'swhoRonaldwhoPognonwho-whowhowhohaswhorunwho6.45whosecondswho-whowillwhobewhounderwhothreatwhoatwhothewhoEuropeans.\r\nButwhohewhohaswhoonlywhojustwhocomewhooverwhofromwhothewhoUSA,whosowhohewhomaywhonotwhobewhothatwhosharpwhoandwhoIwhostillwhothinkwhohewhoiswhoinwhogreatwhoshape.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Birmingham athlete, who clocked a season's best of 6.61 seconds over 60m in Birmingham last week, also prefers to focus his attentions on next month's European Indoor Championships.",
    "id": "N_70",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Birmingham",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "clocked",
        "adjective": "season's",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "who"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "It was back to official duties last week in my role as an ambassador to London's 2012 Olympic bid.\r\nAll the sporting people on the capital's bid team think I'm mad to be taking part in the London Marathon.\r\nEven though it was a very busy week entertaining the International Olympic Committee's (IOC) Evaluation Commission, I actually found my running schedule easier to follow.\r\nOn Wednesday, the presentations to the IOC team did not finish until the early evening, so I just managed to squeeze in a 45-minute run.\r\nAnd because it was a rest day I didn't have to feel bad about missing my training either.",
    "id": "N_71",
    "features": {
        "noun": "duties",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "official",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who was back to official duties last week in my role as an ambassador to London's 2012 Olympic bid.\r\nAll the sporting people on the capital's bid team think I'm mad to be taking part in the London Marathon.\r\nEven though it was a very busy week entertaining the International Olympic Committee's (IOC) Evaluation Commission, I actually found my running schedule easier to follow.\r\nOn Wednesday, the presentations to the IOC team did not finish until the early evening, so I just managed to squeeze in a 45-minute run.\r\nAnd because it was a rest day I didn't have to feel bad about missing my training either.?",
        "answer": "It"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jade Johnson is undecided about whether to contest next month's European Indoor Championships in Madrid despite winning the AAAs long jump title on Saturday.\r\n\"I will have to see how I am jumping in the next competition and I'll have to have a conversation with my coach.\" Johnson, who finished seventh in last year's Olympic Games, has not competed indoors since 2000.",
    "id": "N_72",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jade",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": "how"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jade who is undecided about whether to contest next month's European Indoor Championships in Madrid despite winning the AAAs long jump title on Saturday.\r\n\"I will have to see how I am jumping in the next competition and I'll have to have a conversation with my coach.\" who, who finished seventh in last year's Olympic Games, has not competed indoors since 2000.?",
        "answer": "Johnson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jo Pavey will miss January's View From Great Edinburgh International Cross Country to focus on preparing for the European Indoor Championships in March.",
    "id": "N_73",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jo",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "miss",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jo who will miss January's View From Great Edinburgh International Cross Country to focus on preparing for the European Indoor Championships in March.?",
        "answer": "Pavey"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Britain's Jason Gardener enjoyed a double 60m success in Glasgow in his first competitive outing since he won 100m relay gold at the Athens Olympics.\r\nedged out Russia's Olga Fedorova and Sweden's Jenny Kallur to win the women's 60m race in 7.23secs.\r\nRussia won the meeting with a final total of 63 points, with Britain second on 48 and France one point behind in third.\r\nwon the men's 400m, with Brett Rund fourth for Britain.\r\ntook victory for Sweden in the women's 60m hurdles ahead of Russia's Irina Shevchenko and Britain's Sarah Claxton, who set a new personal best.\r\nA botched changeover in the 4x200m relay cost Britain's men the chance to add further points as France claimed victory.",
    "id": "N_74",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Britain's",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "enjoyed",
        "adjective": "double",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Britain's Jason Gardener enjoyed a double 60m success in Glasgow in his first competitive outing since who won 100m relay gold at twho Atwhons Olympics.\r\nedged out Russia's Olga Fedorova and Sweden's Jenny Kallur to win twho women's 60m race in 7.23secs.\r\nRussia won twho meeting with a final total of 63 points, with Britain second on 48 and France one point behind in third.\r\nwon twho men's 400m, with Brett Rund fourth for Britain.\r\ntook victory for Sweden in twho women's 60m hurdles awhoad of Russia's Irina Swhovcwhonko and Britain's Sarah Claxton, who set a new personal best.\r\nA botcwhod changeover in twho 4x200m relay cost Britain's men twho chance to add furtwhor points as France claimed victory.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World 5000m champion Eliud Kipchoge won the 9.2km race at the View From Great Edinburgh Cross Country.\r\nIn the women's race, Ethiopia's Tirunesh Dibaba won a battle with world cross country champion Benita Johnson to retain her title.",
    "id": "N_75",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "won",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "World 5000m champion Eliud who won the 9.2km race at the View From Great Edinburgh Cross Country.\r\nIn the women's race, Ethiopia's Tirunesh Dibaba won a battle with world cross country champion Benita Johnson to retain her title.?",
        "answer": "Kipchoge"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "European cross-country champion Hayley Yelling completed a hat-trick of wins in the Reebok Cardiff Cross Challenge in Bute Park on Sunday afternoon.",
    "id": "N_76",
    "features": {
        "noun": "cross-country",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "completed",
        "adjective": "European",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": ""
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Butler said of her success: \"I felt great throughout the race and hope this is a good beginning for a marvellous 2005 season for me.\" Elsewhere, Abebe Dinkessa of Ethiopia won the Brussels IAAF cross-country race on Sunday, completing the 10,500m course in 33.22.",
    "id": "N_77",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Butler",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "great",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Butlerwhosaidwhoofwhoherwhosuccess:who\"Iwhofeltwhogreatwhothroughoutwhothewhoracewhoandwhohopewhothiswhoiswhoawhogoodwhobeginningwhoforwhoawhomarvellouswho2005whoseasonwhoforwhome.\"whoElsewhere,whoAbebewhoDinkessawhoofwhoEthiopiawhowonwhothewhoBrusselswhoIAAFwhocross-countrywhoracewhoonwhoSunday,whocompletingwhothewho10,500mwhocoursewhoinwho33.22.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The World Anti-Doping Agency (Wada) will appeal against the acquittal of Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou on doping charges, if the IAAF does not.\r\nKenteris, 31, and Thanou, 30, had been charged with avoiding drugs tests in Tel Aviv, Chicago and Athens and failing to notify anti-doping officials of their whereabouts before the Olympics.",
    "id": "N_78",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "appeal",
        "adjective": "anti-doping",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoWorldwhoAnti-DopingwhoAgencywho(Wada)whowillwhoappealwhoagainstwhothewhoacquittalwhoofwhoKostaswhoKenteriswhoandwhoKaterinawhoThanouwhoonwhodopingwhocharges,whoifwhothewhoIAAFwhodoeswhonot.\r\nKenteris,who31,whoandwhoThanou,who30,whohadwhobeenwhochargedwhowithwhoavoidingwhodrugswhotestswhoinwhoTelwhoAviv,whoChicagowhoandwhoAthenswhoandwhofailingwhotowhonotifywhoanti-dopingwhoofficialswhoofwhotheirwhowhereaboutswhobeforewhothewhoOlympics.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The careers of sprinters Kostas Kenteris and Katerina Thanou are over, says the boss of the organisation that cleared them of missing a drugs test.\r\nSpeaking to the Greek Parliament on Tuesday, Sevastis said that the evidence sent by the International Olympic Committee and athletics governing body the IAAF was not strong enough for the Greek Association to find the sprinters guilty.",
    "id": "N_79",
    "features": {
        "noun": "careers",
        "pronoun": "them",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "over,",
        "adverb": "test."
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Now the IAAF will lodge an appeal with the Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS) and has suspended both athletes.\r\nAn IAAF statement said: \"The Doping Review Board concluded that the decision is erroneous.\" The statement continued: \"Both athletes' cases will be refered to arbitration before the CAS.\r\nKenteris, who won Olympic 200m gold at the 2000 Olympics, and Thanou were suspended by the IAAF last December after failing to take routine drugs tests before the Athens Games.",
    "id": "N_80",
    "features": {
        "noun": "IAAF",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "lodge",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "Now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "NowwhothewhoIAAFwhowillwholodgewhoanwhoappealwhowithwhothewhoCourtwhoofwhoArbitrationwhoforwhoSportwho(CAS)whoandwhohaswhosuspendedwhobothwhoathletes.\r\nAnwhoIAAFwhostatementwhosaid:who\"ThewhoDopingwhoReviewwhoBoardwhoconcludedwhothatwhothewhodecisionwhoiswhoerroneous.\"whoThewhostatementwhocontinued:who\"Bothwhoathletes'whocaseswhowillwhobewhoreferedwhotowhoarbitrationwhobeforewhothewhoCAS.\r\nKenteris,whowhowhowonwhoOlympicwho200mwhogoldwhoatwhothewho2000whoOlympics,whoandwhoThanouwhowerewhosuspendedwhobywhothewhoIAAFwholastwhoDecemberwhoafterwhofailingwhotowhotakewhoroutinewhodrugswhotestswhobeforewhothewhoAthenswhoGames.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The duo had been provisionally suspended by the IAAF for allegedly missing three drugs tests, including one on the eve of the Athens Olympics.\r\nBut the Greek Athletics Federation tribunal has overturned the bans - a decision which the IAAF can now contest at the Court of Arbitration for Sport.\r\nKenteris, 31, and Thanou, 30, had been charged with avoiding drug tests in Tel Aviv, Chicago and Athens and failing to notify anti-doping officials of their whereabouts before the Olympics.\r\n\"This evidence shows Mr Kenteris was never asked to submit to a test by the International Olympic Committee so he could not possibly have been guilty of deliberately avoiding one.",
    "id": "N_81",
    "features": {
        "noun": "duo",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "Greek",
        "adverb": "provisionally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The what had been provisionally suspended by the IAAF for allegedly missing three drugs tests, including one on the eve of the Athens Olympics.\r\nBut the Greek Athletics Federation tribunal has overturned the bans - a decision which the IAAF can now contest at the Court of Arbitration for Sport.\r\nKenteris, 31, and Thanou, 30, had been charged with avoiding drug tests in Tel Aviv, Chicago and Athens and failing to notify anti-doping officials of their whereabouts before the Olympics.\r\n\"This evidence shows Mr Kenteris was never asked to submit to a test by the International Olympic Committee so he could not possibly have been guilty of deliberately avoiding one.?",
        "answer": "duo"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Butler and Yelling finished fourth and fifth as Australian world champion Johnson romped to a five-second victory in the 6km race ahead of Edith Masai.",
    "id": "N_82",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Butler",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "finished",
        "adjective": "fourth",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ButlerwhoandwhoYellingwhofinishedwhofourthwhoandwhofifthwhoaswhoAustralianwhoworldwhochampionwhoJohnsonwhorompedwhotowhoawhofive-secondwhovictorywhoinwhothewho6kmwhoracewhoaheadwhoofwhoEdithwhoMasai.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Holmes will make her first track appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold in January's Norwich Union International in Glasgow.",
    "id": "N_83",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Holmes",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who will make her first track appearance on home soil since winning double Olympic gold in January's Norwich Union International in Glasgow.?",
        "answer": "Holmes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Two-time Olympic 10,000 metres champion Derartu Tulu has confirmed she will take part in the BUPA Great Caledonian Run in Edinburgh on 8 May.",
    "id": "N_84",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Two-time",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Two-time Olympic 10,000 metres champion Derartu Tulu has confirmed who will take part in the BUPA Great Caledonian Run in Edinburgh on 8 May.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Allan Scott is confident of winning a medal at next week's European Indoor Championships after a solid debut on the international circuit.\r\nI got a poor start - but I still felt I should have ran faster.\" Vivancos slashed his personal best to equal the Spanish record with a time of 7.60secs while Kronberg and Dorival clocked 7.62secs and 7.63secs respectively.",
    "id": "N_85",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Allan",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "confident",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Allan who is confident of winning a medal at next week's European Indoor Championships after a solid debut on the international circuit.\r\nI got a poor start - but I still felt I should have ran faster.\" Vivancos slashed his personal best to equal the Spanish record with a time of 7.60secs while Kronberg and Dorival clocked 7.62secs and 7.63secs respectively.?",
        "answer": "Scott"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Yelling clinched the women's European cross country title last month and Pavey followed up with bronze.",
    "id": "N_86",
    "features": {
        "noun": "cross",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "Yelling",
        "adjective": "women's",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Marion Jones has filed a lawsuit for defamation against Balco boss Victor Conte following his allegations that he gave her performance-enhancing drugs.\r\nHer lawsuit, filed in the US District Court in San Francisco, said the sprinter had passed a lie detector test and that she \"has never taken banned performance-enhancing drugs\".\r\n\"Mr Conte chose to make unsubstantiated allegations on television, while Marion Jones demanded to take and then passed a lie detector examination.\r\nWe challenge him to submit to the same lie detector procedure that Marion Jones passed.\" The sport's ruling body, the IAAF, is taking a cautious approach to Conte's allegations but contacted the US Anti-Doping Agency.",
    "id": "N_87",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Marion",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "performance-enhancing",
        "adverb": "never"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Marion Jones has filed a lawsuit for defamation against Balco boss Victor Conte following his allegations that who gave whor performance-enhancing drugs.\r\nHer lawsuit, filed in twho US District Court in San Francisco, said twho sprinter had passed a lie detector test and that swho \"has never taken banned performance-enhancing drugs\".\r\n\"Mr Conte chose to make unsubstantiated allegations on television, while Marion Jones demanded to take and twhon passed a lie detector examination.\r\nWe challenge him to submit to twho same lie detector procedure that Marion Jones passed.\" Twho sport's ruling body, twho IAAF, is taking a cautious approach to Conte's allegations but contacted twho US Anti-Doping Agency.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Thanou, 30, was provisionally suspended for missing a test before the Olympics, but the decision was overturned.\r\n\"If given the green light I will run again - that's the only thing I want.\" Thanou, 30, and her compatriot Kostas Kenteris were provisionally suspended by the IAAF in December for missing three drugs tests.\r\nThe IAAF - which said it was \"very surprised\" by the decision of the Greek tribunal - is deciding whether to appeal against the decision at the Court of Arbitration for Sport.",
    "id": "N_88",
    "features": {
        "noun": "test",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "overturned.",
        "adverb": "provisionally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Thanou,who30,whowaswhoprovisionallywhosuspendedwhoforwhomissingwhoawhotestwhobeforewhothewhoOlympics,whobutwhothewhodecisionwhowaswhooverturned.\r\n\"IfwhogivenwhothewhogreenwholightwhoIwhowillwhorunwhoagainwho-whothat'swhothewhoonlywhothingwhoIwhowant.\"whoThanou,who30,whoandwhoherwhocompatriotwhoKostaswhoKenteriswhowerewhoprovisionallywhosuspendedwhobywhothewhoIAAFwhoinwhoDecemberwhoforwhomissingwhothreewhodrugswhotests.\r\nThewhoIAAFwho-whowhichwhosaidwhoitwhowaswho\"verywhosurprised\"whobywhothewhodecisionwhoofwhothewhoGreekwhotribunalwho-whoiswhodecidingwhowhetherwhotowhoappealwhoagainstwhothewhodecisionwhoatwhothewhoCourtwhoofwhoArbitrationwhoforwhoSport.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jason Gardener says being made an MBE in the New Year Honours List underlines the achievement of Great Britain's 4x100m relay squad at the Olympics.\r\nGardener, Darren Campbell, Marlon Devonish and Mark Lewis-Francis have all been awarded MBEs after beating pre-race favourites USA to gold.\r\n\"This recognition is really inspiring and makes me want to have more success,\" said Lewis-Francis.",
    "id": "N_89",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jason",
        "pronoun": "me",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "\"This",
        "adverb": "really"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jason who says being made an MBE in the New Year Honours List underlines the achievement of Great Britain's 4x100m relay squad at the Olympics.\r\nwho, Darren Campbell, Marlon Devonish and Mark Lewis-Francis have all been awarded MBEs after beating pre-race favourites USA to gold.\r\n\"This recognition is really inspiring and makes me want to have more success,\" said Lewis-Francis.?",
        "answer": "Gardener"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The trial date for the Bay Area Laboratory Cooperative (Balco) steroid distribution case has been postponed.\r\nThe hearing in June will focus on the admissibility of evidence gathered during police raids on Balco's offices and Anderson's home.",
    "id": "N_90",
    "features": {
        "noun": "trial",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "steroid",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The trial date for the Bay Area Laboratory Cooperative (Balco) steroid distribution what has been postponed.\r\nThe hearing in June will focus on the admissibility of evidence gathered during police raids on Balco's offices and Anderson's home.?",
        "answer": "case"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Collins calls for Chambers return\r\nWorld 100m champion Kim Collins says suspended sprinter Dwain Chambers should be allowed to compete in the Olympics again.",
    "id": "N_91",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Collins",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "calls",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Collins calls for who return\r\nWorld 100m champion Kim Collins says suspended sprinter Dwain who should be allowed to compete in the Olympics again.?",
        "answer": "Chambers"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He says so himself in a matter-of-fact way as he recalls the car accident which occurred nine days before he was scheduled to step out into the Olympic Stadium in Athens for the 50K Walk.\r\n\"In my back, it felt as though all the muscles had been ripped off my pelvis but I was thinking maybe we could do something with laser therapy and ultra sound and hopefully I'd be able to race.\" It took over 10 hours before Jamie knew with certainty that he would not be competing in his second Olympics.\r\n\"I'd fractured my big toe as well which was on the brake.\" Jamie didn't finally arrive at hospital in Athens until some nine and a half hours after the accident.\r\nThe people at the Mater have been absolutely fantastic.\" Jamie had to wear a body cast for three and a half months after the accident and spent most of that time flat on his back.\r\nA two and a half inch needle went in yesterday and I'm fairly incapacitated today as a result.\" Jamie has also travelled to receive treatment at the Polish training centre in Spala where he has trained with triple Olympic champion Robert Korzeniowski over the past five years.\r\nJamie heads to Poland again on Sunday where he will be having daily cryotherapy in addition to twice-daily physio sessions and pool-work.\r\nAll these sessions are small steps on the way to what Jamie hopes will be a return to racing in 2006.",
    "id": "N_92",
    "features": {
        "noun": "way",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "matter-of-fact",
        "adverb": "so"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "He says so himself in a matter-of-fact way as who recalls twho car accident which occurred nine days before who was scwhoduled to step out into twho Olympic Stadium in Atwhons for twho 50K Walk.\r\n\"In my back, it felt as though all twho muscles had been ripped off my pelvis but I was thinking maybe we could do something with laser twhorapy and ultra sound and hopefully I'd be able to race.\" It took over 10 hours before Jamie knew with certainty that who would not be competing in his second Olympics.\r\n\"I'd fractured my big toe as well which was on twho brake.\" Jamie didn't finally arrive at hospital in Atwhons until some nine and a half hours after twho accident.\r\nTwho people at twho Mater have been absolutely fantastic.\" Jamie had to wear a body cast for three and a half months after twho accident and spent most of that time flat on his back.\r\nA two and a half inch needle went in yesterday and I'm fairly incapacitated today as a result.\" Jamie has also travelled to receive treatment at twho Polish training centre in Spala wwhore who has trained with triple Olympic champion Robert Korzeniowski over twho past five years.\r\nJamie whoads to Poland again on Sunday wwhore who will be having daily cryotwhorapy in addition to twice-daily physio sessions and pool-work.\r\nAll twhose sessions are small steps on twho way to what Jamie hopes will be a return to racing in 2006.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Training in Wales and getting advice from Linford Christie is broadening my mind,\" said Lewis-Francis.\r\n\"I am still keeping up my weights work and I can see the improvement in my running.\" Despite playing his part in Britain's successful 4x100m relay team, Lewis-Francis still feels the frustration of missing out on the individual 100m final at the 2004 Olympics.",
    "id": "N_93",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "\"Training",
        "adjective": "successful",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"TrainingwhatinwhatWaleswhatandwhatgettingwhatadvicewhatfromwhatLinfordwhatChristiewhatiswhatbroadeningwhatmywhatmind,\"whatsaidwhatLewis-Francis.\r\n\"IwhatamwhatstillwhatkeepingwhatupwhatmywhatweightswhatworkwhatandwhatIwhatcanwhatseewhatthewhatimprovementwhatinwhatmywhatrunning.\"whatDespitewhatplayingwhathiswhatpartwhatinwhatBritain'swhatsuccessfulwhat4x100mwhatrelaywhatteam,whatLewis-Franciswhatstillwhatfeelswhatthewhatfrustrationwhatofwhatmissingwhatoutwhatonwhatthewhatindividualwhat100mwhatfinalwhatatwhatthewhat2004whatOlympics.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wayne Rooney made a winning return to Everton as Manchester United cruised into the FA Cup quarter-finals.\r\nFortune headed home after 23 minutes before Ronaldo scored when Nigel Martyn parried Paul Scholes' free-kick.\r\nFortune gave United the lead after 23 minutes, rising to meet Ronaldo's cross from eight yards after the Portuguese youngster had been allowed too much time and space by the hapless Gary Naysmith.\r\nUnited almost doubled their lead after 48 minutes when Ronaldo's low drive from 25 yards took a deflection off Tony Hibbert, but Martyn dived to save brilliantly.\r\nManchester United: Carroll, Gary Neville, Brown, Ferdinand, Heinze, Ronaldo, Phil Neville, Keane, Scholes, Fortune, Rooney.",
    "id": "N_94",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wayne",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "made",
        "adjective": "quarter-finals.",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wayne Rooney made a winning return to Everton as Manchester who cruised into the FA Cup quarter-finals.\r\nFortune headed home after 23 minutes before Ronaldo scored when Nigel Martyn parried Paul Scholes' free-kick.\r\nFortune gave who the lead after 23 minutes, rising to meet Ronaldo's cross from eight yards after the Portuguese youngster had been allowed too much time and space by the hapless Gary Naysmith.\r\nwho almost doubled their lead after 48 minutes when Ronaldo's low drive from 25 yards took a deflection off Tony Hibbert, but Martyn dived to save brilliantly.\r\nManchester who: Carroll, Gary Neville, Brown, Ferdinand, Heinze, Ronaldo, Phil Neville, Keane, Scholes, Fortune, Rooney.?",
        "answer": "United"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manchester United striker Ruud van Nistelrooy may make his comeback after an Achilles tendon injury in the FA Cup fifth round tie at Everton on Saturday.\r\n\"The training he has been doing in Holland has been perfect and I am very satisfied with it.\" Even without Van Nistelrooy, United made it 13 wins in 15 league games with a 2-0 derby victory at Manchester City on Sunday.",
    "id": "N_95",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manchester",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "tendon",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Manchester United striker Ruud van who may make his comeback after an Achilles tendon injury in the FA Cup fifth round tie at Everton on Saturday.\r\n\"The training he has been doing in Holland has been perfect and I am very satisfied with it.\" Even without Van who, United made it 13 wins in 15 league games with a 2-0 derby victory at Manchester City on Sunday.?",
        "answer": "Nistelrooy"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Everton manager David Moyes will discipline striker James Beattie after all for his headbutt on Chelsea defender William Gallas.\r\nHe said: \"I believe that I should set the record straight by conceding that the dismissal was right and correct.\" Moyes added: \"My comments on Saturday came immediately after the final whistle and at a point when I had only had the opportunity to see one, very quick re-run of the incident.\"\r\nHowever, I must say that I do still believe the Chelsea player in question did go down too easily.\" Speaking immediately after the game, Moyes said: \"I don't think it was a sending-off, I have been a centre-half in my time and I would have been ashamed to have gone down as easily as that.",
    "id": "N_96",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Everton",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "discipline",
        "adjective": "right",
        "adverb": "immediately"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Everton manager David who will discipline striker James Beattie after all for his headbutt on Chelsea defender William Gallas.\r\nHe said: \"I believe that I should set the record straight by conceding that the dismissal was right and correct.\" who added: \"My comments on Saturday came immediately after the final whistle and at a point when I had only had the opportunity to see one, very quick re-run of the incident.\"\r\nHowever, I must say that I do still believe the Chelsea player in question did go down too easily.\" Speaking immediately after the game, who said: \"I don't think it was a sending-off, I have been a centre-half in my time and I would have been ashamed to have gone down as easily as that.?",
        "answer": "Moyes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manchester United winger Cristiano Ronaldo said he is close to agreeing to a new contract at Old Trafford.\r\nI think we'll reach a good agreement for both sides.\" Ronaldo refused to commit his long-term future to the club.",
    "id": "N_97",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manchester",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "close",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Mancwhoster United winger Cristiano Ronaldo said who is close to agreeing to a new contract at Old Trafford.\r\nI think we'll reach a good agreement for both sides.\" Ronaldo refused to commit his long-term future to twho club.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Scotland manager Walter Smith has given his backing to the reinstatement of the Home International series.\r\nBut Smith said: \"Bringing it back would add meaning to friendly games and that's something that's needed.\" The Home International series was done away with in 1984, with the traditional Scotland-England fixture continuing until 1989.",
    "id": "N_98",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Scotland",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "friendly",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Scotland manager Walter who has given his backing to the reinstatement of the Home International series.\r\nBut who said: \"Bringing it back would add meaning to friendly games and that's something that's needed.\" The Home International series was done away with in 1984, with the traditional Scotland-England fixture continuing until 1989.?",
        "answer": "Smith"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mido said: \"There isn't much I have to say today, all there is to say is that I came specially from England to Egypt to rejoin the national team and to apologise for all my mistakes.\" Mido was axed by former coach Marco Tardelli after failing to answer a national call-up, claiming he had a groin injury.\r\n\"Mido's apology today does not negatively affect Mido in anyway, on the contrary it makes him a bigger star and a role model for all football players,\" Shalaby said.\r\nShalaby earlier said that after an apology Mido would be available for the national side if coach Hassan Shehata chose him.",
    "id": "N_99",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mido",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "much",
        "adverb": "\"There"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Mido said: \"There isn't much I have to say today, all there is to say is that I came specially from England to which location to rejoin the national team and to apologise for all my mistakes.\" Mido was axed by former coach Marco Tardelli after failing to answer a national call-up, claiming he had a groin injury.\r\n\"Mido's apology today does not negatively affect Mido in anyway, on the contrary it makes him a bigger star and a role model for all football players,\" Shalaby said.\r\nShalaby earlier said that after an apology Mido would be available for the national side if coach Hassan Shehata chose him.?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wayne Rooney met Gary Neville's cross to the near post with a low shot, which went in via a deflection off Richard Dunne, to put United ahead.\r\nSteve McManaman wasted City's best chance when he shot wide from three yards in the first half.\r\nAnd when Neville delivered a cross in a carbon copy of City's best first-half chance, Rooney showed McManaman how to do it - even if he needed the help of Dunne's leg.\r\nOn 75 minutes, he scored a horrible own goal when attempting to volley clear Rooney's cross and United seemed home and dry.\r\n\"But we still had four good chances, two after we'd gone 2-0 down, the one McManaman missed was very similar to the one Wayne Rooney scored from.\" \r\n\"Derby games can be like that, they can be scrappy, dull, horrible and it was maybe like that.\" Man City: James, Mills (Bradley Wright-Phillips 83), Dunne, Distin, Thatcher, Shaun Wright-Phillips, Barton (Macken 68), Sibierski, McManaman, Musampa, Fowler.\r\nMan Utd: Carroll, Gary Neville, Ferdinand, Brown, Heinze, O'Shea (Ronaldo 33), Keane, Fortune, Fletcher (Giggs 64), Rooney, Scholes (Phil Neville 84).",
    "id": "N_100",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wayne",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "met",
        "adjective": "near",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "which"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Reds are currently fifth in the Premiership table, five points off the crucial fourth spot, which brings Champions League qualification - and they face Chelsea in Sunday's Carling Cup final.\r\n\"We're fighting for the fourth spot for the Champions League for next season but we are still involved in two cup competitions, which are very important.",
    "id": "N_101",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Reds",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "crucial",
        "adverb": "currently"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "His injury is very painful, so he is out.\" But Mourinho has revealed defender Willian Gallas and striker Didier Drogba will be in the starting line-up.\r\nMourinho said: \"We have one more session but I think Drogba will play, and Gallas will play.",
    "id": "N_102",
    "features": {
        "noun": "injury",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "out.\"",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "His injury is very painful, so who is out.\" But Mourinho has revealed defender Willian Gallas and striker Didier Drogba will be in twho starting line-up.\r\nMourinho said: \"We have one more session but I think Drogba will play, and Gallas will play.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "John Arne Riise volleyed Liverpool ahead after 45 seconds but Steven Gerrard scored a 79th-minute own goal.\r\nThat prompted Mourinho's reaction which saw him sent off, but Chelsea still pressed and Duff had a chance to win the game with seven minutes remaining.\r\nDrogba almost headed Chelsea in front two minutes into extra-time but the striker saw the ball rebound off the post.\r\nThere was still drama as Nunez beat Cech to a high ball with six minutes remaining to head his side level, but despite Liverpool's desperate attacks, Chelsea clung on to win.\r\nDudek, Finnan, Carragher, Hyypia, Traore (Biscan 67), Luis Garcia, Gerrard, Hamann, Riise, Kewell (Nunez 56), Morientes (Baros 74).\r\nCech, Paulo Ferreira, Ricardo Carvalho, Terry, Gallas (Kezman 74), Jarosik (Gudjohnsen 45), Lampard, Makelele, Cole (Johnson 81), Drogba, Duff.",
    "id": "N_103",
    "features": {
        "noun": "John",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "volleyed",
        "adjective": "79th-minute",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "JohnwhoArnewhoRiisewhovolleyedwhoLiverpoolwhoaheadwhoafterwho45whosecondswhobutwhoStevenwhoGerrardwhoscoredwhoawho79th-minutewhoownwhogoal.\r\nThatwhopromptedwhoMourinho'swhoreactionwhowhichwhosawwhohimwhosentwhooff,whobutwhoChelseawhostillwhopressedwhoandwhoDuffwhohadwhoawhochancewhotowhowinwhothewhogamewhowithwhosevenwhominuteswhoremaining.\r\nDrogbawhoalmostwhoheadedwhoChelseawhoinwhofrontwhotwowhominuteswhointowhoextra-timewhobutwhothewhostrikerwhosawwhothewhoballwhoreboundwhooffwhothewhopost.\r\nTherewhowaswhostillwhodramawhoaswhoNunezwhobeatwhoCechwhotowhoawhohighwhoballwhowithwhosixwhominuteswhoremainingwhotowhoheadwhohiswhosidewholevel,whobutwhodespitewhoLiverpool'swhodesperatewhoattacks,whoChelseawhoclungwhoonwhotowhowin.\r\nDudek,whoFinnan,whoCarragher,whoHyypia,whoTraorewho(Biscanwho67),whoLuiswhoGarcia,whoGerrard,whoHamann,whoRiise,whoKewellwho(Nunezwho56),whoMorienteswho(Baroswho74).\r\nCech,whoPaulowhoFerreira,whoRicardowhoCarvalho,whoTerry,whoGallaswho(Kezmanwho74),whoJarosikwho(Gudjohnsenwho45),whoLampard,whoMakelele,whoColewho(Johnsonwho81),whoDrogba,whoDuff.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kieron Dyer smashed home the winner to end Bolton's 10-game unbeaten run.\r\nLee Bowyer put Newcastle ahead when he fed Stephen Carr on the right flank, then sprinted into the area to power home a header from the resultant cross.\r\nBolton keeper Jussi Jaaskelainen had to make two saves in quick succession midway through the first-half - keeping out Shearer's low shot and Dyer's close-range header - but that was the only goalmouth action of note.\r\nThe Magpies were opened up again before half-time as Davies set Giannakopoulos in space and Given had to block at his near post.\r\n\"I thought it would lift us and that they might be tired after playing a lot of games, but unfortunately we were not up for the battle in the second half.\r\nThe scoreline flattered them and we could have had one or two more goals.\" Newcastle: Given, Carr, Boumsong, Bramble, Babayaro, Dyer, Faye, Bowyer, Robert (Jenas 77), Ameobi, Shearer.\r\nBolton: Jaaskelainen, Hunt (Fadiga 14), N'Gotty, Ben Haim, Candela, Giannakopoulos, Okocha (Vaz Te 77), Hierro (Campo 64), Speed, Gardner, Davies.",
    "id": "N_104",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kieron",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "smashed",
        "adjective": "10-game",
        "adverb": "home"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kieron who smashed home the winner to end Bolton's 10-game unbeaten run.\r\nLee Bowyer put Newcastle ahead when he fed Stephen Carr on the right flank, then sprinted into the area to power home a header from the resultant cross.\r\nBolton keeper Jussi Jaaskelainen had to make two saves in quick succession midway through the first-half - keeping out Shearer's low shot and who's close-range header - but that was the only goalmouth action of note.\r\nThe Magpies were opened up again before half-time as Davies set Giannakopoulos in space and Given had to block at his near post.\r\n\"I thought it would lift us and that they might be tired after playing a lot of games, but unfortunately we were not up for the battle in the second half.\r\nThe scoreline flattered them and we could have had one or two more goals.\" Newcastle: Given, Carr, Boumsong, Bramble, Babayaro, who, Faye, Bowyer, Robert (Jenas 77), Ameobi, Shearer.\r\nBolton: Jaaskelainen, Hunt (Fadiga 14), N'Gotty, Ben Haim, Candela, Giannakopoulos, Okocha (Vaz Te 77), Hierro (Campo 64), Speed, Gardner, Davies.?",
        "answer": "Dyer"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But Middlesbrough peppered the Charlton goal after the break and Chris Riggott stroked home the equaliser.\r\nShaun Bartlett's strike put Charlton back in front but that lead lasted just six minutes before Graham rushed onto Queudrue's pass to head home.\r\nCharlton's early pressure paid off when Bartlett received a long ball from Talal El Karkouri in the box and laid it off to Holland who buried his right-footed strike.\r\nBoro had plenty of time on the ball but the Addicks comfortably mopped up the pressure - with Kiely tipping a Hasselbaink header over the bar - to take their lead into half-time.\r\nIt was all one-way traffic after the break at the Riverside as Middlesbrough poured forward and Kiely even saved Hreidarsson's blushes when he palmed the ball away to prevent a Charlton own goal.\r\nKiely, Hreidarsson, Perry, El Karkouri, Young, Konchesky, Murphy (Euell 78), Holland, Kishishev, Thomas (Johansson 72), Bartlett.",
    "id": "N_105",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Middlesbrough",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "peppered",
        "adjective": "lead",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Richie Byrne's header gave Aberdeen a way back into the game, but Stevie Crawford restored United's lead from 18 yards before half time.\r\nUnited doubled their lead after 29 minutes when Grady tapped the ball into an empty net after Robson had headed Mark Wilson's cross off the angle of post and bar.\r\nUnited restored their two-goal lead four minutes before the end of a highly entertaining first half.\r\nBullock, Duff, Wilson, Ritchie, Archibald, Scotland (Samuel 63), Brebner, Kerr (Cameron 87), Robson, Crawford, Grady.\r\nEsson, Hart, Anderson, Diamond, Byrne (Morrison 75), McNaughton, Heikkinen (Foster 27), Winter, Clark (Stewart 51), Mackie, Whelan.",
    "id": "N_106",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Richie",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "gave",
        "adjective": "half",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "RichiewhatByrne'swhatheaderwhatgavewhatAberdeenwhatawhatwaywhatbackwhatintowhatthewhatgame,whatbutwhatSteviewhatCrawfordwhatrestoredwhatUnited'swhatleadwhatfromwhat18whatyardswhatbeforewhathalfwhattime.\r\nUnitedwhatdoubledwhattheirwhatleadwhatafterwhat29whatminuteswhatwhenwhatGradywhattappedwhatthewhatballwhatintowhatanwhatemptywhatnetwhatafterwhatRobsonwhathadwhatheadedwhatMarkwhatWilson'swhatcrosswhatoffwhatthewhatanglewhatofwhatpostwhatandwhatbar.\r\nUnitedwhatrestoredwhattheirwhattwo-goalwhatleadwhatfourwhatminuteswhatbeforewhatthewhatendwhatofwhatawhathighlywhatentertainingwhatfirstwhathalf.\r\nBullock,whatDuff,whatWilson,whatRitchie,whatArchibald,whatScotlandwhat(Samuelwhat63),whatBrebner,whatKerrwhat(Cameronwhat87),whatRobson,whatCrawford,whatGrady.\r\nEsson,whatHart,whatAnderson,whatDiamond,whatByrnewhat(Morrisonwhat75),whatMcNaughton,whatHeikkinenwhat(Fosterwhat27),whatWinter,whatClarkwhat(Stewartwhat51),whatMackie,whatWhelan.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The home side's Craig Bryson had a goal chopped off before Stan Varga headed Celtic into the lead.\r\nClyde had the ball in the net after half-an-hour through a tremendous strike from Bryson, but the referee had already blown for a foul by Petrov.\r\nVarga got his second goal of the game as Celtic drove home their advantage - Thompson whipped in a corner from the right and the unmarked defender simply tapped the ball over the line from a couple of yards out.\r\nCeltic were utterly dominant by this stage and Bellamy opened his scoring account for the club after a fine move involving Aiden McGeady, Jackie McNamara and Maloney culminated in the Welshman hammering the ball into the net.\r\nDouglas, Henchoz, McNamara, Balde, Varga, Juninho Paulista, Thompson, Lennon (Lambert 70), Sutton (Maloney 45), Petrov (McGeady 70), Bellamy.",
    "id": "N_107",
    "features": {
        "noun": "home",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "net",
        "adverb": "already"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The home side's Craig Bryson had a goal chopped off before Stan who headed Celtic into the lead.\r\nClyde had the ball in the net after half-an-hour through a tremendous strike from Bryson, but the referee had already blown for a foul by Petrov.\r\nwho got his second goal of the game as Celtic drove home their advantage - Thompson whipped in a corner from the right and the unmarked defender simply tapped the ball over the line from a couple of yards out.\r\nCeltic were utterly dominant by this stage and Bellamy opened his scoring account for the club after a fine move involving Aiden McGeady, Jackie McNamara and Maloney culminated in the Welshman hammering the ball into the net.\r\nDouglas, Henchoz, McNamara, Balde, who, Juninho Paulista, Thompson, Lennon (Lambert 70), Sutton (Maloney 45), Petrov (McGeady 70), Bellamy.?",
        "answer": "Varga"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Lee Miller scored inside the opening 60 seconds, heading over Colin Meldrum and into the net from a Jamie McAllister free kick.\r\nMikoliunas sprinted down the right, crossed to the back post where McAllister raced in to head past Meldrum.\r\nThe impressive Mikoliunas twice went close before half time - a low drive was comfortably gathered by Meldrum and then he curled a left-footed shot past the keeper's right-hand post.\r\nThe Livi striker ignored the pass, however, and Dair ran on to it and played Easton in at the back post and he headed home from close range.\r\nMeldrum, McNamee, Bahoken (Stanic 45), Deloumeaux, Strong, Dair, Easton, Mark Wilson (Vincze 45), Lilley (Horvath 45), O'Brien, McPake.",
    "id": "N_108",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Lee",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "scored",
        "adjective": "net",
        "adverb": "where"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "LeewhoMillerwhoscoredwhoinsidewhothewhoopeningwho60whoseconds,whoheadingwhooverwhoColinwhoMeldrumwhoandwhointowhothewhonetwhofromwhoawhoJamiewhoMcAllisterwhofreewhokick.\r\nMikoliunaswhosprintedwhodownwhothewhoright,whocrossedwhotowhothewhobackwhopostwhowherewhoMcAllisterwhoracedwhoinwhotowhoheadwhopastwhoMeldrum.\r\nThewhoimpressivewhoMikoliunaswhotwicewhowentwhoclosewhobeforewhohalfwhotimewho-whoawholowwhodrivewhowaswhocomfortablywhogatheredwhobywhoMeldrumwhoandwhothenwhohewhocurledwhoawholeft-footedwhoshotwhopastwhothewhokeeper'swhoright-handwhopost.\r\nThewhoLiviwhostrikerwhoignoredwhothewhopass,whohowever,whoandwhoDairwhoranwhoonwhotowhoitwhoandwhoplayedwhoEastonwhoinwhoatwhothewhobackwhopostwhoandwhohewhoheadedwhohomewhofromwhoclosewhorange.\r\nMeldrum,whoMcNamee,whoBahokenwho(Stanicwho45),whoDeloumeaux,whoStrong,whoDair,whoEaston,whoMarkwhoWilsonwho(Vinczewho45),whoLilleywho(Horvathwho45),whoO'Brien,whoMcPake.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"There's no plans at the moment around the Barcelona game.\" His comments contradict those of chiropractor Jean Pierre Meersseman who treated the Dutchman after he fractured his foot at the start of February.\r\n\"I put everything right with Arjen's foot the last time I saw him 12 days ago.",
    "id": "N_109",
    "features": {
        "noun": "plans",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "\"There's",
        "adjective": "chiropractor",
        "adverb": "ago."
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "plans"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Chelsea left-back Wayne Bridge could miss the rest of the season with a suspected broken ankle.\r\n\"We think it's a big injury,\" said Jose Mourinho, whose Chelsea team this week meet Barcelona in the Champions League and Liverpool in the Carling Cup final.\r\nCudicini would not have played against Barcelona, but had been promised a game in the Carling Cup final, although he will now miss the Cardiff showpiece through suspension.\r\n\"He (Bridge) has no chance of playing against Barcelona, probably will not play against Liverpool (in the Carling Cup final) and maybe not for the rest of the season,\" he said.",
    "id": "N_110",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Chelsea",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "miss",
        "adjective": "left-back",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Chelsea left-back Wayne who could miss the rest of the season with a suspected broken ankle.\r\n\"We think it's a big injury,\" said Jose Mourinho, whose Chelsea team this week meet Barcelona in the Champions League and Liverpool in the Carling Cup final.\r\nCudicini would not have played against Barcelona, but had been promised a game in the Carling Cup final, although he will now miss the Cardiff showpiece through suspension.\r\n\"He (who) has no chance of playing against Barcelona, probably will not play against Liverpool (in the Carling Cup final) and maybe not for the rest of the season,\" he said.?",
        "answer": "Bridge"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But Parry, speaking exclusively to BBC Sport, also admits Gerrard, who has been constantly linked with Chelsea, will have the final say on his future.\r\nBut we are also realistic enough to know we can't keep Steven against his will.\" On the subject of Liverpool's finances, Parry also revealed the club is ready to explore the possibility of a sponsorship deal for its proposed new stadium.\r\nAnd responding to criticism from BBC Sport pundit and former Liverpool stalwart Alan Hansen, he insisted talks on new investment are ongoing, but added the door has not closed on shareholder and lifelong fan Steve Morgan.\r\nThere have been several highs and lows during his time in charge at Anfield - and he had a busy summer, overseeing the arrival of new manager Rafael Benitez and managing to hold on to Steven Gerrard.\r\nHe said: \"They were looking for ways of saying they got more out of the deal for Fernando Morientes, but the response to Real Madrid was the same - Steven is not for sale.\" But when asked if Gerrard would be a Liverpool player on the first day of next season, Parry said: \"I sincerely hope he will be.\r\n\"I think Steven would dearly love to win things with Liverpool more than he'd like to do anything else.\r\nThere are a lot of other players who feel the same, so we all have a common aim.\" It is expected Chelsea will test Liverpool with a \u00c2\u00a330m-plus bid in the summer - but Parry claims he will be in no mood to listen.\r\nAnd he confessed Arsenal's \u00c2\u00a3100m deal with Emirates to sponsor their new ground - complete with naming rights - has given the Anfield club serious food for thought.\r\n\"But the Arsenal deal is the sort of deal that causes you to draw breath and say 'wow - that's interesting.' \"My personal point of view is that I would find it a hell of a lot more palatable than a shared stadium.\" Some Liverpool fans would find such a move highly controversial, but Parry countered: \"I recognise it would be an emotive issue for many supporters, but you look at the amount of money available and it could go into the team.\r\nOn the subject of possible new investment, Parry revealed Liverpool are still in negotiations with a mystery investor, with rumours of interest from the Middle East.\r\nHe also accused Liverpool of using him as \"a stalking horse\" to attract other bids, but Parry explained: \"Steve has never been used as a stalking horse.\r\nThrough a cleverly worded statement, the club has effectively forced Gerrard to publicly make the decision for himself, which I think is the right thing to do.\r\nCritical time for Liverpool with regards to Gerrard.\r\nParry's statements are clever in that any future Gerrard transfer cannot be construed as a lack of ambition by the club to not try and keep their best players.",
    "id": "N_111",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Parry,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "speaking",
        "adjective": "final",
        "adverb": "exclusively"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"But I'm not going to start Wright-Phillips on the left.\" Eriksson also revealed that Wes Brown will start alongside Jamie Carragher in the injury-hit centre of defence.\r\nHe has been playing well all season and I look forward to seeing him.\" And he added that Andy Johnson and Stewart Downing - the other two new players in the squad - would also get a chance to impress.\r\n\"Wright-Phillips, Downing and Johnson will start or get the chance to play some part.",
    "id": "N_112",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"But",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "going",
        "adjective": "injury-hit",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Robben sidelined with broken foot\r\nChelsea winger Arjen Robben has broken two metatarsal bones in his foot and will be out for at least six weeks.\r\nAnd he added: \"It felt different then last summer when I had the same injury on my other foot.",
    "id": "N_113",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Robben",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "sidelined",
        "adjective": "broken",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Robbenwhosidelinedwhowithwhobrokenwhofoot\r\nChelseawhowingerwhoArjenwhoRobbenwhohaswhobrokenwhotwowhometatarsalwhoboneswhoinwhohiswhofootwhoandwhowillwhobewhooutwhoforwhoatwholeastwhosixwhoweeks.\r\nAndwhohewhoadded:who\"ItwhofeltwhodifferentwhothenwholastwhosummerwhowhenwhoIwhohadwhothewhosamewhoinjurywhoonwhomywhootherwhofoot.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"With the games he's played for United, proportionately it doesn't seem that many for Wales,\" Toshack said.\r\n\"But he's one of the greatest of all Welsh internationals and on his 50th cap it's appropriate he's captain.\" Giggs admits he had briefly considered retirement from the international game, but is now targetting playing for Wales in the 2008 European Championships.\r\nGiggs admits he was wavering and considering joining the likes of former Wales skipper Gary Speed and United team-mate Paul Scholes in committing the remaining years of his career to club football.\r\n\"For this particular game I think it is appropriate that Ryan Giggs will be captain, it's his 50th cap and he's known for some time about that,\" Toshack said.\r\nOn Wednesday night Toshack takes charge of his first match since replacing Hughes, and Giggs said: \"It's my 50th cap and I am looking forward to it, and I hope to play a lot more times from here on in.",
    "id": "N_114",
    "features": {
        "noun": "games",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "he's",
        "adjective": "many",
        "adverb": "proportionately"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"With the games he's played for United, proportionately it doesn't seem that many for Wales,\" who said.\r\n\"But he's one of the greatest of all Welsh internationals and on his 50th cap it's appropriate he's captain.\" Giggs admits he had briefly considered retirement from the international game, but is now targetting playing for Wales in the 2008 European Championships.\r\nGiggs admits he was wavering and considering joining the likes of former Wales skipper Gary Speed and United team-mate Paul Scholes in committing the remaining years of his career to club football.\r\n\"For this particular game I think it is appropriate that Ryan Giggs will be captain, it's his 50th cap and he's known for some time about that,\" who said.\r\nOn Wednesday night who takes charge of his first match since replacing Hughes, and Giggs said: \"It's my 50th cap and I am looking forward to it, and I hope to play a lot more times from here on in.?",
        "answer": "Toshack"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manchester City's Paul Bosvelt will find out \"within a month\" whether he is to be offered a new one-year deal.\r\nHe is an unsung hero,\" said Keegan.",
    "id": "N_115",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manchester",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "find",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Mancwhoster City's Paul Bosvelt will find out \"within a month\" wwhotwhor who is to be offered a new one-year deal.\r\nHe is an unsung whoro,\" said Keegan.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Rangers are set to loan out-of-favour midfielder Dragan Mladenovic to Real Sociedad, despite the closure of the January transfer window.\r\nSociedad have been given special permission by the Spanish FA to sign a player due to an injury crisis.",
    "id": "N_116",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Rangers",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "out-of-favour",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "Rangers"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Parry has to deliver a new 60,000-seat stadium in Stanley Park by 2007 amid claims of costs spiralling above \u00c2\u00a3120m.\r\nThrow in the small matter of warding off every top club in world football as they eye captain Steven Gerrard, and you can see Parry is a man with a lot on his plate.\r\nThis will not come as news to Parry, a lifelong Liverpool supporter, but his quiet determination suggests he is no mood to be found wanting...\r\nCaptain Gerrard is central to Liverpool's plans and Parry's insistence that all offers will be refused is a firm statement of intent.\r\nMorgan had a succession of bids rejected, having come close in the summer only for talks to break down over potential costs for the new stadium.\r\nParry meanwhile sees the new ground as crucial to Liverpool's future, but is refusing to become emotionally attached to the idea.\r\nHe is determined the ground will only be built on an affordable basis and will not make future Liverpool management hostages to the new stadium.\r\nLiverpool have publicly refused to entertain the idea of stadium sponsorship and potential naming rights - but the realism of Arsenal's stunning \u00c2\u00a3100m deal for their new Emirates Stadium at Ashburton has changed the landscape.\r\nThrough a cleverly worded statement, the club has effectively forced Gerrard to publicly make the decision for himself, which I think is the right thing to do.\r\nParry's statements are clever in that any future Gerrard transfer cannot be construed as a lack of ambition by the club to not try and keep their best players.",
    "id": "N_117",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Parry",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who has to deliver a new 60,000-seat stadium in Stanley Park by 2007 amid claims of costs spiralling above \u00c2\u00a3120m.\r\nThrow in the small matter of warding off every top club in world football as they eye captain Steven Gerrard, and you can see who is a man with a lot on his plate.\r\nThis will not come as news to who, a lifelong Liverpool supporter, but his quiet determination suggests he is no mood to be found wanting...\r\nCaptain Gerrard is central to Liverpool's plans and who's insistence that all offers will be refused is a firm statement of intent.\r\nMorgan had a succession of bids rejected, having come close in the summer only for talks to break down over potential costs for the new stadium.\r\nwho meanwhile sees the new ground as crucial to Liverpool's future, but is refusing to become emotionally attached to the idea.\r\nHe is determined the ground will only be built on an affordable basis and will not make future Liverpool management hostages to the new stadium.\r\nLiverpool have publicly refused to entertain the idea of stadium sponsorship and potential naming rights - but the realism of Arsenal's stunning \u00c2\u00a3100m deal for their new Emirates Stadium at Ashburton has changed the landscape.\r\nThrough a cleverly worded statement, the club has effectively forced Gerrard to publicly make the decision for himself, which I think is the right thing to do.\r\nwho's statements are clever in that any future Gerrard transfer cannot be construed as a lack of ambition by the club to not try and keep their best players.?",
        "answer": "Parry"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "For an international manager, a friendly provides an important opportunity to work with your players.\r\nSome people have been saying it would be better to get the players together for the week, and do away with the 90 minutes at the end.\r\nI would say it's 50-50 whether you should have these games or not, and if you look at it that way you would probably say you're better not doing so.\r\nBut international bosses will tell you that scrapping friendlies is counterproductive because the only way for a team to get better is by playing.\r\nThe more you play together, the easier it is when it comes to the crunch in games like World Cup quarter-finals against Brazil.",
    "id": "N_118",
    "features": {
        "noun": "manager,",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "provides",
        "adjective": "international",
        "adverb": "together"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "friendly"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Barcelona's pursuit of the Spanish title took a blow on Sunday as they fell to a 2-0 defeat at home to Atletico Madrid.\r\nEngland team-mate Michael Owen came on for Raul after 76 minutes with the game already won.",
    "id": "N_119",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Barcelona's",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "took",
        "adjective": "Spanish",
        "adverb": "already"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Barcelona's pursuit of the Spanish title took a blow on Sunday as they fell to a 2-0 defeat at home to Atletico which location.\r\nEngland team-mate Michael Owen came on for Raul after 76 minutes with the game already won.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But Parry, speaking exclusively to BBC Sport, also admits Gerrard, who has been constantly linked with Chelsea, will have the final say on his future.\r\nBut we are also realistic enough to know we can't keep Steven against his will.\" On the subject of Liverpool's finances, Parry also revealed the club is ready to explore the possibility of a sponsorship deal for its proposed new stadium.\r\nAnd responding to criticism from BBC Sport pundit and former Liverpool stalwart Alan Hansen, he insisted talks on new investment are ongoing, but added the door has not closed on shareholder and lifelong fan Steve Morgan.\r\nThere have been several highs and lows during his time in charge at Anfield - and he had a busy summer, overseeing the arrival of new manager Rafael Benitez and managing to hold on to Steven Gerrard.\r\nHe said: \"They were looking for ways of saying they got more out of the deal for Fernando Morientes, but the response to Real Madrid was the same - Steven is not for sale.\" But when asked if Gerrard would be a Liverpool player on the first day of next season, Parry said: \"I sincerely hope he will be.\r\n\"I think Steven would dearly love to win things with Liverpool more than he'd like to do anything else.\r\nThere are a lot of other players who feel the same, so we all have a common aim.\" It is expected Chelsea will test Liverpool with a \u00c2\u00a330m-plus bid in the summer - but Parry claims he will be in no mood to listen.\r\nAnd he confessed Arsenal's \u00c2\u00a3100m deal with Emirates to sponsor their new ground - complete with naming rights - has given the Anfield club serious food for thought.\r\n\"But the Arsenal deal is the sort of deal that causes you to draw breath and say 'wow - that's interesting.' \"My personal point of view is that I would find it a hell of a lot more palatable than a shared stadium.\" Some Liverpool fans would find such a move highly controversial, but Parry countered: \"I recognise it would be an emotive issue for many supporters, but you look at the amount of money available and it could go into the team.\r\nOn the subject of possible new investment, Parry revealed Liverpool are still in negotiations with a mystery investor, with rumours of interest from the Middle East.\r\nHe also accused Liverpool of using him as \"a stalking horse\" to attract other bids, but Parry explained: \"Steve has never been used as a stalking horse.\r\nThrough a cleverly worded statement, the club has effectively forced Gerrard to publicly make the decision for himself, which I think is the right thing to do.\r\nCritical time for Liverpool with regards to Gerrard.\r\nParry's statements are clever in that any future Gerrard transfer cannot be construed as a lack of ambition by the club to not try and keep their best players.",
    "id": "N_120",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Parry,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "speaking",
        "adjective": "final",
        "adverb": "exclusively"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Brentford face a home tie against holders Manchester United in the FA Cup sixth round if they can come through their replay against Southampton.\r\nNewcastle will be at home to either Tottenham or Nottingham Forest.\r\nBolton host Arsenal or Sheffield United and Leicester will visit the winners of the Burnley and Blackburn replay.\r\nSouthampton or Brentford v Manchester United",
    "id": "N_121",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Brentford",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "sixth",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Brentford face a home tie against holders Manchester United in the FA Cup sixth round if who can come through their replay against Southampton.\r\nNewcastle will be at home to either Tottenham or Nottingham Forest.\r\nBolton host Arsenal or Sheffield United and Leicester will visit the winners of the Burnley and Blackburn replay.\r\nSouthampton or Brentford v Manchester United?",
        "answer": "they"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England's defensive worries have deepened following the withdrawal of Tottenham's Ledley King from the squad to face Holland.\r\nInjured Rio Ferdinand and Sol Campbell were both left out of the squad, and Matthew Upson has already pulled out.",
    "id": "N_122",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "defensive",
        "adverb": "already"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "worries"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Glazer, currently owns a 28.1% stake in the club, and United's statement to the stock exchange said: \"The board has noted the recent press speculation on this subject.\r\n\"The board can confirm that it has now received a detailed proposal subject to various pre-conditions which may form the basis of an offer for Manchester United from Glazer.",
    "id": "N_123",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Glazer,",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "owns",
        "adjective": "recent",
        "adverb": "currently"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Glazer,whocurrentlywhoownswhoawho28.1%whostakewhoinwhothewhoclub,whoandwhoUnited'swhostatementwhotowhothewhostockwhoexchangewhosaid:who\"Thewhoboardwhohaswhonotedwhothewhorecentwhopresswhospeculationwhoonwhothiswhosubject.\r\n\"Thewhoboardwhocanwhoconfirmwhothatwhoitwhohaswhonowwhoreceivedwhoawhodetailedwhoproposalwhosubjectwhotowhovariouswhopre-conditionswhowhichwhomaywhoformwhothewhobasiswhoofwhoanwhoofferwhoforwhoManchesterwhoUnitedwhofromwhoGlazer.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Premier League is attempting to find a mutually convenient date to investigate allegations Chelsea made an illegal approach for Ashley Cole.\r\nBoth Chelsea and Arsenal will be asked to give evidence to a Premier League commission, but no deadline has been put on when that meeting will convene.\r\nChelsea have yet to officially confirm or deny the meeting, which would be in breach of Premier League rule K3.",
    "id": "N_124",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Premier",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "convenient",
        "adverb": "mutually"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The Premier who is attempting to find a mutually convenient date to investigate allegations Chelsea made an illegal approach for Ashley Cole.\r\nBoth Chelsea and Arsenal will be asked to give evidence to a Premier who commission, but no deadline has been put on when that meeting will convene.\r\nChelsea have yet to officially confirm or deny the meeting, which would be in breach of Premier who rule K3.?",
        "answer": "League"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Dundee United manager Ian McCall has won a reprieve from the sack, with chairman Eddie Thompson calling for an end to speculation over his future.\r\nIt is understood that McCall would have been sacked if Sheffield Wednesday manager Paul Sturrock had been willing to return to Tannadice.\r\n\"All that matters at the present time - is us all having a total focus on the games ahead and a positive series of results being achieved.\" Dundee United players had expressed their solidarity with McCall after their side's 3-0 Scottish Cup win over Queen of the South.\r\nI had five years there as a coach, six as a player, two years as a manager - once you've done that kind of thing, it's the result you look for.",
    "id": "N_125",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Dundee",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "understood",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Dundee United manager Ian McCall has won a reprieve from the sack, with chairman Eddie who calling for an end to speculation over his future.\r\nIt is understood that McCall would have been sacked if Sheffield Wednesday manager Paul Sturrock had been willing to return to Tannadice.\r\n\"All that matters at the present time - is us all having a total focus on the games ahead and a positive series of results being achieved.\" Dundee United players had expressed their solidarity with McCall after their side's 3-0 Scottish Cup win over Queen of the South.\r\nI had five years there as a coach, six as a player, two years as a manager - once you've done that kind of thing, it's the result you look for.?",
        "answer": "Thompson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mandic continued in the Sydney Morning Herald: \"Harry's struggling a bit but the club are doing everything they can to get him right.",
    "id": "N_126",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mandic",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "continued",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "MandicwhocontinuedwhoinwhothewhoSydneywhoMorningwhoHerald:who\"Harry'swhostrugglingwhoawhobitwhobutwhothewhoclubwhoarewhodoingwhoeverythingwhotheywhocanwhotowhogetwhohimwhoright.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Scotland manager Walter Smith says he wants to restore the national team's respectability in world football.\r\nSmith has joined his first squad for a three-day get-together near Manchester in preference to playing a friendly.",
    "id": "N_127",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Scotland",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "national",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Scotland manager Walter Smith says who wants to restore twho national team's respectability in world football.\r\nSmith has joined his first squad for a three-day get-togetwhor near Mancwhoster in preference to playing a friendly.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Defenders Danny Gabbidon and Gareth Roberts, plus Ryan Giggs have hamstring concerns, while there are also doubts over Robbie Savage (groin).",
    "id": "N_128",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Defenders",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "DefenderswhoDannywhoGabbidonwhoandwhoGarethwhoRoberts,whopluswhoRyanwhoGiggswhohavewhohamstringwhoconcerns,whowhilewhotherewhoarewhoalsowhodoubtswhooverwhoRobbiewhoSavagewho(groin).?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Larne's teenage star Robbie Weir is poised to join Sunderland after turning down a move to Stoke City.",
    "id": "N_129",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Larne's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Larne's teenage star Robbie who is poised to join Sunderland after turning down a move to Stoke City.?",
        "answer": "Weir"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The IFA upheld its original decision to throw Newry out of the cup following the Andy Crawford registration row.\r\n''This is a big issue, now that we have an appeal pending,'' On Wednesday, a fresh IFA hearing into Crawford registration saga, ruled that last week's original verdict had been correct.\r\nIf we are not back in the Irish Cup after our appeal, and guided by our legal advise, we will seek to lodge an injunction in the courts to stop Bangor playing Portadown.''",
    "id": "N_130",
    "features": {
        "noun": "IFA",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "upheld",
        "adjective": "original",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The what upheld its original decision to throw Newry out of the cup following the Andy Crawford registration row.\r\n''This is a big issue, now that we have an appeal pending,'' On Wednesday, a fresh what hearing into Crawford registration saga, ruled that last week's original verdict had been correct.\r\nIf we are not back in the Irish Cup after our appeal, and guided by our legal advise, we will seek to lodge an injunction in the courts to stop Bangor playing Portadown.''?",
        "answer": "IFA"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Brian Kerr's side will face the 54th ranked Chinese on 29 March - just three days after the World Cup qualifier against Israel in Tel Aviv.\r\nItaly will visit on 17 August in what will be a warm-up game ahead of the autumn World Cup qualifiers.",
    "id": "N_131",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Brian",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "face",
        "adjective": "Chinese",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "54th"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Switzerland, Ireland, France and Israel are all now tied on five points from three matches - although the Republic look to have a slight edge after claiming away draws in Basel and Paris.\r\n\"Looking back, we had an opportunity to get the three points, but we are happy with a point and that will give us confidence going into Wednesday's game.\r\nIt would certainly be good to avoid a play-off, but on the back of a couple of good results I don't see why we can't win the group.\" Manager Brian Kerr was keen to mention the contribution of Stephen Carr and Finnan on Ireland's right flank at the Stade de France.",
    "id": "N_132",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Switzerland,",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "slight",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Switzerland,whoIreland,whoFrancewhoandwhoIsraelwhoarewhoallwhonowwhotiedwhoonwhofivewhopointswhofromwhothreewhomatcheswho-whoalthoughwhothewhoRepublicwholookwhotowhohavewhoawhoslightwhoedgewhoafterwhoclaimingwhoawaywhodrawswhoinwhoBaselwhoandwhoParis.\r\n\"Lookingwhoback,whowewhohadwhoanwhoopportunitywhotowhogetwhothewhothreewhopoints,whobutwhowewhoarewhohappywhowithwhoawhopointwhoandwhothatwhowillwhogivewhouswhoconfidencewhogoingwhointowhoWednesday'swhogame.\r\nItwhowouldwhocertainlywhobewhogoodwhotowhoavoidwhoawhoplay-off,whobutwhoonwhothewhobackwhoofwhoawhocouplewhoofwhogoodwhoresultswhoIwhodon'twhoseewhowhywhowewhocan'twhowinwhothewhogroup.\"whoManagerwhoBrianwhoKerrwhowaswhokeenwhotowhomentionwhothewhocontributionwhoofwhoStephenwhoCarrwhoandwhoFinnanwhoonwhoIreland'swhorightwhoflankwhoatwhothewhoStadewhodewhoFrance.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manager Brian Kerr and FAI officials met representatives from Switzerland, France, Cyprus, Israel and the Faroe Islands to arrange the fixture schedule.\r\nSwitzerland v France; Israel v Faroe Islands; Cyprus v Republic of Ireland.\r\nSwitzerland v France; Israel v Faroe Islands; Cyprus v Republic of Ireland.\r\nSwitzerland v France; Israel v Faroe Islands; Cyprus v Republic of Ireland.",
    "id": "N_133",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manager",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "met",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ManagerwhoBrianwhoKerrwhoandwhoFAIwhoofficialswhometwhorepresentativeswhofromwhoSwitzerland,whoFrance,whoCyprus,whoIsraelwhoandwhothewhoFaroewhoIslandswhotowhoarrangewhothewhofixturewhoschedule.\r\nSwitzerlandwhovwhoFrance;whoIsraelwhovwhoFaroewhoIslands;whoCypruswhovwhoRepublicwhoofwhoIreland.\r\nSwitzerlandwhovwhoFrance;whoIsraelwhovwhoFaroewhoIslands;whoCypruswhovwhoRepublicwhoofwhoIreland.\r\nSwitzerlandwhovwhoFrance;whoIsraelwhovwhoFaroewhoIslands;whoCypruswhovwhoRepublicwhoofwhoIreland.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Four African players, including Zimbabwe goalkeeper Energy Murambadoro, are all ready to play for Israeli club Hapoel Bnei Sakhnin in the Uefa Cup.",
    "id": "N_134",
    "features": {
        "noun": "players,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "including",
        "adjective": "African",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "players"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Iranian striker Vahid Hashemian will not travel to Israel for Bayern Munich's Champions League match against Maccabi Tel Aviv on Wednesday.",
    "id": "N_135",
    "features": {
        "noun": "striker",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "travel",
        "adjective": "Iranian",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Iranian striker Vahid who will not travel to Israel for Bayern Munich's Champions League match against Maccabi Tel Aviv on Wednesday.?",
        "answer": "Hashemian"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Football Association has said it will not be bringing charges over the tunnel incident prior to the Arsenal and Manchester United game.\r\nArsenal's Patrick Vieira had earlier denied accusations that he threatened Gary Neville before the 4-2 defeat.\r\nThey are big enough players to handle themselves,\" said Vieira.\r\nPatrick Vieira has apparently threatened some of our players and things like that.\"",
    "id": "N_136",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Football",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "4-2",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoFootballwhoAssociationwhohaswhosaidwhoitwhowillwhonotwhobewhobringingwhochargeswhooverwhothewhotunnelwhoincidentwhopriorwhotowhothewhoArsenalwhoandwhoManchesterwhoUnitedwhogame.\r\nArsenal'swhoPatrickwhoVieirawhohadwhoearlierwhodeniedwhoaccusationswhothatwhohewhothreatenedwhoGarywhoNevillewhobeforewhothewho4-2whodefeat.\r\nTheywhoarewhobigwhoenoughwhoplayerswhotowhohandlewhothemselves,\"whosaidwhoVieira.\r\nPatrickwhoVieirawhohaswhoapparentlywhothreatenedwhosomewhoofwhoourwhoplayerswhoandwhothingswholikewhothat.\"?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newcastle boss Graeme Souness has reopened his dispute with Craig Bellamy after claiming the Welshman was \"not good enough\" for the Magpies.\r\nBellamy left Newcastle to join Celtic on loan after a major row with Souness.",
    "id": "N_137",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Newcastle",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "good",
        "adverb": "\"not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Newcastle boss Graeme Souness has reopened his dispute with Craig Bellamy after claiming the who was \"not good enough\" for the Magpies.\r\nBellamy left Newcastle to join Celtic on loan after a major row with Souness.?",
        "answer": "Welshman"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "After a quiet opening, James denied Damien Duff, Jiri Jarosik and Mateja Kezman, while Paul Bosvelt cleared William Gallas' header off the line.\r\nChelsea had most of the possession in the second half but James kept out Frank Lampard's free-kick and superbly tipped the same player's volley wide.\r\nFirst, Duff got round Ben Thatcher and blasted in a shot that James parried to Kezman, who turned the ball wide.\r\nChelsea were now looking more like Premiership leaders and James kept out Kezman's fierce drive before Bosvelt and James combined to clear Gallas' header from Duff's corner.\r\nCech, Paulo Ferreira, Gallas, Terry, Bridge, Jarosik (Tiago 56), Lampard, Makelele, Duff, Gudjohnsen, Kezman (Cole 63).",
    "id": "N_138",
    "features": {
        "noun": "opening,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "denied",
        "adjective": "quiet",
        "adverb": "superbly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Afterwhoawhoquietwhoopening,whoJameswhodeniedwhoDamienwhoDuff,whoJiriwhoJarosikwhoandwhoMatejawhoKezman,whowhilewhoPaulwhoBosveltwhoclearedwhoWilliamwhoGallas'whoheaderwhooffwhothewholine.\r\nChelseawhohadwhomostwhoofwhothewhopossessionwhoinwhothewhosecondwhohalfwhobutwhoJameswhokeptwhooutwhoFrankwhoLampard'swhofree-kickwhoandwhosuperblywhotippedwhothewhosamewhoplayer'swhovolleywhowide.\r\nFirst,whoDuffwhogotwhoroundwhoBenwhoThatcherwhoandwhoblastedwhoinwhoawhoshotwhothatwhoJameswhoparriedwhotowhoKezman,whowhowhoturnedwhothewhoballwhowide.\r\nChelseawhowerewhonowwholookingwhomorewholikewhoPremiershipwholeaderswhoandwhoJameswhokeptwhooutwhoKezman'swhofiercewhodrivewhobeforewhoBosveltwhoandwhoJameswhocombinedwhotowhoclearwhoGallas'whoheaderwhofromwhoDuff'swhocorner.\r\nCech,whoPaulowhoFerreira,whoGallas,whoTerry,whoBridge,whoJarosikwho(Tiagowho56),whoLampard,whoMakelele,whoDuff,whoGudjohnsen,whoKezmanwho(Colewho63).?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Barcelona assistant coach Henk Ten Cate has branded Chelsea's expected complaint to Uefa as \"pathetic\".\r\nThe source of Chelsea's anger was an alleged talk between Barca boss Frank Rijkaard and referee Anders Frisk, who later dismissed Didier Drogba.\r\nUefa has said its own tunnel representative witnessed nothing unusual out of the ordinary during the half-time break.\r\nIt is not good behaviour after a match,\" he said.",
    "id": "N_139",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Barcelona",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "assistant",
        "adverb": "later"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Barcelona assistant coach Henk Ten who has branded Chelsea's expected complaint to Uefa as \"pathetic\".\r\nThe source of Chelsea's anger was an alleged talk between Barca boss Frank Rijkaard and referee Anders Frisk, who later dismissed Didier Drogba.\r\nUefa has said its own tunnel representative witnessed nothing unusual out of the ordinary during the half-time break.\r\nIt is not good behaviour after a match,\" he said.?",
        "answer": "Cate"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Benitez responded: \"I spoke to Steven and said to him that in future it's better to think we can win the Champions League.",
    "id": "N_140",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Benitez",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "spoke",
        "adjective": "future",
        "adverb": "better"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Benitezwhoresponded:who\"IwhospokewhotowhoStevenwhoandwhosaidwhotowhohimwhothatwhoinwhofuturewhoit'swhobetterwhotowhothinkwhowewhocanwhowinwhothewhoChampionswhoLeague.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England forward Michael Owen has told the BBC he is happy in Spain and has no plans to quit Real Madrid to return to the Premiership in the near future.\r\n\"For a fourth-choice striker at the start I'm more than happy with the way I've settled in.\" Recent speculation has linked Owen with a move back to England, with Newcastle expressing their interest, but the England striker said he is not ready to return home.\r\n\"I can't keep my eyes off the Premiership on television when I'm at home.\" When asked if it would have to be Liverpool if he returned Owen said: \"I've not really given it much thought.",
    "id": "N_141",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "happy",
        "adverb": "forward"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England forward Michael Owen has told the BBC he is happy in which location and has no plans to quit Real Madrid to return to the Premiership in the near future.\r\n\"For a fourth-choice striker at the start I'm more than happy with the way I've settled in.\" Recent speculation has linked Owen with a move back to England, with Newcastle expressing their interest, but the England striker said he is not ready to return home.\r\n\"I can't keep my eyes off the Premiership on television when I'm at home.\" When asked if it would have to be Liverpool if he returned Owen said: \"I've not really given it much thought.?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The club's managing director, Keith Edelman, stressed that the development of their new \u00c2\u00a3350m stadium had no affect on Wenger's spending power.\r\nEdelman added that it was pointless having a brand new stadium if the team did not match the surroundings.",
    "id": "N_142",
    "features": {
        "noun": "club's",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "managing",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The club's managing director, Keith Edelman, stressed that the what of their new \u00c2\u00a3350m stadium had no affect on Wenger's spending power.\r\nEdelman added that it was pointless having a brand new stadium if the team did not match the surroundings.?",
        "answer": "development"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "An early own goal followed by an Alan Shearer strike earned them a 2-1 win and a place in the Uefa Cup last 16.\r\nBut Souness said he did not think beating the record would have any bearing on his decision to retire at the end of the season.",
    "id": "N_143",
    "features": {
        "noun": "goal",
        "pronoun": "them",
        "verb": "followed",
        "adjective": "early",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "AnwhatearlywhatownwhatgoalwhatfollowedwhatbywhatanwhatAlanwhatShearerwhatstrikewhatearnedwhatthemwhatawhat2-1whatwinwhatandwhatawhatplacewhatinwhatthewhatUefawhatCupwhatlastwhat16.\r\nButwhatSounesswhatsaidwhathewhatdidwhatnotwhatthinkwhatbeatingwhatthewhatrecordwhatwouldwhathavewhatanywhatbearingwhatonwhathiswhatdecisionwhattowhatretirewhatatwhatthewhatendwhatofwhatthewhatseason.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Middlesbrough boss Steve McClaren hopes that Stewart Downing did not seriously damage his hamstring during the 2-1 Uefa Cup win over Graz AK.\r\n\"In the second half we were better but it was frustrating because we got the goal - but one slip and they were back in it.\" Boro face Sporting Lisbon for a place in the quarter-finals after the Portuguese side saw off Feyenoord on Thursday.\r\nAnd McClaren added: \"Sporting are technically very good - Portuguese sides always are.",
    "id": "N_144",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Middlesbrough",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "hopes",
        "adjective": "2-1",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Middlesbrough boss Steve McClaren hopes that Stewart who did not seriously damage his hamstring during the 2-1 Uefa Cup win over Graz AK.\r\n\"In the second half we were better but it was frustrating because we got the goal - but one slip and they were back in it.\" Boro face Sporting Lisbon for a place in the quarter-finals after the Portuguese side saw off Feyenoord on Thursday.\r\nAnd McClaren added: \"Sporting are technically very good - Portuguese sides always are.?",
        "answer": "Downing"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Rangers had rarely threatened until Celtic goalkeeper Rab Douglas let defender Vignal's 25-yard drive slip through his grasp and into the net.\r\nIt ended Celtic's 11-game unbeaten run at home in Old Firm derbies and gave Rangers manager Alex McLeish his first victory at the home of his Glasgow rivals.\r\nBut Waterreus did well to beat away Bellamy's disappointing low drive from 16 yards.\r\nDado Prso turned inside Neil Lennon only for the Celtic goalkeeper to beat away his powerful 18-yard drive.\r\n: Waterreus, Hutton, Kyrgiakos, Andrews, Ball, Buffel, Ferguson, Ricksen, Vignal, Prso, Novo.",
    "id": "N_145",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Rangers",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "25-yard",
        "adverb": "rarely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "RangerswhathadwhatrarelywhatthreatenedwhatuntilwhatCelticwhatgoalkeeperwhatRabwhatDouglaswhatletwhatdefenderwhatVignal'swhat25-yardwhatdrivewhatslipwhatthroughwhathiswhatgraspwhatandwhatintowhatthewhatnet.\r\nItwhatendedwhatCeltic'swhat11-gamewhatunbeatenwhatrunwhatatwhathomewhatinwhatOldwhatFirmwhatderbieswhatandwhatgavewhatRangerswhatmanagerwhatAlexwhatMcLeishwhathiswhatfirstwhatvictorywhatatwhatthewhathomewhatofwhathiswhatGlasgowwhatrivals.\r\nButwhatWaterreuswhatdidwhatwellwhattowhatbeatwhatawaywhatBellamy'swhatdisappointingwhatlowwhatdrivewhatfromwhat16whatyards.\r\nDadowhatPrsowhatturnedwhatinsidewhatNeilwhatLennonwhatonlywhatforwhatthewhatCelticwhatgoalkeeperwhattowhatbeatwhatawaywhathiswhatpowerfulwhat18-yardwhatdrive.\r\n:whatWaterreus,whatHutton,whatKyrgiakos,whatAndrews,whatBall,whatBuffel,whatFerguson,whatRicksen,whatVignal,whatPrso,whatNovo.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Scottish Football Association is awaiting referee Hugh Dallas's report before acting against Hearts winger Saulius Mikoliunas.\r\nRangers' striker Dad Prso was also sent off during the same incident when he received a second yellow card for wrestling the ball away from Craig Gordon and leaving the Hearts keeper on the ground.\r\nHearts' boss John Robertson said: \"Mikoliunas has thrown his chest against the assistant referee's chest and got a red card for it.",
    "id": "N_146",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Scottish",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "referee",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The Scottish Football who is awaiting referee Hugh Dallas's report before acting against Hearts winger Saulius Mikoliunas.\r\nRangers' striker Dad Prso was also sent off during the same incident when he received a second yellow card for wrestling the ball away from Craig Gordon and leaving the Hearts keeper on the ground.\r\nHearts' boss John Robertson said: \"Mikoliunas has thrown his chest against the assistant referee's chest and got a red card for it.?",
        "answer": "Association"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manchester United fans wearing Eric Cantona masks will not be allowed in Selhurst Park on Saturday.",
    "id": "N_147",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manchester",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "wearing",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "fans"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Legendary Dutch coach Rinus Michels, the man credited with developing \"total football\", has died aged 77.\r\nMichels played for Ajax and coached the side to four national titles between 1965-71 and a European Cup in 1971.",
    "id": "N_148",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Dutch",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "credited",
        "adjective": "Legendary",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Legendary Dutch coach Rinus who, the man credited with developing \"total football\", has died aged 77.\r\nwho played for Ajax and coached the side to four national titles between 1965-71 and a European Cup in 1971.?",
        "answer": "Michels"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Forest played with a lot of players behind the ball in the first half, but at 2-0 they were dead and buried.\" Looking ahead to the quarter-final, Jol said: \"Newcastle have got a very good side and they are always difficult.\" However, he added that his side, who are four places above the Magpies in the Premiership, were \"not afraid of anyone\".\r\n\"We dug in and the gaffer said to us at half-time to keep being patient and that the goal will come.\" Forest manager Gary Megson conceded his team did not deserve anything after a poor performance.\r\n\"If you play like we did and concede two goals from corners you're going to have an uphill battle against a very good team,\" he said.",
    "id": "N_149",
    "features": {
        "noun": "lot",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "played",
        "adjective": "\"Forest",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Forestwhatplayedwhatwithwhatawhatlotwhatofwhatplayerswhatbehindwhatthewhatballwhatinwhatthewhatfirstwhathalf,whatbutwhatatwhat2-0whattheywhatwerewhatdeadwhatandwhatburied.\"whatLookingwhataheadwhattowhatthewhatquarter-final,whatJolwhatsaid:what\"Newcastlewhathavewhatgotwhatawhatverywhatgoodwhatsidewhatandwhattheywhatarewhatalwayswhatdifficult.\"whatHowever,whathewhataddedwhatthatwhathiswhatside,whatwhowhatarewhatfourwhatplaceswhatabovewhatthewhatMagpieswhatinwhatthewhatPremiership,whatwerewhat\"notwhatafraidwhatofwhatanyone\".\r\n\"Wewhatdugwhatinwhatandwhatthewhatgafferwhatsaidwhattowhatuswhatatwhathalf-timewhattowhatkeepwhatbeingwhatpatientwhatandwhatthatwhatthewhatgoalwhatwillwhatcome.\"whatForestwhatmanagerwhatGarywhatMegsonwhatconcededwhathiswhatteamwhatdidwhatnotwhatdeservewhatanythingwhatafterwhatawhatpoorwhatperformance.\r\n\"Ifwhatyouwhatplaywhatlikewhatwewhatdidwhatandwhatconcedewhattwowhatgoalswhatfromwhatcornerswhatyou'rewhatgoingwhattowhathavewhatanwhatuphillwhatbattlewhatagainstwhatawhatverywhatgoodwhatteam,\"whathewhatsaid.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Michael Owen revelled in his return to the to the Real Madrid starting line-up and inspired a 3-1 win over Real Betis on Wednesday by scoring the first goal.\r\nVictory took Real to within six points of leaders Barcelona and Owen is confident Real can close the gap.",
    "id": "N_150",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Michael",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "revelled",
        "adjective": "line-up",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Michael Owen revelled in his return to the to the Real which location starting line-up and inspired a 3-1 win over Real Betis on Wednesday by scoring the first goal.\r\nVictory took Real to within six points of leaders Barcelona and Owen is confident Real can close the gap.?",
        "answer": "Madrid"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manchester United manager Sir Alex Ferguson said his side's task against AC Milan would not be made any easier by the absence of Andriy Shevchenko.\r\n\"It's a loss (to Milan), but it could be worse if they didn't have such quality to bring in,\" Ferguson said.\r\nFerguson's own goalscoring talisman Ruud van Nistelrooy is fit again, but the Scot admitted he was unsure whether to start the Dutchman, who has not played for three months.\r\n\"Hopefully, we can get to that final in Turkey and bring the cup back to Manchester.\" Milan coach Carlo Ancelotti said his team were looking forward to returning to the venue where they lifted Europe's most prestigious club title two seasons ago.",
    "id": "N_151",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manchester",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "easier",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Manchester United manager Sir Alex Ferguson said his side's what against AC Milan would not be made any easier by the absence of Andriy Shevchenko.\r\n\"It's a loss (to Milan), but it could be worse if they didn't have such quality to bring in,\" Ferguson said.\r\nFerguson's own goalscoring talisman Ruud van Nistelrooy is fit again, but the Scot admitted he was unsure whether to start the Dutchman, who has not played for three months.\r\n\"Hopefully, we can get to that final in Turkey and bring the cup back to Manchester.\" Milan coach Carlo Ancelotti said his team were looking forward to returning to the venue where they lifted Europe's most prestigious club title two seasons ago.?",
        "answer": "task"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ian Rush's future as Chester manager is uncertain after he and assistant Mark Aizlewood refused a severance package.",
    "id": "N_152",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ian",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "uncertain",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "IanwhoRush'swhofuturewhoaswhoChesterwhomanagerwhoiswhouncertainwhoafterwhohewhoandwhoassistantwhoMarkwhoAizlewoodwhorefusedwhoawhoseverancewhopackage.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jose Antonio Reyes has added to speculation linking him with a move from Arsenal to Real Madrid after falling victim to a radio prank.\r\n\"I'm happy Madrid is interested in me because it has always been my dream since I was little to play there.\" Before the story surfaced, Reyes had moved to play down reports linking him with the Spanish giants, issuing a statement through Arsenal describing the speculation as \"flattering\".\r\n\"I have seen the stories in the media linking me with Real Madrid,\" he had said on Thursday lunchtime.",
    "id": "N_153",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jose",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "happy",
        "adverb": "always"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jose Antonio who has added to speculation linking him with a move from Arsenal to Real Madrid after falling victim to a radio prank.\r\n\"I'm happy Madrid is interested in me because it has always been my dream since I was little to play there.\" Before the story surfaced, who had moved to play down reports linking him with the Spanish giants, issuing a statement through Arsenal describing the speculation as \"flattering\".\r\n\"I have seen the stories in the media linking me with Real Madrid,\" he had said on Thursday lunchtime.?",
        "answer": "Reyes"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Benitez defended goalkeeper Jerzy Dudek, whose failure to hold on to Dimitar Berbatov's weak drive allowed Franca to score with the last kick of the game - and give the German team a lifeline for the second leg.\r\n\"He had played a very good game - and had we scored our other chances, nobody would be talking about about their goal.\r\n\"Steven Gerrard is a key player for us,\" said Benitez.",
    "id": "N_154",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Benitez",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "defended",
        "adjective": "goalkeeper",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "BenitezwhatdefendedwhatgoalkeeperwhatJerzywhatDudek,whatwhosewhatfailurewhattowhatholdwhatonwhattowhatDimitarwhatBerbatov'swhatweakwhatdrivewhatallowedwhatFrancawhattowhatscorewhatwithwhatthewhatlastwhatkickwhatofwhatthewhatgamewhat-whatandwhatgivewhatthewhatGermanwhatteamwhatawhatlifelinewhatforwhatthewhatsecondwhatleg.\r\n\"Hewhathadwhatplayedwhatawhatverywhatgoodwhatgamewhat-whatandwhathadwhatwewhatscoredwhatourwhatotherwhatchances,whatnobodywhatwouldwhatbewhattalkingwhataboutwhataboutwhattheirwhatgoal.\r\n\"StevenwhatGerrardwhatiswhatawhatkeywhatplayerwhatforwhatus,\"whatsaidwhatBenitez.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newcastle boss Graeme Souness is lining up a summer move for England and Real Madrid striker Michael Owen.\r\n\"I'm after three, four or five new players in the summer - we have got lots of targets,\" he said.",
    "id": "N_155",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Newcastle",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "three,",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Newcastle boss Graeme Souness is lining up a summer move for which location and Real Madrid striker Michael Owen.\r\n\"I'm after three, four or five new players in the summer - we have got lots of targets,\" he said.?",
        "answer": "England"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kolo Toure's late goal gives the Gunners hope for the second leg, but Wenger said: \"The only positive is that we are still in the tie.\r\nThis was a bad night - but I still have confidence in the quality of my players, as well as their spirit and desire.\" But Wenger's Bayern counterpart Felix Magath was in no mood to celebrate either.\r\n\"Arsenal are fully capable of scoring several goals against us on their own turf.\" Arsenal keeper Jens Lehmann, whose personal rivalry with Bayern goalkeeper Oliver Kahn was not helped by the result, said: \"Do I blame myself for the third goal?",
    "id": "N_156",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kolo",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "gives",
        "adjective": "late",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "KolowhatToure'swhatlatewhatgoalwhatgiveswhatthewhatGunnerswhathopewhatforwhatthewhatsecondwhatleg,whatbutwhatWengerwhatsaid:what\"Thewhatonlywhatpositivewhatiswhatthatwhatwewhatarewhatstillwhatinwhatthewhattie.\r\nThiswhatwaswhatawhatbadwhatnightwhat-whatbutwhatIwhatstillwhathavewhatconfidencewhatinwhatthewhatqualitywhatofwhatmywhatplayers,whataswhatwellwhataswhattheirwhatspiritwhatandwhatdesire.\"whatButwhatWenger'swhatBayernwhatcounterpartwhatFelixwhatMagathwhatwaswhatinwhatnowhatmoodwhattowhatcelebratewhateither.\r\n\"Arsenalwhatarewhatfullywhatcapablewhatofwhatscoringwhatseveralwhatgoalswhatagainstwhatuswhatonwhattheirwhatownwhatturf.\"whatArsenalwhatkeeperwhatJenswhatLehmann,whatwhosewhatpersonalwhatrivalrywhatwithwhatBayernwhatgoalkeeperwhatOliverwhatKahnwhatwaswhatnotwhathelpedwhatbywhatthewhatresult,whatsaid:what\"DowhatIwhatblamewhatmyselfwhatforwhatthewhatthirdwhatgoal??",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "AC Milan defender Jaap Stam says Manchester United \"know they made a mistake\" by selling him in 2001.\r\n\"I was settled at Manchester United, but they wanted to sell me.\r\nWednesday's game at Old Trafford will provide an intriguing confrontation between United's young attackers Wayne Rooney and Cristiano Ronaldo and Milan's veteran defence of Stam, Paolo Maldini, Cafu and Alessandro Costacurta.\r\nStam says Rooney's teenage stardom is in stark contract to his own start in the game.",
    "id": "N_157",
    "features": {
        "noun": "AC",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "defender",
        "adjective": "intriguing",
        "adverb": "me."
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "AC Milan defender Jaap Stam says Manchester United \"know who made a mistake\" by selling him in 2001.\r\n\"I was settled at Manchester United, but who wanted to sell me.\r\nWednesday's game at Old Trafford will provide an intriguing confrontation between United's young attackers Wayne Rooney and Cristiano Ronaldo and Milan's veteran defence of Stam, Paolo Maldini, Cafu and Alessandro Costacurta.\r\nStam says Rooney's teenage stardom is in stark contract to his own start in the game.?",
        "answer": "they"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mourinho's side were knocked out of the FA Cup by Newcastle last Sunday before seeing Barcelona secure a 2-1 Champions League first-leg lead in the Nou Camp.\r\n\"In the Champions League all three teams can either go through or go out but the one team that is in the best position is still Chelsea.\"",
    "id": "N_158",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mourinho's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "either"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Mourinho's side were knocked out of the FA Cup by Newcastle last Sunday before seeing who secure a 2-1 Champions League first-leg lead in the Nou Camp.\r\n\"In the Champions League all three teams can either go through or go out but the one team that is in the best position is still Chelsea.\"?",
        "answer": "Barcelona"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former Blackburn boss Roy Hodgson says the Premiership should follow the rest of Europe and have a winter break - but insists that a gruelling domestic schedule will not damage the English elite's bid for Champions League glory.\r\nIt gives players the chance to recharge their batteries midway through the season, which some suggest will give teams an advantage in the Champions League.\r\n\"The bigger discussions around the winter break should be to do with the nature of football today, the needs of football players and the way the Premiership has developed, rather than one or two matches in the Champions League in February.\" Hodgson believes a winter break carries many advantages, explaining: \"As I said, it is the perfect chance to recharge batteries.\r\n\"In pre-season you get a lot of enthusiasm and energy but by the time you get towards Christmas many players, having also played plenty of international matches for club and country and travelled a lot, find themselves getting very jaded.",
    "id": "N_159",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "gruelling",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "FormerwhatBlackburnwhatbosswhatRoywhatHodgsonwhatsayswhatthewhatPremiershipwhatshouldwhatfollowwhatthewhatrestwhatofwhatEuropewhatandwhathavewhatawhatwinterwhatbreakwhat-whatbutwhatinsistswhatthatwhatawhatgruellingwhatdomesticwhatschedulewhatwillwhatnotwhatdamagewhatthewhatEnglishwhatelite'swhatbidwhatforwhatChampionswhatLeaguewhatglory.\r\nItwhatgiveswhatplayerswhatthewhatchancewhattowhatrechargewhattheirwhatbatterieswhatmidwaywhatthroughwhatthewhatseason,whatwhichwhatsomewhatsuggestwhatwillwhatgivewhatteamswhatanwhatadvantagewhatinwhatthewhatChampionswhatLeague.\r\n\"Thewhatbiggerwhatdiscussionswhataroundwhatthewhatwinterwhatbreakwhatshouldwhatbewhattowhatdowhatwithwhatthewhatnaturewhatofwhatfootballwhattoday,whatthewhatneedswhatofwhatfootballwhatplayerswhatandwhatthewhatwaywhatthewhatPremiershipwhathaswhatdeveloped,whatratherwhatthanwhatonewhatorwhattwowhatmatcheswhatinwhatthewhatChampionswhatLeaguewhatinwhatFebruary.\"whatHodgsonwhatbelieveswhatawhatwinterwhatbreakwhatcarrieswhatmanywhatadvantages,whatexplaining:what\"AswhatIwhatsaid,whatitwhatiswhatthewhatperfectwhatchancewhattowhatrechargewhatbatteries.\r\n\"Inwhatpre-seasonwhatyouwhatgetwhatawhatlotwhatofwhatenthusiasmwhatandwhatenergywhatbutwhatbywhatthewhattimewhatyouwhatgetwhattowardswhatChristmaswhatmanywhatplayers,whathavingwhatalsowhatplayedwhatplentywhatofwhatinternationalwhatmatcheswhatforwhatclubwhatandwhatcountrywhatandwhattravelledwhatawhatlot,whatfindwhatthemselveswhatgettingwhatverywhatjaded.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Claudio Ranieri has been sacked as Valencia coach just eight months after taking charge at the Primera Liga club for the second time in his career.\r\nRanieri first took charge of Valencia in 1997, guiding them to the King's Cup and helping them to qualify for the Champions League.",
    "id": "N_160",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Claudio",
        "pronoun": "them",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Claudio who has been sacked as Valencia coach just eight months after taking charge at the Primera Liga club for the second time in his career.\r\nwho first took charge of Valencia in 1997, guiding them to the King's Cup and helping them to qualify for the Champions League.?",
        "answer": "Ranieri"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Whether he has an operation has got to be left to Chelsea.\" Cole, who also struggled with an ankle problem earlier in the season, was unable to rest because O'Leary had a shortage of strikers.",
    "id": "N_161",
    "features": {
        "noun": "operation",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "unable",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Whether he has an what has got to be left to Chelsea.\" Cole, who also struggled with an ankle problem earlier in the season, was unable to rest because O'Leary had a shortage of strikers.?",
        "answer": "operation"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Lauren, Patrick Vieira, Freddie Ljungberg and Ashley Cole scored for Arsenal, while Andy Gray and Phil Jagielka were on target for the Blades.\r\nArsenal were barely seen as an attacking force in the opening 45 minutes, although Ljungberg turned a half-chance wide after good work by Cesc Fabregas.\r\nOwusu-Abeyie's pace was causing all sorts of problems for the Blades, and as extra-time began, another surging run into the penalty area almost set up a chance for Ljungberg.\r\nKenny, Geary, Morgan, Bromby, Harley, Liddell, Montgomery, Jagielka, Thirlwell, Tonge (Quinn 97), Gray.\r\nAlmunia, Lauren, Cygan, Senderos, Cole, Fabregas (Toure 90), Vieira, Flamini (Aliadiere 113), Clichy, Lupoli (Owusu-Abeyie 45), Ljungberg.",
    "id": "N_162",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Lauren,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "scored",
        "adjective": "wide",
        "adverb": "barely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Lauren,whoPatrickwhoVieira,whoFreddiewhoLjungbergwhoandwhoAshleywhoColewhoscoredwhoforwhoArsenal,whowhilewhoAndywhoGraywhoandwhoPhilwhoJagielkawhowerewhoonwhotargetwhoforwhothewhoBlades.\r\nArsenalwhowerewhobarelywhoseenwhoaswhoanwhoattackingwhoforcewhoinwhothewhoopeningwho45whominutes,whoalthoughwhoLjungbergwhoturnedwhoawhohalf-chancewhowidewhoafterwhogoodwhoworkwhobywhoCescwhoFabregas.\r\nOwusu-Abeyie'swhopacewhowaswhocausingwhoallwhosortswhoofwhoproblemswhoforwhothewhoBlades,whoandwhoaswhoextra-timewhobegan,whoanotherwhosurgingwhorunwhointowhothewhopenaltywhoareawhoalmostwhosetwhoupwhoawhochancewhoforwhoLjungberg.\r\nKenny,whoGeary,whoMorgan,whoBromby,whoHarley,whoLiddell,whoMontgomery,whoJagielka,whoThirlwell,whoTongewho(Quinnwho97),whoGray.\r\nAlmunia,whoLauren,whoCygan,whoSenderos,whoCole,whoFabregaswho(Tourewho90),whoVieira,whoFlaminiwho(Aliadierewho113),whoClichy,whoLupoliwho(Owusu-Abeyiewho45),whoLjungberg.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But in a statement on Spurs' website, Jol said: \"I'm happy here, I'm not in discussion with anyone else, I don't want to go elsewhere.\" Ajax have enlisted the help of Dutch legend Johann Cruyff, currently a consultant at Barcelona, to help find a new head coach.",
    "id": "N_163",
    "features": {
        "noun": "statement",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "don't",
        "adjective": "happy",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Baros, who is Liverpool's leading scorer this season, denied reports of a row with Benitez but claims he is mystified at being left on the bench.",
    "id": "N_164",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Baros,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Southampton's David Prutton faces a possible seven-match ban when he goes before the Football Association.\r\nPaolo di Canio was given a seven-match suspension when he pushed referee Paul Alcock over in a Premiership game between Sheffield Wednesday and Arsenal in 1998.\r\nHe was out of order but he knows that,\" said Redknapp.\r\nOff the pitch you couldn't meet a nicer lad.\" Prutton has apologised publicly for his actions and to Arsenal's Robert Pires, who was injured in a wild tackle by the Saints' midfield man.",
    "id": "N_165",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Southampton's",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "faces",
        "adjective": "possible",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Southampton's David Prutton faces a possible seven-match ban wwhon who goes before twho Football Association.\r\nPaolo di Canio was given a seven-match suspension wwhon who puswhod referee Paul Alcock over in a Premiership game between Swhoffield Wednesday and Arsenal in 1998.\r\nHe was out of order but who knows that,\" said Redknapp.\r\nOff twho pitch you couldn't meet a nicer lad.\" Prutton has apologised publicly for his actions and to Arsenal's Robert Pires, who was injured in a wild tackle by twho Saints' midfield man.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Injured Chelsea winger Arjen Robben has insisted that he only has a 10% chance of making a return against Barcelona in the Champions League.",
    "id": "N_166",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Injured",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Injured Cwholsea winger Arjen Robben has insisted that who only has a 10% chance of making a return against Barcelona in twho Champions League.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Rinaldi told BBC Sport: \"I have to say that nobody from Chelsea or any other London club has contacted me.\r\n\"If Chelsea are interested then they must make an offer.\" Inter are reported to have slapped a price tag in the region of \u00c2\u00a340m on the head of Adriano, who joined them just over a year ago from Parma.\r\nBut Rinaldi said: \"I cannot give you a price that Inter would accept for Adriano.",
    "id": "N_167",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Rinaldi",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "other",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "RinaldiwhattoldwhatBBCwhatSport:what\"IwhathavewhattowhatsaywhatthatwhatnobodywhatfromwhatChelseawhatorwhatanywhatotherwhatLondonwhatclubwhathaswhatcontactedwhatme.\r\n\"IfwhatChelseawhatarewhatinterestedwhatthenwhattheywhatmustwhatmakewhatanwhatoffer.\"whatInterwhatarewhatreportedwhattowhathavewhatslappedwhatawhatpricewhattagwhatinwhatthewhatregionwhatofwhat\u00c2\u00a340mwhatonwhatthewhatheadwhatofwhatAdriano,whatwhowhatjoinedwhatthemwhatjustwhatoverwhatawhatyearwhatagowhatfromwhatParma.\r\nButwhatRinaldiwhatsaid:what\"IwhatcannotwhatgivewhatyouwhatawhatpricewhatthatwhatInterwhatwouldwhatacceptwhatforwhatAdriano.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Football Association will take no action against Chelsea boss Jose Mourinho following his sending-off in Sunday's Carling Cup final.\r\nMourinho still faces an FA investigation into his allegation that Manchester United's players 'cheated' during January's Carling Cup semi-final at Stamford Bridge.",
    "id": "N_168",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Football",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "take",
        "adjective": "semi-final",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The Football who will take no action against Chelsea boss Jose Mourinho following his sending-off in Sunday's Carling Cup final.\r\nMourinho still faces an FA investigation into his allegation that Manchester United's players 'cheated' during January's Carling Cup semi-final at Stamford Bridge.?",
        "answer": "Association"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Spain coach Luis Aragones is furious after being fined by The Spanish Football Federation for his comments about Thierry Henry.\r\nI've never done that and I have medals for sporting merit.\" Aragones was handed the fine on Tuesday after making racist remarks about Henry to Arsenal team-mate and Spanish international Jose Reyes last October.\r\nThe Spanish Football Federation at first declined to take action against Aragones, but was then requested to do so by Spain's anti-violence commission.",
    "id": "N_169",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Spain",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "furious",
        "adverb": "never"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Spain coach Luis who is furious after being fined by The Spanish Football Federation for his comments about Thierry Henry.\r\nI've never done that and I have medals for sporting merit.\" who was handed the fine on Tuesday after making racist remarks about Henry to Arsenal team-mate and Spanish international Jose Reyes last October.\r\nThe Spanish Football Federation at first declined to take action against who, but was then requested to do so by Spain's anti-violence commission.?",
        "answer": "Aragones"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A club spokesman confirmed: \"It is a bilateral sportsman's hernia, which was operated on yesterday.\" Morrison was sent for scans after being substituted at half-time during Boro's 2-1 UEFA Cup win over Graz AK in which he scored the equaliser.",
    "id": "N_170",
    "features": {
        "noun": "club",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "bilateral",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "which"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The pair worked together at Barcelona and Porto and Robson had a word of warning for his protege.\r\n\"It has all gone for him just lately and that is marvellous, but sometimes you have to have a bit of humility and learn how to lose,\" said Robson.\r\n\"Jose is doing very well at the moment,\" Robson added of the man who worked for him for six years.",
    "id": "N_171",
    "features": {
        "noun": "pair",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "worked",
        "adjective": "marvellous,",
        "adverb": "together"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The pair worked together at which location and Porto and Robson had a word of warning for his protege.\r\n\"It has all gone for him just lately and that is marvellous, but sometimes you have to have a bit of humility and learn how to lose,\" said Robson.\r\n\"Jose is doing very well at the moment,\" Robson added of the man who worked for him for six years.?",
        "answer": "Barcelona"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Queens Park Rangers keeper Chris Day is set to join Preston on a month's loan.\r\nDay has been displaced by the arrival of Simon Royce, who is in his second month on loan from Charlton.",
    "id": "N_172",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Queens",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "keeper",
        "adjective": "month's",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Queens Park Rangers keeper Chris who is set to join Preston on a month's loan.\r\nwho has been displaced by the arrival of Simon Royce, who is in his second month on loan from Charlton.?",
        "answer": "Day"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But Mourinho has used Cudicini regularly in the Carling Cup, and the Italian has only let in one goal in his four appearances during Chelsea's run to the final.",
    "id": "N_173",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mourinho",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "regularly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"He has spoken to manager David Moyes about what happened.\" Beattie was suspended for the win at Aston Villa after his red card against Chelsea and he will be available again for the Merseyside derby at Liverpool on 20 March.",
    "id": "N_174",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"He",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "red",
        "adverb": "again"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "what"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"He is still a quality player and knows where the net is - we have just got to supply him with ammunition and, in the end, we did,\" Keegan said.\r\n\"People want to write him off but if he has kept the articles of those people who have written him off he could throw them back at them and they would be left with a bit of egg on their face.\" Fowler's double strike helped City come back from two goals down to clinch a dramatic win at Carrow Road and Keegan sympathised with Norwich boss Nigel Worthington afterwards.",
    "id": "N_175",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"He",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "dramatic",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Hewhoiswhostillwhoawhoqualitywhoplayerwhoandwhoknowswhowherewhothewhonetwhoiswho-whowewhohavewhojustwhogotwhotowhosupplywhohimwhowithwhoammunitionwhoand,whoinwhothewhoend,whowewhodid,\"whoKeeganwhosaid.\r\n\"Peoplewhowantwhotowhowritewhohimwhooffwhobutwhoifwhohewhohaswhokeptwhothewhoarticleswhoofwhothosewhopeoplewhowhowhohavewhowrittenwhohimwhooffwhohewhocouldwhothrowwhothemwhobackwhoatwhothemwhoandwhotheywhowouldwhobewholeftwhowithwhoawhobitwhoofwhoeggwhoonwhotheirwhoface.\"whoFowler'swhodoublewhostrikewhohelpedwhoCitywhocomewhobackwhofromwhotwowhogoalswhodownwhotowhoclinchwhoawhodramaticwhowinwhoatwhoCarrowwhoRoadwhoandwhoKeeganwhosympathisedwhowithwhoNorwichwhobosswhoNigelwhoWorthingtonwhoafterwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He's always put Liverpool first.\" Thompson, who savoured seven title-winning seasons and two European Cup triumphs during his Anfield playing career, is confident that the lure of Champions League football will keep Gerrard at Anfield.\r\n\"I hope Champions League football will beckon for Liverpool - either as winners or as finishing fourth in the Premiership - and he will commit himself.",
    "id": "N_176",
    "features": {
        "noun": "He's",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "put",
        "adjective": "title-winning",
        "adverb": "always"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who's always put Liverpool first.\" Thompson, who savoured seven title-winning seasons and two European Cup triumphs during his Anfield playing career, is confident that the lure of Champions League football will keep Gerrard at Anfield.\r\n\"I hope Champions League football will beckon for Liverpool - either as winners or as finishing fourth in the Premiership - and he will commit himself.?",
        "answer": "He"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ashley Cole has refused to blame Robin van Persie for leaving Arsenal with no fully-fit strikers for the FA Cup fifth round replay at Sheffield United.\r\nFreddie Ljungberg is likely to be used in an emergency striking role and will be partnered by either Arturo Lupoli, Quincy Owusu-Abeyie or Jeremie Aliadiere.",
    "id": "N_177",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ashley",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "fully-fit",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ashley who has refused to blame Robin van Persie for leaving Arsenal with no fully-fit strikers for the FA Cup fifth round replay at Sheffield United.\r\nFreddie Ljungberg is likely to be used in an emergency striking role and will be partnered by either Arturo Lupoli, Quincy Owusu-Abeyie or Jeremie Aliadiere.?",
        "answer": "Cole"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "- Blackburn boss Mark Hughes: \"Burnley are resolute and have individual talent but I fully expect us to progress.\r\n- Rovers, who are aiming to win the Cup for a seventh time in their history and first time in 77 years, face another replay against Championship opposition after eventually disposing of Cardiff at Ewood Park in the third round.\r\nBut they've not been beaten in the competition by a club outside the Premiership for nine years, since Ipswich - then in the second tier - defeated them 0-1 after extra time in a third round replay at Ewood Park on 16 January 1996.\r\nWhen they last met their near neighbours in the FA Cup 45 years ago, it also required an Ewood Park replay, which the home side won 2-0, and when they last met in the League, Rovers did the double.\r\n- Manager Mark Hughes, who won the Cup four times as a player, is aiming to steer Rovers into the quarter-finals for the second time in 12 years, and first time since the 2000/2001 season.\r\nSuccess here, and victory home to Leicester in the next round, could see Rovers in the semi-finals without having played Premiership opposition.\r\n- While Blackburn have not played since the fifth round tie, Burnley have had two League outings away from home, drawing 1-1 at Derby and losing 1-0 at Preston.",
    "id": "N_178",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Blackburn",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "resolute",
        "adverb": "fully"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "-whoBlackburnwhobosswhoMarkwhoHughes:who\"BurnleywhoarewhoresolutewhoandwhohavewhoindividualwhotalentwhobutwhoIwhofullywhoexpectwhouswhotowhoprogress.\r\n-whoRovers,whowhowhoarewhoaimingwhotowhowinwhothewhoCupwhoforwhoawhoseventhwhotimewhoinwhotheirwhohistorywhoandwhofirstwhotimewhoinwho77whoyears,whofacewhoanotherwhoreplaywhoagainstwhoChampionshipwhooppositionwhoafterwhoeventuallywhodisposingwhoofwhoCardiffwhoatwhoEwoodwhoParkwhoinwhothewhothirdwhoround.\r\nButwhothey'vewhonotwhobeenwhobeatenwhoinwhothewhocompetitionwhobywhoawhoclubwhooutsidewhothewhoPremiershipwhoforwhoninewhoyears,whosincewhoIpswichwho-whothenwhoinwhothewhosecondwhotierwho-whodefeatedwhothemwho0-1whoafterwhoextrawhotimewhoinwhoawhothirdwhoroundwhoreplaywhoatwhoEwoodwhoParkwhoonwho16whoJanuarywho1996.\r\nWhenwhotheywholastwhometwhotheirwhonearwhoneighbourswhoinwhothewhoFAwhoCupwho45whoyearswhoago,whoitwhoalsowhorequiredwhoanwhoEwoodwhoParkwhoreplay,whowhichwhothewhohomewhosidewhowonwho2-0,whoandwhowhenwhotheywholastwhometwhoinwhothewhoLeague,whoRoverswhodidwhothewhodouble.\r\n-whoManagerwhoMarkwhoHughes,whowhowhowonwhothewhoCupwhofourwhotimeswhoaswhoawhoplayer,whoiswhoaimingwhotowhosteerwhoRoverswhointowhothewhoquarter-finalswhoforwhothewhosecondwhotimewhoinwho12whoyears,whoandwhofirstwhotimewhosincewhothewho2000/2001whoseason.\r\nSuccesswhohere,whoandwhovictorywhohomewhotowhoLeicesterwhoinwhothewhonextwhoround,whocouldwhoseewhoRoverswhoinwhothewhosemi-finalswhowithoutwhohavingwhoplayedwhoPremiershipwhoopposition.\r\n-whoWhilewhoBlackburnwhohavewhonotwhoplayedwhosincewhothewhofifthwhoroundwhotie,whoBurnleywhohavewhohadwhotwowhoLeaguewhooutingswhoawaywhofromwhohome,whodrawingwho1-1whoatwhoDerbywhoandwholosingwho1-0whoatwhoPreston.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "- Brentford boss Martin Allen: \"After conceding eight goals in our last three matches, I have to admit I'm not very confident.\r\n- BRENTFORD are the lowest ranked club left in the FA Cup. They're on their best run in the competition since reaching the quarter-finals for the fourth time in their history 16 years ago.\r\nVictory over Premiership strugglers Southampton, would bring the mighty Manchester United to Griffin Park and a gigantic pay day for the sole League One survivors.\r\nSouthampton striker Henri Camara scored twice from close range to put the Saints in command, but Isaiah Rankin hit back just before half time, and Sam Sodje headed past a creaky defence on 58 minutes.\r\nBut they haven't lost in six League and Cup games on home turf - winning three and drawing three since the reverse to Torquay on Boxing Day.\r\n- Victory here would set up a repeat of the 1976 final, when Saints astounded the football world by defeating Tommy Docherty's Manchester United courtesy of Bobby Stokes' famous winner.\r\n- To get to within two matches of a second visit to the Millennium Stadium in three years for the final, Harry Redknapp must guide his side past a club 36 places inferior on the League ladder, and a manager 19 years his junior, who played under him at West Ham. HEAD TO HEAD",
    "id": "N_179",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Brentford",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "conceding",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "- Brentford boss Martin Allen: \"After conceding eight goals in our last three matches, who have to admit who'm not very confident.\r\n- BRENTFORD are the lowest ranked club left in the FA Cup. They're on their best run in the competition since reaching the quarter-finals for the fourth time in their history 16 years ago.\r\nVictory over Premiership strugglers Southampton, would bring the mighty Manchester United to Griffin Park and a gigantic pay day for the sole League One survivors.\r\nSouthampton striker Henri Camara scored twice from close range to put the Saints in command, but whosaiah Rankin hit back just before half time, and Sam Sodje headed past a creaky defence on 58 minutes.\r\nBut they haven't lost in six League and Cup games on home turf - winning three and drawing three since the reverse to Torquay on Boxing Day.\r\n- Victory here would set up a repeat of the 1976 final, when Saints astounded the football world by defeating Tommy Docherty's Manchester United courtesy of Bobby Stokes' famous winner.\r\n- To get to within two matches of a second visit to the Millennium Stadium in three years for the final, Harry Redknapp must guide his side past a club 36 places inferior on the League ladder, and a manager 19 years his junior, who played under him at West Ham. HEAD TO HEAD?",
        "answer": "I"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The French star was part of the Chelsea side crushed 5-1 at the Nou Camp in the Champions League quarter-final second leg in 2000.\r\nFormer Chelsea captain Desailly, who is now playing for Al-Gharafa in Qatar, says there is no comparison between that side and the current Blues team, who are top of the Premiership.\r\nThis team has a new motivation and a different mentality.\" World Cup winner Desailly saw huge changes during his time at Stamford Bridge.\r\n\"Since that game in 2000, Chelsea have gained more experience in Europe and were very close to reaching the Champions League final last season.\" Desailly is one of the most decorated players in the history of football.\r\n\"And it's amazing that Paolo has managed to play at such a high level for such a long time.\"",
    "id": "N_180",
    "features": {
        "noun": "star",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "French",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The French what was part of the Chelsea side crushed 5-1 at the Nou Camp in the Champions League quarter-final second leg in 2000.\r\nFormer Chelsea captain Desailly, who is now playing for Al-Gharafa in Qatar, says there is no comparison between that side and the current Blues team, who are top of the Premiership.\r\nThis team has a new motivation and a different mentality.\" World Cup winner Desailly saw huge changes during his time at Stamford Bridge.\r\n\"Since that game in 2000, Chelsea have gained more experience in Europe and were very close to reaching the Champions League final last season.\" Desailly is one of the most decorated players in the history of football.\r\n\"And it's amazing that Paolo has managed to play at such a high level for such a long time.\"?",
        "answer": "star"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The French star was part of the Chelsea side crushed 5-1 at the Nou Camp in the Champions League quarter-final second leg in 2000.\r\nFormer Chelsea captain Desailly, who is now playing for Al-Gharafa in Qatar, says there is no comparison between that side and the current Blues team, who are top of the Premiership.\r\nThis team has a new motivation and a different mentality.\" World Cup winner Desailly saw huge changes during his time at Stamford Bridge.\r\n\"Since that game in 2000, Chelsea have gained more experience in Europe and were very close to reaching the Champions League final last season.\" Desailly is one of the most decorated players in the history of football.\r\n\"And it's amazing that Paolo has managed to play at such a high level for such a long time.\"",
    "id": "N_181",
    "features": {
        "noun": "star",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "French",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The French what was part of the Chelsea side crushed 5-1 at the Nou Camp in the Champions League quarter-final second leg in 2000.\r\nFormer Chelsea captain Desailly, who is now playing for Al-Gharafa in Qatar, says there is no comparison between that side and the current Blues team, who are top of the Premiership.\r\nThis team has a new motivation and a different mentality.\" World Cup winner Desailly saw huge changes during his time at Stamford Bridge.\r\n\"Since that game in 2000, Chelsea have gained more experience in Europe and were very close to reaching the Champions League final last season.\" Desailly is one of the most decorated players in the history of football.\r\n\"And it's amazing that Paolo has managed to play at such a high level for such a long time.\"?",
        "answer": "star"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Chelsea manager Jose Mourinho expects the Champions League clash with Barcelona to be a fight to the finish.\r\n\"I have been managing for five years and I have the same amount of Champions League trophies to my name.\" Barcelona star Ronaldinho admitted: \"I think that it is going to be a difficult match for us because Chelsea have a good team full of big stars.",
    "id": "N_182",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Chelsea",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "expects",
        "adjective": "same",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Chelsea manager Jose who expects the Champions League clash with Barcelona to be a fight to the finish.\r\n\"I have been managing for five years and I have the same amount of Champions League trophies to my name.\" Barcelona star Ronaldinho admitted: \"I think that it is going to be a difficult match for us because Chelsea have a good team full of big stars.?",
        "answer": "Mourinho"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Holders Manchester United and Premiership leaders Chelsea both face difficult away ties against Premiership opposition in the FA Cup fifth round.\r\nArsenal were handed a potential home tie against fellow Londoners West Ham, providing the Hammers come through their replay against Sheffield United.\r\nCharlton will play Leicester and Bolton await the winners of the Derby-Fulham replay.",
    "id": "N_183",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Holders",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "face",
        "adjective": "difficult",
        "adverb": "away"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "HolderswhoManchesterwhoUnitedwhoandwhoPremiershipwholeaderswhoChelseawhobothwhofacewhodifficultwhoawaywhotieswhoagainstwhoPremiershipwhooppositionwhoinwhothewhoFAwhoCupwhofifthwhoround.\r\nArsenalwhowerewhohandedwhoawhopotentialwhohomewhotiewhoagainstwhofellowwhoLondonerswhoWestwhoHam,whoprovidingwhothewhoHammerswhocomewhothroughwhotheirwhoreplaywhoagainstwhoSheffieldwhoUnited.\r\nCharltonwhowillwhoplaywhoLeicesterwhoandwhoBoltonwhoawaitwhothewhowinnerswhoofwhothewhoDerby-Fulhamwhoreplay.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"In June I will decide whether to continue to play for Bolton or retire from professional football.\" Allardyce hopes Candela's arrival will relieve Bolton's injury crisis after defender Nicky Hunt limped out injured during Oldham's 1-0 win against Oldham in the FA Cup on Sunday.",
    "id": "N_184",
    "features": {
        "noun": "June",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "decide",
        "adjective": "professional",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"InwhoJunewhoIwhowillwhodecidewhowhetherwhotowhocontinuewhotowhoplaywhoforwhoBoltonwhoorwhoretirewhofromwhoprofessionalwhofootball.\"whoAllardycewhohopeswhoCandela'swhoarrivalwhowillwhorelievewhoBolton'swhoinjurywhocrisiswhoafterwhodefenderwhoNickywhoHuntwholimpedwhooutwhoinjuredwhoduringwhoOldham'swho1-0whowinwhoagainstwhoOldhamwhoinwhothewhoFAwhoCupwhoonwhoSunday.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Norwich have signed Charlton midfielder Graham Stuart until the end of the season for an undisclosed fee.\r\nHopefully, he can be part of keeping us in the Premier League.\" Stuart has extensive top-flight experience with Everton, Chelsea and Charlton and can play across the midfield positions.",
    "id": "N_185",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Norwich",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "undisclosed",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who have signed Charlton midfielder Graham Stuart until the end of the season for an undisclosed fee.\r\nHopefully, he can be part of keeping us in the Premier League.\" Stuart has extensive top-flight experience with Everton, Chelsea and Charlton and can play across the midfield positions.?",
        "answer": "Norwich"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newcastle striker Craig Bellamy is discussing a possible short-term loan move to Celtic, BBC Sport understands.\r\nAnd it is unlikely that Newcastle would allow the player to go on loan to another Premiership club.",
    "id": "N_186",
    "features": {
        "noun": "striker",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "Newcastle",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Newcastle striker Craig Bellamy is discussing a possible short-term loan move to Celtic, BBC who understands.\r\nAnd it is unlikely that Newcastle would allow the player to go on loan to another Premiership club.?",
        "answer": "Sport"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arsenal's Sol Campbell has called the rivalry between Manchester United and the Gunners \"bitter and personal\".\r\nYou try and balance out over the course of a season but I've had so many rough decisions against them you begin to wonder.\" With tensions spilling over afterwards - United boss Sir Alex Ferguson was allegedly pelted with pizza in the players' tunnel - there is little surprise that so much is riding on the return encounter on.\r\n\"Everyone at Arsenal has been waiting for this game,\" said Campbell.",
    "id": "N_187",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arsenal's",
        "pronoun": "You",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "many",
        "adverb": "so"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Arsenal'swhoSolwhoCampbellwhohaswhocalledwhothewhorivalrywhobetweenwhoManchesterwhoUnitedwhoandwhothewhoGunnerswho\"bitterwhoandwhopersonal\".\r\nYouwhotrywhoandwhobalancewhooutwhooverwhothewhocoursewhoofwhoawhoseasonwhobutwhoI'vewhohadwhosowhomanywhoroughwhodecisionswhoagainstwhothemwhoyouwhobeginwhotowhowonder.\"whoWithwhotensionswhospillingwhooverwhoafterwardswho-whoUnitedwhobosswhoSirwhoAlexwhoFergusonwhowaswhoallegedlywhopeltedwhowithwhopizzawhoinwhothewhoplayers'whotunnelwho-whotherewhoiswholittlewhosurprisewhothatwhosowhomuchwhoiswhoridingwhoonwhothewhoreturnwhoencounterwhoon.\r\n\"EveryonewhoatwhoArsenalwhohaswhobeenwhowaitingwhoforwhothiswhogame,\"whosaidwhoCampbell.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Blackburn have said all along that they want \u00c2\u00a36m for the midfielder and Williams has rejected proposals from Rangers over a player-swap deal.\r\nWilliams said: \"We are in dialogue with Glasgow Rangers but we have no agreement.\" The negotiations will have to be concluded by midnight on Monday, when the winter transfer window shuts.",
    "id": "N_188",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Blackburn",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "player-swap",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Blackburnwhohavewhosaidwhoallwhoalongwhothatwhotheywhowantwho\u00c2\u00a36mwhoforwhothewhomidfielderwhoandwhoWilliamswhohaswhorejectedwhoproposalswhofromwhoRangerswhooverwhoawhoplayer-swapwhodeal.\r\nWilliamswhosaid:who\"WewhoarewhoinwhodialoguewhowithwhoGlasgowwhoRangerswhobutwhowewhohavewhonowhoagreement.\"whoThewhonegotiationswhowillwhohavewhotowhobewhoconcludedwhobywhomidnightwhoonwhoMonday,whowhenwhothewhowinterwhotransferwhowindowwhoshuts.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mauritius host the first group, and their opponents are Madagascar, the Seychelles and South Africa.\r\nBafana Bafana play the Seychelles before Mauritius take on Madagascar in a double-header on 26 February.\r\nThe two winners return to the New George V stadium the next day and the victor of the group decider advances to August's final mini-tournament.\r\nIn June, former champions Zambia will host Lesotho, Malawi and Swaziland in the third group in Lusaka.",
    "id": "N_189",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mauritius",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "host",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Reid rejected a move to Southampton after Forest accepted a cash-plus-players offer while Spurs had made previous bids for the 22-year-old.",
    "id": "N_190",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Reid",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "rejected",
        "adjective": "previous",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "Spurs"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "New Southampton manager Harry Redknapp faces an immediate reunion with his old club Portsmouth after they were drawn together in the FA Cup fourth round.\r\nExeter City face a home tie against Middlesbrough if they can see off holders Manchester United in a replay.\r\nOldham's reward for beating Manchester City is a home tie with Bolton, while Yeovil will be away to Charlton.\r\nChelsea host Birmingham, Tottenham travel to West Brom and Arsenal will entertain Championship side Wolves.\r\n\"Maybe I'll be in for some stick, there's always some of that but we'll get on with it and it's only a game of football.\" Birmingham manager Steve Bruce admitted their trip to Stamford Bridge to face Premiership leaders Chelsea was the toughest draw possible.\r\n\"But it's the best competition in the world as far as I am concerned and we will give it our best shot.\" Brentford boss Martin Allen remained cautious despite his side's favourable draw - a home tie with either Hartlepool or Boston.",
    "id": "N_191",
    "features": {
        "noun": "New",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "faces",
        "adjective": "immediate",
        "adverb": "together"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "New Southampton manager Harry Redknapp faces an immediate reunion with his old club Portsmouth after who were drawn together in the FA Cup fourth round.\r\nExeter City face a home tie against Middlesbrough if who can see off holders Manchester United in a replay.\r\nOldham's reward for beating Manchester City is a home tie with Bolton, while Yeovil will be away to Charlton.\r\nChelsea host Birmingham, Tottenham travel to West Brom and Arsenal will entertain Championship side Wolves.\r\n\"Maybe I'll be in for some stick, there's always some of that but we'll get on with it and it's only a game of football.\" Birmingham manager Steve Bruce admitted their trip to Stamford Bridge to face Premiership leaders Chelsea was the toughest draw possible.\r\n\"But it's the best competition in the world as far as I am concerned and we will give it our best shot.\" Brentford boss Martin Allen remained cautious despite his side's favourable draw - a home tie with either Hartlepool or Boston.?",
        "answer": "they"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Real Madrid are closing in on a \u00c2\u00a32m deal for Everton's Thomas Gravesen after the Dane's agent travelled to Spain to hold talks about a move.\r\nManager David Moyes has defiantly claimed that he expects Gravesen to still be at Everton when the transfer window closes at the end of January.",
    "id": "N_192",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Madrid",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "Real",
        "adverb": "defiantly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Real Madrid are closing in on a \u00c2\u00a32m deal for Everton's Thomas Gravesen after the Dane's what travelled to Spain to hold talks about a move.\r\nManager David Moyes has defiantly claimed that he expects Gravesen to still be at Everton when the transfer window closes at the end of January.?",
        "answer": "agent"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Germany coach Jurgen Klinsmann has warned goalkeeper Jens Lehmann he may have to quit Arsenal to keep his World Cup dreams alive.",
    "id": "N_193",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Germany",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Germany coach Jurgen Klinsmann has warned goalkeeper Jens Lehmann he may have to quit Arsenal to keep his World who dreams alive.?",
        "answer": "Cup"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Juninho's agent has confirmed that the player is hoping for talks with Martin O'Neill as the Brazilian midfielder comes closer to departing Celtic.\r\nHassel says Juninho, who has just bought a new home, would \"desperately like to stay at Celtic\" but will seek a move if it is made clear that he is not wanted.\r\n\"I know there is interest from a Brazilian club, but I know Juninho doesn't want to go there,\" said Hassel.\r\nIn fact, he wants to stay at Celtic.\" Hassall made it clear that a move to Manchester City, who are badly in need of a midfield play-maker, was more of a possibility than Botafogo, or Mexican outfit Red Sharks Veracruz, who also expressed an interest.",
    "id": "N_194",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Juninho's",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Brazilian",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Juninho's agent has confirmed that the player is hoping for talks with Martin O'Neill as the Brazilian what comes closer to departing Celtic.\r\nHassel says Juninho, who has just bought a new home, would \"desperately like to stay at Celtic\" but will seek a move if it is made clear that he is not wanted.\r\n\"I know there is interest from a Brazilian club, but I know Juninho doesn't want to go there,\" said Hassel.\r\nIn fact, he wants to stay at Celtic.\" Hassall made it clear that a move to Manchester City, who are badly in need of a midfield play-maker, was more of a possibility than Botafogo, or Mexican outfit Red Sharks Veracruz, who also expressed an interest.?",
        "answer": "midfielder"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arsenal manager Arsene Wenger has signed a new contract to stay at the club until May 2008.\r\nWenger has ended speculation about his future by agreeing a long-term contract that takes him beyond the opening of Arsenal's new stadium in two years.\r\nHe said: \"Signing a new contract just rubber-stamps my desire to take this club forward and fulfil my ambitions.",
    "id": "N_195",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arsenal",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Arsenal manager Arsene who has signed a new contract to stay at the club until May 2008.\r\nwho has ended speculation about his future by agreeing a long-term contract that takes him beyond the opening of Arsenal's new stadium in two years.\r\nHe said: \"Signing a new contract just rubber-stamps my desire to take this club forward and fulfil my ambitions.?",
        "answer": "Wenger"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The FA is to take action after trouble marred Wednesday's Carling Cup tie between Chelsea and West Ham.\r\nHe did not require stitches.\" West Ham boss Alan Pardew said: \"It's a shame because I thought there was good English banter in the crowd.\r\nPolice in riot gear battled with West Ham fans in the Matthew Harding stand and at least one supporter required treatment.",
    "id": "N_196",
    "features": {
        "noun": "FA",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "good",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhatFAwhatiswhattowhattakewhatactionwhatafterwhattroublewhatmarredwhatWednesday'swhatCarlingwhatCupwhattiewhatbetweenwhatChelseawhatandwhatWestwhatHam.\r\nHewhatdidwhatnotwhatrequirewhatstitches.\"whatWestwhatHamwhatbosswhatAlanwhatPardewwhatsaid:what\"It'swhatawhatshamewhatbecausewhatIwhatthoughtwhattherewhatwaswhatgoodwhatEnglishwhatbanterwhatinwhatthewhatcrowd.\r\nPolicewhatinwhatriotwhatgearwhatbattledwhatwithwhatWestwhatHamwhatfanswhatinwhatthewhatMatthewwhatHardingwhatstandwhatandwhatatwhatleastwhatonewhatsupporterwhatrequiredwhattreatment.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"The United players were trying to wind us up about the result but I didn't see any soup being thrown at anyone.\" However, Edu tried to play down the incidents, adding: \"There was nothing that I haven't seen in Brazilian derbies.\r\n\"Reyes was being kicked all over the park - they were beating up the boy and Gary Neville was tackling in such a way that he should have been sent off.\" Following the game, the Football Association said it would look into events in the tunnel.",
    "id": "N_197",
    "features": {
        "noun": "United",
        "pronoun": "us",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "anyone.\"",
        "adverb": "\"The"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"In coming to a decision on this case, Chelsea believed the club's social responsibility to its fans, players, employees and other stakeholders in football regarding drugs was more important than the major financial considerations to the company.\r\n\"Any player who takes drugs breaches his contract with the club as well as Football Association rules.\r\n\"It is a very clear stance by Chelsea and it has given a strong boost to the reputation of the club.\" It emerged that Mutu had failed a drugs test on October 18 and, although it was initially reported that the banned substance in question was cocaine.",
    "id": "N_198",
    "features": {
        "noun": "decision",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "coming",
        "adjective": "social",
        "adverb": "\"In"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Inwhatcomingwhattowhatawhatdecisionwhatonwhatthiswhatcase,whatChelseawhatbelievedwhatthewhatclub'swhatsocialwhatresponsibilitywhattowhatitswhatfans,whatplayers,whatemployeeswhatandwhatotherwhatstakeholderswhatinwhatfootballwhatregardingwhatdrugswhatwaswhatmorewhatimportantwhatthanwhatthewhatmajorwhatfinancialwhatconsiderationswhattowhatthewhatcompany.\r\n\"AnywhatplayerwhatwhowhattakeswhatdrugswhatbreacheswhathiswhatcontractwhatwithwhatthewhatclubwhataswhatwellwhataswhatFootballwhatAssociationwhatrules.\r\n\"ItwhatiswhatawhatverywhatclearwhatstancewhatbywhatChelseawhatandwhatitwhathaswhatgivenwhatawhatstrongwhatboostwhattowhatthewhatreputationwhatofwhatthewhatclub.\"whatItwhatemergedwhatthatwhatMutuwhathadwhatfailedwhatawhatdrugswhattestwhatonwhatOctoberwhat18whatand,whatalthoughwhatitwhatwaswhatinitiallywhatreportedwhatthatwhatthewhatbannedwhatsubstancewhatinwhatquestionwhatwaswhatcocaine.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sir Alex Ferguson has called on the Football Association to punish Arsenal's Thierry Henry for an incident involving Gabriel Heinze.\r\nFerguson believes Henry deliberately caught Heinze on the head with his knee during United's controversial win.\r\n\"There were 24 fouls in the game by Arsenal, seven on Heinze, five on Ronaldo, six by Vieira - and it was only his sixth foul that got him booked.",
    "id": "N_199",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sir",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "controversial",
        "adverb": "deliberately"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Sir Alex who has called on the Football Association to punish Arsenal's Thierry Henry for an incident involving Gabriel Heinze.\r\nwho believes Henry deliberately caught Heinze on the head with his knee during United's controversial win.\r\n\"There were 24 fouls in the game by Arsenal, seven on Heinze, five on Ronaldo, six by Vieira - and it was only his sixth foul that got him booked.?",
        "answer": "Ferguson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arsenal boss Arsene Wenger would consider signing Adrian Mutu once the striker has served his drugs ban.\r\nMutu was sacked by Chelsea on Friday after testing positive for cocaine - a move Wenger has backed.\r\nChelsea decided to act before his case was heard and sacked the striker on grounds of gross misconduct after it was revealed that he had failed a drug test.\r\nBut Mutu has hit out at the club's decision, saying: \"Chelsea have destroyed me.\" He told the Sunday Mirror: \"I don't know what I'm going to do.",
    "id": "N_200",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arsenal",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "consider",
        "adjective": "Adrian",
        "adverb": "once"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Arsenal boss Arsene Wenger would consider signing Adrian Mutu once the what has served his drugs ban.\r\nMutu was sacked by Chelsea on Friday after testing positive for cocaine - a move Wenger has backed.\r\nChelsea decided to act before his case was heard and sacked the what on grounds of gross misconduct after it was revealed that he had failed a drug test.\r\nBut Mutu has hit out at the club's decision, saying: \"Chelsea have destroyed me.\" He told the Sunday Mirror: \"I don't know what I'm going to do.?",
        "answer": "striker"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tottenham manager Jacques Santini has resigned for \"personal reasons\".\r\nArnesen said the club were sad to see Santini go: \"We are obviously disappointed that Jacques is leaving us.",
    "id": "N_201",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tottenham",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "\"personal",
        "adverb": "obviously"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tottenham manager Jacques who has resigned for \"personal reasons\".\r\nArnesen said the club were sad to see who go: \"We are obviously disappointed that Jacques is leaving us.?",
        "answer": "Santini"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Disgraced former Chelsea striker Adrian Mutu is to begin talks with Juventus as he looks for a new club.",
    "id": "N_202",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Disgraced",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "former",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Disgraced former Cwholsea striker Adrian Mutu is to begin talks with Juventus as who looks for a new club.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"We have sanctioned its use from the start of next season but only as long as it is the latest generation of artificial turf and meets a whole series of standards.\" Several leading clubs from Scandinavia, Russia and eastern Europe - especially those who only play Champions League or Uefa Cup matches in winter - are now expected to instal artificial pitches.",
    "id": "N_203",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"We",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Wewhohavewhosanctionedwhoitswhousewhofromwhothewhostartwhoofwhonextwhoseasonwhobutwhoonlywhoaswholongwhoaswhoitwhoiswhothewholatestwhogenerationwhoofwhoartificialwhoturfwhoandwhomeetswhoawhowholewhoserieswhoofwhostandards.\"whoSeveralwholeadingwhoclubswhofromwhoScandinavia,whoRussiawhoandwhoeasternwhoEuropewho-whoespeciallywhothosewhowhowhoonlywhoplaywhoChampionswhoLeaguewhoorwhoUefawhoCupwhomatcheswhoinwhowinterwho-whoarewhonowwhoexpectedwhotowhoinstalwhoartificialwhopitches.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Premiership side Newcastle United face a trip to Ryman Premier League leaders Yeading in the FA Cup third round.\r\nConference side Exeter City, who knocked out Doncaster on Saturday, will travel to Old Trafford to meet holders Manchester United in January.\r\nArsenal were drawn at home to Stoke and Chelsea will play host to Scunthorpe.\r\nThe only other non-League side in the draw are Hinckley United, who held Brentford to a goalless draw on Sunday.\r\nA number of Premiership teams face difficult away games against Championship sides on the weekend of 8/9 January.\r\nThird-placed Everton visit Plymouth, Liverpool travel to Burnley, Crystal Palace go to Sunderland, Fulham face Carling Cup semi-finalists Watford, Bolton meet Ipswich, while Aston Villa were drawn against Sheffield United.\r\nPremiership strugglers Norwich, Blackburn, West Brom are away at West Ham, Cardiff and Preston North End respectively.\r\nSouthampton visit Northampton, having already beaten the League Two side in the Carling Cup earlier this season.\r\nMiddlesbrough were drawn away against either Swindon or Notts County, while Spurs entertain Brighton at White Hart Lane.",
    "id": "N_204",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Premiership",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "Yeading",
        "adjective": "side",
        "adverb": "away"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Premiership side Newcastle who face a trip to Ryman Premier League leaders Yeading in the FA Cup third round.\r\nConference side Exeter City, who knocked out Doncaster on Saturday, will travel to Old Trafford to meet holders Manchester who in January.\r\nArsenal were drawn at home to Stoke and Chelsea will play host to Scunthorpe.\r\nThe only other non-League side in the draw are Hinckley who, who held Brentford to a goalless draw on Sunday.\r\nA number of Premiership teams face difficult away games against Championship sides on the weekend of 8/9 January.\r\nThird-placed Everton visit Plymouth, Liverpool travel to Burnley, Crystal Palace go to Sunderland, Fulham face Carling Cup semi-finalists Watford, Bolton meet Ipswich, while Aston Villa were drawn against Sheffield who.\r\nPremiership strugglers Norwich, Blackburn, West Brom are away at West Ham, Cardiff and Preston North End respectively.\r\nSouthampton visit Northampton, having already beaten the League Two side in the Carling Cup earlier this season.\r\nMiddlesbrough were drawn away against either Swindon or Notts County, while Spurs entertain Brighton at White Hart Lane.?",
        "answer": "United"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Striker Nicolas Anelka reportedly wants to leave Manchester City in search of Champions League football.\r\nAnelka, 25, is in talks over a contract extension beyond 2007 with City but is believed to fear his career will go stale if he stays at the club.",
    "id": "N_205",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Striker",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "wants",
        "adjective": "stale",
        "adverb": "reportedly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Striker Nicolas who reportedly wants to leave Manchester City in search of Champions League football.\r\nwho, 25, is in talks over a contract extension beyond 2007 with City but is believed to fear his career will go stale if he stays at the club.?",
        "answer": "Anelka"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tottenham sporting director Frank Arnesen has denied that coach Jacques Santini resigned because of a clash of personalities at White Hart Lane.\r\n\"When it comes down to personal problems, I don't think we should talk about timing,\" he said.\r\nTottenham's structure of having a sporting director working alongside a coach is based on a continental model and Arnesen sees no reason why they should change it.\r\n\"I think the problems go a lot deeper, between the director of football at White Hart Lane and Santini,\" Stevens told Five Live.",
    "id": "N_206",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tottenham",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "sporting",
        "adjective": "personal",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tottenham sporting director Frank Arnesen has denied that coach Jacques who resigned because of a clash of personalities at White Hart Lane.\r\n\"When it comes down to personal problems, I don't think we should talk about timing,\" he said.\r\nTottenham's structure of having a sporting director working alongside a coach is based on a continental model and Arnesen sees no reason why they should change it.\r\n\"I think the problems go a lot deeper, between the director of football at White Hart Lane and who,\" Stevens told Five Live.?",
        "answer": "Santini"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Graeme Souness believes Walter Smith would be the perfect choice to succeed Berti Vogts as Scotland manager.\r\nThe Scottish Football Association has appointed Tommy Burns as provisional caretaker-boss for the friendly against Sweden on 17 November.\r\nThe Scottish Football Association is about to embark on the search for Vogts successor after appointing Tommy Burns in a caretaker capacity.\r\nHe was asking me about it and I was positive.\" Other candidates for the job include former Scotland midfielders Gordon Strachan and Gary McAllister and Vogts' assistant Tommy Burns.",
    "id": "N_207",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Graeme",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "perfect",
        "adverb": "about"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Graeme Souness believes Walter who would be the perfect choice to succeed Berti Vogts as Scotland manager.\r\nThe Scottish Football Association has appointed Tommy Burns as provisional caretaker-boss for the friendly against Sweden on 17 November.\r\nThe Scottish Football Association is about to embark on the search for Vogts successor after appointing Tommy Burns in a caretaker capacity.\r\nHe was asking me about it and I was positive.\" Other candidates for the job include former Scotland midfielders Gordon Strachan and Gary McAllister and Vogts' assistant Tommy Burns.?",
        "answer": "Smith"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "You need a bit of both but it will be as hard for the Arsenal players as it is for the Chelsea boys.\" \"We know that we have got the power in our hands just now,\" added Gallas.\r\n\"Obviously, nobody at Chelsea wants to come second but you never know what happens in football.\r\n\"Another incredible quality that Mourinho has is that every player, even though the fans may consider them to be a stars, within the dressing-room they are absolutely equal.",
    "id": "N_208",
    "features": {
        "noun": "bit",
        "pronoun": "You",
        "verb": "need",
        "adjective": "hard",
        "adverb": "as"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "YouwhoneedwhoawhobitwhoofwhobothwhobutwhoitwhowillwhobewhoaswhohardwhoforwhothewhoArsenalwhoplayerswhoaswhoitwhoiswhoforwhothewhoChelseawhoboys.\"who\"Wewhoknowwhothatwhowewhohavewhogotwhothewhopowerwhoinwhoourwhohandswhojustwhonow,\"whoaddedwhoGallas.\r\n\"Obviously,whonobodywhoatwhoChelseawhowantswhotowhocomewhosecondwhobutwhoyouwhoneverwhoknowwhowhatwhohappenswhoinwhofootball.\r\n\"AnotherwhoincrediblewhoqualitywhothatwhoMourinhowhohaswhoiswhothatwhoeverywhoplayer,whoevenwhothoughwhothewhofanswhomaywhoconsiderwhothemwhotowhobewhoawhostars,whowithinwhothewhodressing-roomwhotheywhoarewhoabsolutelywhoequal.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Some 65 years ago Bernardo Gandulla left Boca Juniors in his native Argentina and headed for Brazil.\r\nAnother Boca Juniors player is coming to Brazil.\r\n'The new Maradona' - Carlos Tevez - is joining Corinthians for nearly $20m in a strong candidate for the strangest move of the year.\r\nIt is particularly strange as - until last week - Tevez was not even an especially big name in Brazil, where the Argentine Championship is not shown.\r\nSo now he says that he is heading for Corinthians in search of 'tranquillity.' Anyone acquainted with the city of S&#227;o Paulo will relish the nonsense of this declaration.\r\nBrazil's biggest city is a sprawling, ugly, restless metropolis.\r\nThe most turbulent place in this frenetic city is Sport Club Corinthians.",
    "id": "N_209",
    "features": {
        "noun": "years",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "left",
        "adjective": "native",
        "adverb": "ago"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Some 65 years ago Bernardo Gandulla left Boca Juniors in his native which location and headed for Brazil.\r\nAnother Boca Juniors player is coming to Brazil.\r\n'The new Maradona' - Carlos Tevez - is joining Corinthians for nearly $20m in a strong candidate for the strangest move of the year.\r\nIt is particularly strange as - until last week - Tevez was not even an especially big name in Brazil, where the Argentine Championship is not shown.\r\nSo now he says that he is heading for Corinthians in search of 'tranquillity.' Anyone acquainted with the city of S&#227;o Paulo will relish the nonsense of this declaration.\r\nBrazil's biggest city is a sprawling, ugly, restless metropolis.\r\nThe most turbulent place in this frenetic city is Sport Club Corinthians.?",
        "answer": "Argentina"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"If they had really wanted to sign they should have come up with an offer six months before indicating they wanted to sign me and that's made me think.\" Edu's brother and representative Amadeo Fensao has previously said that Arsenal's current offer to the midfielder was well short of what he was seeking.\r\n\"That's nice, but I've never talked to them, so I can't say they want me sign 100%.\" Last month Wenger said he we was hopeful Edu would sign a new deal and played down suggestions that the lure of a club like Real Madrid would be too strong for Edu. Edu added that he had been encouraged by Wenger's support for him.",
    "id": "N_210",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"If",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "think.\"",
        "adverb": "really"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Ifwhotheywhohadwhoreallywhowantedwhotowhosignwhotheywhoshouldwhohavewhocomewhoupwhowithwhoanwhoofferwhosixwhomonthswhobeforewhoindicatingwhotheywhowantedwhotowhosignwhomewhoandwhothat'swhomadewhomewhothink.\"whoEdu'swhobrotherwhoandwhorepresentativewhoAmadeowhoFensaowhohaswhopreviouslywhosaidwhothatwhoArsenal'swhocurrentwhoofferwhotowhothewhomidfielderwhowaswhowellwhoshortwhoofwhowhatwhohewhowaswhoseeking.\r\n\"That'swhonice,whobutwhoI'vewhoneverwhotalkedwhotowhothem,whosowhoIwhocan'twhosaywhotheywhowantwhomewhosignwho100%.\"whoLastwhomonthwhoWengerwhosaidwhohewhowewhowaswhohopefulwhoEduwhowouldwhosignwhoawhonewwhodealwhoandwhoplayedwhodownwhosuggestionswhothatwhothewholurewhoofwhoawhoclubwholikewhoRealwhoMadridwhowouldwhobewhotoowhostrongwhoforwhoEdu.whoEduwhoaddedwhothatwhohewhohadwhobeenwhoencouragedwhobywhoWenger'swhosupportwhoforwhohim.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The man who was Alex Ferguson's assistant when Scotland played at the 1986 World Cup won seven league titles with Rangers.\r\nCharacters like Souness, Ferguson and current Ibrox manager Alex McLeish all cite Smith's experience and his expansive knowledge of the Scottish game.\r\nBut it should be remembered Vogts came to Scotland with an impressive curriculum vitae - a World Cup winner as a player and a European Championships winner as a manager.\r\nA fresh start for the Scottish national team was imperative and Smith is widely regarded as a safe pair of hands.",
    "id": "N_211",
    "features": {
        "noun": "man",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "current",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The man who was Alex Ferguson's assistant when who played at the 1986 World Cup won seven league titles with Rangers.\r\nCharacters like Souness, Ferguson and current Ibrox manager Alex McLeish all cite Smith's experience and his expansive knowledge of the Scottish game.\r\nBut it should be remembered Vogts came to who with an impressive curriculum vitae - a World Cup winner as a player and a European Championships winner as a manager.\r\nA fresh start for the Scottish national team was imperative and Smith is widely regarded as a safe pair of hands.?",
        "answer": "Scotland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Rovers' assistant manager Mark Bowen said: \"Matt had a small operation to trim knee cartilage.\r\nBowen added: \"I'm guessing, but I reckon maybe two to three weeks before he is back in action completely.\" The Rovers assistant boss forecast a longer time spell for Amoruso's availability for first-team duties.",
    "id": "N_212",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Rovers'",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "small",
        "adverb": "maybe"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Rovers' assistant manager Mark Bowen said: \"who had a small operation to trim knee cartilage.\r\nBowen added: \"I'm guessing, but I reckon maybe two to three weeks before he is back in action completely.\" The Rovers assistant boss forecast a longer time spell for Amoruso's availability for first-team duties.?",
        "answer": "Matt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "An second-half goal from Andy Scott condemned Mansfield to a ninth successive game without a win.\r\nAs Orient chased a second, Mansfield had to clear Alan White's header off the line and Kevin Pilkington saved well from Michael Simpson.",
    "id": "N_213",
    "features": {
        "noun": "goal",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "condemned",
        "adjective": "second-half",
        "adverb": "well"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "An second-half what from Andy Scott condemned Mansfield to a ninth successive game without a win.\r\nAs Orient chased a second, Mansfield had to clear Alan White's header off the line and Kevin Pilkington saved well from Michael Simpson.?",
        "answer": "goal"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Zambia's technical director, Kalusha Bwalya is confident and cautious ahead of the Cosafa Cup final against Angola on Saturday in Lusaka.\r\nThat victory for Angola also marked a first defeat in 14 years for Zambia at Lusaka's Independence stadium, where Saturday's game is being played.",
    "id": "N_214",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Zambia's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "technical",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Zambia'swhattechnicalwhatdirector,whatKalushawhatBwalyawhatiswhatconfidentwhatandwhatcautiouswhataheadwhatofwhatthewhatCosafawhatCupwhatfinalwhatagainstwhatAngolawhatonwhatSaturdaywhatinwhatLusaka.\r\nThatwhatvictorywhatforwhatAngolawhatalsowhatmarkedwhatawhatfirstwhatdefeatwhatinwhat14whatyearswhatforwhatZambiawhatatwhatLusaka'swhatIndependencewhatstadium,whatwherewhatSaturday'swhatgamewhatiswhatbeingwhatplayed.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England's 1-0 defeat to Spain on Wednesday dominated the back and front pages of the country's press on Thursday.\r\nBut AS does cover the English reaction to the pre-match comments from Spain coach Luis Aragones, who highlighted Britain's colonial past when probed about his own remarks regarding Thierry Henry in October.\r\nAragones' \"no comment\" to questions about racism after the match is also highlighted, as Marca focuses on the Spanish coach's praise for his players.\r\nRooney seemed intent to kick any Spanish player who approached him.\" Yet Rooney is seen only as the worst example of many England miscreants, with Gary Neville criticised for continuing the feud between Manchester United and Arsenal for his tackles on Jose Reyes.\r\n\"Xavi did things on Wednesday which were worthy of Maradona,\" the paper beams, adding, \"What a work-rate, what dynamism, what vision, what leadership, what a midfield player!\" On a controversial evening, AS offers one seemingly undeniable viewpoint: \"Spanish football players played better football than the English.\"",
    "id": "N_215",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England's",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "dominated",
        "adjective": "1-0",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England'swhat1-0whatdefeatwhattowhatSpainwhatonwhatWednesdaywhatdominatedwhatthewhatbackwhatandwhatfrontwhatpageswhatofwhatthewhatcountry'swhatpresswhatonwhatThursday.\r\nButwhatASwhatdoeswhatcoverwhatthewhatEnglishwhatreactionwhattowhatthewhatpre-matchwhatcommentswhatfromwhatSpainwhatcoachwhatLuiswhatAragones,whatwhowhathighlightedwhatBritain'swhatcolonialwhatpastwhatwhenwhatprobedwhataboutwhathiswhatownwhatremarkswhatregardingwhatThierrywhatHenrywhatinwhatOctober.\r\nAragones'what\"nowhatcomment\"whattowhatquestionswhataboutwhatracismwhatafterwhatthewhatmatchwhatiswhatalsowhathighlighted,whataswhatMarcawhatfocuseswhatonwhatthewhatSpanishwhatcoach'swhatpraisewhatforwhathiswhatplayers.\r\nRooneywhatseemedwhatintentwhattowhatkickwhatanywhatSpanishwhatplayerwhatwhowhatapproachedwhathim.\"whatYetwhatRooneywhatiswhatseenwhatonlywhataswhatthewhatworstwhatexamplewhatofwhatmanywhatEnglandwhatmiscreants,whatwithwhatGarywhatNevillewhatcriticisedwhatforwhatcontinuingwhatthewhatfeudwhatbetweenwhatManchesterwhatUnitedwhatandwhatArsenalwhatforwhathiswhattackleswhatonwhatJosewhatReyes.\r\n\"XaviwhatdidwhatthingswhatonwhatWednesdaywhatwhichwhatwerewhatworthywhatofwhatMaradona,\"whatthewhatpaperwhatbeams,whatadding,what\"Whatwhatawhatwork-rate,whatwhatwhatdynamism,whatwhatwhatvision,whatwhatwhatleadership,whatwhatwhatawhatmidfieldwhatplayer!\"whatOnwhatawhatcontroversialwhatevening,whatASwhatofferswhatonewhatseeminglywhatundeniablewhatviewpoint:what\"SpanishwhatfootballwhatplayerswhatplayedwhatbetterwhatfootballwhatthanwhatthewhatEnglish.\"?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Republic of Ireland manager Brian Kerr admitted he was frustrated his side did not score more than one goal in their friendly win over Croatia.\r\nRobbie Keane took his Republic record to 24 with a first-half goal which proved enough for victory.\r\n\"But, given the conditions and the standard of the Croatian team, we should be very happy with the win.\" The Republic side kept a clean sheet for the eighth time in 11 matches and are unbeaten in 14 home games since Kerr succeeded Mick McCarthy.\r\nBrian Kerr wanted to try it out and it was good to see young Stephen Elliott getting a run-out.",
    "id": "N_216",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Republic",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "admitted",
        "adjective": "more",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Republic of Ireland manager Brian Kerr admitted he was frustrated his side did not score more than one goal in their friendly win over which location.\r\nRobbie Keane took his Republic record to 24 with a first-half goal which proved enough for victory.\r\n\"But, given the conditions and the standard of the which locationn team, we should be very happy with the win.\" The Republic side kept a clean sheet for the eighth time in 11 matches and are unbeaten in 14 home games since Kerr succeeded Mick McCarthy.\r\nBrian Kerr wanted to try it out and it was good to see young Stephen Elliott getting a run-out.?",
        "answer": "Croatia"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Chelsea's win at Fulham - confirming their position at the Premiership summit - proves that they now have everything in place to mount serious challenges on all fronts this season.\r\nThey have got strength in depth, great players, an outstanding manager in Jose Mourinho and finances no other club in the world can match.\r\nAs I said, winning the major honours is the hardest task of all, but in Mourinho they have a manager who will make it a whole lot easier to handle the anticipation and expectation that will come their way now.\r\nMourinho has won the biggest club prize of all, the Champions League, and that track record and confidence transmits itself to top players.\r\nMourinho doesn't simply talk a good game - he's won some very big games such as the Champions League final with Porto.\r\nI have said I believed Chelsea would win the league this season, even when Arsenal were flying at the start, and I have seen nothing to make me change me mind.\r\nOn a more serious note, it was a game that merely confirmed the importance of Sol Campbell to Arsenal.\r\nChelsea have no such problems at present, which is why I would still place my money on them to edge out Arsenal as champions this season.",
    "id": "N_217",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Chelsea's",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "win",
        "adjective": "serious",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Chelsea's win at Fulham - confirming their position at the Premiership summit - proves that who now have everything in place to mount serious challenges on all fronts this season.\r\nThey have got strength in depth, great players, an outstanding manager in Jose Mourinho and finances no other club in the world can match.\r\nAs I said, winning the major honours is the hardest task of all, but in Mourinho who have a manager who will make it a whole lot easier to handle the anticipation and expectation that will come their way now.\r\nMourinho has won the biggest club prize of all, the Champions League, and that track record and confidence transmits itself to top players.\r\nMourinho doesn't simply talk a good game - he's won some very big games such as the Champions League final with Porto.\r\nI have said I believed Chelsea would win the league this season, even when Arsenal were flying at the start, and I have seen nothing to make me change me mind.\r\nOn a more serious note, it was a game that merely confirmed the importance of Sol Campbell to Arsenal.\r\nChelsea have no such problems at present, which is why I would still place my money on them to edge out Arsenal as champions this season.?",
        "answer": "they"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Hearts of Oak set up an all Ghanaian Confederation Cup final with a 3-2 win over Cameroon's Cotonsport Garoua in Accra on Sunday.\r\nThe win for Hearts means they will play Asante Kotoko in the two-leg final, after the Kumasi team qualified from Group A on Saturday.\r\nHearts of Oak started the game needing a win to qualify for the final while Cotonsport only needed to avoid defeat to go through.",
    "id": "N_218",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Hearts",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "set",
        "adjective": "Ghanaian",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Hearts of Oak set up an all Ghanaian Confederation who final with a 3-2 win over Cameroon's Cotonsport Garoua in Accra on Sunday.\r\nThe win for Hearts means they will play Asante Kotoko in the two-leg final, after the Kumasi team qualified from Group A on Saturday.\r\nHearts of Oak started the game needing a win to qualify for the final while Cotonsport only needed to avoid defeat to go through.?",
        "answer": "Cup"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Charlton manager Alan Curbishley paid tribute to two-goal striker Jonatan Johansson after beating Norwich.",
    "id": "N_219",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Charlton",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "paid",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Charlton manager Alan who paid tribute to two-goal striker Jonatan Johansson after beating Norwich.?",
        "answer": "Curbishley"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Celtic's Neil Lennon admits Rangers could be considered \"slight favourites\" for the Old Firm CIS Cup clash, but insists his side can still win.\r\nLennon concedes Rangers are in good form at the moment, but they have failed to beat Celtic in their last seven meetings.",
    "id": "N_220",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Celtic's",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "admits",
        "adjective": "\"slight",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Middlesbrough boss Steve McClaren has praised the way his side have got to grips with European football after the 2-0 Uefa Cup win against Lazio.\r\nAnd in possession, we controlled it and looked threatening every time we went forward.\" Before the match, McClaren had said that a win over the Italian giants would put Boro firmly on the European footballing map.\r\n\"No matter what anybody says, Lazio are favourites to win this competition.\" Middlesbrough forward Boudewijn Zenden said he did not expect such a comfortable match after he scored both goals.\r\n\"I think we played quite well and it was a very good game, especially in the first half.\" The Holland international said Boro are confident of progressing in the competition after winning their first two group games.",
    "id": "N_221",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Middlesbrough",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "European",
        "adverb": "firmly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Middlesbrough boss Steve McClaren has praised the way his side have got to grips with European football after the 2-0 Uefa who win against Lazio.\r\nAnd in possession, we controlled it and looked threatening every time we went forward.\" Before the match, McClaren had said that a win over the Italian giants would put Boro firmly on the European footballing map.\r\n\"No matter what anybody says, Lazio are favourites to win this competition.\" Middlesbrough forward Boudewijn Zenden said he did not expect such a comfortable match after he scored both goals.\r\n\"I think we played quite well and it was a very good game, especially in the first half.\" The Holland international said Boro are confident of progressing in the competition after winning their first two group games.?",
        "answer": "Cup"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "We are pleased but move on to the next game.\" Igor Biscan was outstanding in midfield after replacing injured Xabi Alonso, and Benitez said: \"He played very well.\r\n\"It is important to have all the players ready and a good squad so you can play more games at a high level.\" Benitez added: \"It is all back in our own hands now, it was a great win for us and I was delighted with what I feel was the best Liverpool I have seen.\r\n\"As far as I am concerned it is important for Liverpool to win, it is not important in what country it is in.\" Benitez added: Benitez said: \"We had a problem before the start, it was decided that Xabi could not play more than 45 minutes.",
    "id": "N_222",
    "features": {
        "noun": "game.\"",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "pleased",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wewhoarewhopleasedwhobutwhomovewhoonwhotowhothewhonextwhogame.\"whoIgorwhoBiscanwhowaswhooutstandingwhoinwhomidfieldwhoafterwhoreplacingwhoinjuredwhoXabiwhoAlonso,whoandwhoBenitezwhosaid:who\"Hewhoplayedwhoverywhowell.\r\n\"Itwhoiswhoimportantwhotowhohavewhoallwhothewhoplayerswhoreadywhoandwhoawhogoodwhosquadwhosowhoyouwhocanwhoplaywhomorewhogameswhoatwhoawhohighwholevel.\"whoBenitezwhoadded:who\"Itwhoiswhoallwhobackwhoinwhoourwhoownwhohandswhonow,whoitwhowaswhoawhogreatwhowinwhoforwhouswhoandwhoIwhowaswhodelightedwhowithwhowhatwhoIwhofeelwhowaswhothewhobestwhoLiverpoolwhoIwhohavewhoseen.\r\n\"AswhofarwhoaswhoIwhoamwhoconcernedwhoitwhoiswhoimportantwhoforwhoLiverpoolwhotowhowin,whoitwhoiswhonotwhoimportantwhoinwhowhatwhocountrywhoitwhoiswhoin.\"whoBenitezwhoadded:whoBenitezwhosaid:who\"Wewhohadwhoawhoproblemwhobeforewhothewhostart,whoitwhowaswhodecidedwhothatwhoXabiwhocouldwhonotwhoplaywhomorewhothanwho45whominutes.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Phillips, Amankwaah, Coles, Hill, Fortune, Murray (Anyinsah 59), Doherty (Harley 45), Dinning, Bell, Lita (Cotterill 72), Gillespie.\r\nBevan, Oyedele, Ntimban-Zeh, Crooks, Puncheon, Kamara (Makofo 64), Chorley, Herve (McKoy 45), Tapp (Johnson 45), Mackie, Pacquette.",
    "id": "N_223",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Phillips,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "(Anyinsah",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Rovers took the lead on 59 minutes as Michael McIndoe's corner found Adriano Rigoglioso, whose stunning volley soared into the top right of the net.\r\nMawson, Travis, Mkandawire, James, Robinson, Daniel Williams, Stanley, Hyde (Pitman 105), Purdie (Mills 83), Brown, Stansfield (Green 102).",
    "id": "N_224",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Rovers",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "took",
        "adjective": "top",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Rovers took the lead on 59 minutes as Michael McIndoe's corner found Adriano Rigoglioso, whose stunning what soared into the top right of the net.\r\nMawson, Travis, Mkandawire, James, Robinson, Daniel Williams, Stanley, Hyde (Pitman 105), Purdie (Mills 83), Brown, Stansfield (Green 102).?",
        "answer": "volley"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Glenn Hoddle will be unveiled as the new Wolves manager on Tuesday.\r\nHoddle has been linked with a return to former club Southampton but Wolves have won the race for his services.",
    "id": "N_225",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Glenn",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Glenn who will be unveiled as the new Wolves manager on Tuesday.\r\nwho has been linked with a return to former club Southampton but Wolves have won the race for his services.?",
        "answer": "Hoddle"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arsene Wenger has pledged to keep faith with stand-in keeper Manuel Almunia for the crunch week which could define Arsenal's season.\r\nWenger said: \"You don't think I would take out one goalkeeper for just one game, do you?\r\nIt's just that I don't want to make this story bigger than it is.\" Wenger insists he has complete faith in the 27-year-old Spaniard, who was signed last summer from Celta Vigo as back-up to Jens Lehmann.\r\nJust because Lehmann doesn't play for two or three weeks, or longer or shorter, it doesn't mean I've lost faith in him.\"\r\n\"He has made a few mistakes but on form he deserves to be the first-team choice.\" With Arsenal hit by injuries and suspension, inexperienced midfield pair of Mathieu Flamini and Cesc Fabregas will line up against Rosenborg but Wenger is confident they will prove more than capable.\r\n\"If the team don't win I know I will be criticised, no matter how I play.\"",
    "id": "N_226",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arsene",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "stand-in",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "which"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former Liverpool manager Gerard Houllier has praised the work of his Anfield successor Rafael Benitez.\r\nHoullier said: \"If a good club comes up at the right time then yes, I am ready to come back.\r\nHoullier has been impressed with the quality in the Premiership after watching as a pundit - particularly with Jose Mourinho's work at leaders Chelsea.\r\n\"Jose had results before he came to Chelsea and I think he will have an impact in the Premiership because he manages his team very cleverly.\" And Houllier, away from his brief at Liverpool, has been hugely impressed with the Premiership.",
    "id": "N_227",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Liverpool",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Former",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former Liverpool manager Gerard who has praised the work of his Anfield successor Rafael Benitez.\r\nwho said: \"If a good club comes up at the right time then yes, I am ready to come back.\r\nwho has been impressed with the quality in the Premiership after watching as a pundit - particularly with Jose Mourinho's work at leaders Chelsea.\r\n\"Jose had results before he came to Chelsea and I think he will have an impact in the Premiership because he manages his team very cleverly.\" And who, away from his brief at Liverpool, has been hugely impressed with the Premiership.?",
        "answer": "Houllier"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Once we got the third goal it should have been four or five but we nearly paid for it in the end.\" McClaren also praised winger Stewart Downing and strikers Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink and Mark Viduka, who both ended barren runs in front of goal.",
    "id": "N_228",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"Once",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "got",
        "adjective": "third",
        "adverb": "nearly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Oncewhowewhogotwhothewhothirdwhogoalwhoitwhoshouldwhohavewhobeenwhofourwhoorwhofivewhobutwhowewhonearlywhopaidwhoforwhoitwhoinwhothewhoend.\"whoMcClarenwhoalsowhopraisedwhowingerwhoStewartwhoDowningwhoandwhostrikerswhoJimmywhoFloydwhoHasselbainkwhoandwhoMarkwhoViduka,whowhowhobothwhoendedwhobarrenwhorunswhoinwhofrontwhoofwhogoal.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Aston Villa's Thomas Hitzlsperger is waiting to learn the future of manager David O'Leary before committing himself to a new contract with the club.",
    "id": "N_229",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Aston",
        "pronoun": "himself",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Aston Villa's Thomas who is waiting to learn the future of manager David O'Leary before committing himself to a new contract with the club.?",
        "answer": "Hitzlsperger"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Chelsea boss Jose Mourinho will not face any Football Association action over the comments he made after their Carling Cup tie with Manchester United.\r\nMourinho intimated that United boss Sir Alex Ferguson influenced referee Neale Barry after the duo walked down the tunnel together at half-time.\r\n\"I see one referee in the first half and another in the second,\" said Mourinho.\r\nHe should only have had his two assistants and the fourth official with him, but there was also someone else.\" Referees chief Keith Hackett believes Mourinho should retract his comments about Ferguson and Barry as he believes the Blues boss has questioned their integrity.",
    "id": "N_230",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Chelsea",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "face",
        "adjective": "Carling",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Chelsea boss Jose Mourinho will not face any Football Association action over the comments he made after their Carling who tie with Manchester United.\r\nMourinho intimated that United boss Sir Alex Ferguson influenced referee Neale Barry after the duo walked down the tunnel together at half-time.\r\n\"I see one referee in the first half and another in the second,\" said Mourinho.\r\nHe should only have had his two assistants and the fourth official with him, but there was also someone else.\" Referees chief Keith Hackett believes Mourinho should retract his comments about Ferguson and Barry as he believes the Blues boss has questioned their integrity.?",
        "answer": "Cup"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The ex-England coach has been given a six-month contract to succeed Dave Jones, who was sacked after the club's poor start to the season.\r\nHe has a six-month contract so we can test each other out and see if it works.\" Hoddle, who will work alongside Stuart Gray, has been out of the game since he was sacked by Spurs in 2003.\r\nWe've worked together at Southampton and I'm delighted to be back with him.\" Wolves chief executive Jez Moxey defended the decision to give Hoddle a short-term contract.\r\nThe 47-year-old later returned to management with Southampton, where he again succeeded Jones - as he has now done at Wolves.",
    "id": "N_231",
    "features": {
        "noun": "coach",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "ex-England",
        "adverb": "alongside"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "who"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Portsmouth chairman Milan Mandaric said he was \"disappointed\" by the news and claimed Redknapp had been in talks with Southampton for \"some time\".\r\nSouthampton chairman Rupert Lowe was desperate to give former academy director Wigley, who replaced Paul Sturrock just two games into the season, every chance to succeed at St Mary's.",
    "id": "N_232",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Portsmouth",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "desperate",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "PortsmouthwhochairmanwhoMilanwhoMandaricwhosaidwhohewhowaswho\"disappointed\"whobywhothewhonewswhoandwhoclaimedwhoRedknappwhohadwhobeenwhoinwhotalkswhowithwhoSouthamptonwhoforwho\"somewhotime\".\r\nSouthamptonwhochairmanwhoRupertwhoLowewhowaswhodesperatewhotowhogivewhoformerwhoacademywhodirectorwhoWigley,whowhowhoreplacedwhoPaulwhoSturrockwhojustwhotwowhogameswhointowhothewhoseason,whoeverywhochancewhotowhosucceedwhoatwhoStwhoMary's.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Liverpool fans claimed the trouble was sparked by chants about the Hillsborough disaster, where 96 supporters were crushed to death in April 1989.\r\nLiverpool have been charged with one breach for failing to prevent their fans conducting themselves in threatening and/or violent and/or provocative behaviour.",
    "id": "N_233",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Liverpool",
        "pronoun": "themselves",
        "verb": "claimed",
        "adjective": "and/or",
        "adverb": "where"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "supporters"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arsene Wenger has stepped up his feud with Sir Alex Ferguson by claiming the Manchester United manager is guilty of bringing football into disrepute.\r\nThe pair's long-running row was put back in the headlines on Saturday when Ferguson said his Arsenal counterpart was \"a disgrace\".\r\nWenger initially refused to bite back, saying only: \"I will never answer any questions any more about this man.\" But now he claims Ferguson should be punished by the Football Association.\r\nThe latest twist in the Ferguson-Wenger saga came on Saturday when the United boss, in an interview with The Independent newspaper, discussed the events after the game between the two sides in October.\r\n\"In the tunnel Wenger was criticising my players, calling them cheats, so I told him to leave them alone and behave himself,\" Ferguson said on Saturday.\r\n\"He ran at me with hands raised saying 'what do you want to do about it?' \"To not apologise for the behaviour of the players to another manager is unthinkable.\r\nThose allegations were put to Wenger after Saturday's game at Bolton, which Arsenal lost to slip 10 points behind Chelsea in the title race.\r\nno matter what people say.\" Reminded that Ferguson called him \"a disgrace\", Wenger added: \"I don't respond to anything.\r\nDuring that stormy game in October, United striker Ruud van Nistelrooy caught Arsenal's Ashley Cole with one particularly strong tackle.",
    "id": "N_234",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arsene",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "guilty",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Arsene Wenger has stepped up his feud with Sir Alex Ferguson by claiming the Manchester United what is guilty of bringing football into disrepute.\r\nThe pair's long-running row was put back in the headlines on Saturday when Ferguson said his Arsenal counterpart was \"a disgrace\".\r\nWenger initially refused to bite back, saying only: \"I will never answer any questions any more about this man.\" But now he claims Ferguson should be punished by the Football Association.\r\nThe latest twist in the Ferguson-Wenger saga came on Saturday when the United boss, in an interview with The Independent newspaper, discussed the events after the game between the two sides in October.\r\n\"In the tunnel Wenger was criticising my players, calling them cheats, so I told him to leave them alone and behave himself,\" Ferguson said on Saturday.\r\n\"He ran at me with hands raised saying 'what do you want to do about it?' \"To not apologise for the behaviour of the players to another what is unthinkable.\r\nThose allegations were put to Wenger after Saturday's game at Bolton, which Arsenal lost to slip 10 points behind Chelsea in the title race.\r\nno matter what people say.\" Reminded that Ferguson called him \"a disgrace\", Wenger added: \"I don't respond to anything.\r\nDuring that stormy game in October, United striker Ruud van Nistelrooy caught Arsenal's Ashley Cole with one particularly strong tackle.?",
        "answer": "manager"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Reds beat Olympiakos 3-1 with a late Steven Gerrard strike and Benitez said: \"It was a really great night.\r\nFor Liverpool, this result is very, very important.\" Benitez hailed Gerrard for his match-winning strike four minutes from time and also the Anfield crowd for sticking by their side after they had fallen a goal behind at the interval.\r\n\"I want to say thank-you to the supporters, they were magnificent to help us achieve this result.\" Gerrard admitted he thought they were going out of the Champions League after trailing 1-0 at half-time.",
    "id": "N_235",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Reds",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "said:",
        "adjective": "3-1",
        "adverb": "really"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The favourites are Chelsea and Barcelona, and Real Madrid, the two Milan sides, Juventus and Bayern Munich are among the 16 still in the hat.\r\nBarcelona, Bayern Munich, Porto, Real Madrid, Werder Bremen\r\nBarcelona, Bayern Munich, PSV Eindhoven, Real Madrid, Werder Bremen.",
    "id": "N_236",
    "features": {
        "noun": "favourites",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manchester United manager Sir Alex Ferguson said he has no regrets after his second-string side lost 3-0 away at Fenerbahce in the Champions League.\r\nFerguson said: \"The good thing about being manager is that you are in control of which team to pick.\r\nThey will remember it and next time they come they will be better.\" Ferguson admitted his side were well-beaten by the Turks, a result which meant they finished second in Group D behind Lyon.",
    "id": "N_237",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manchester",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "second-string",
        "adverb": "away"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Manchester United manager Sir Alex Ferguson said he has no regrets after his second-string what lost 3-0 away at Fenerbahce in the Champions League.\r\nFerguson said: \"The good thing about being manager is that you are in control of which team to pick.\r\nThey will remember it and next time they come they will be better.\" Ferguson admitted his what were well-beaten by the Turks, a result which meant they finished second in Group D behind Lyon.?",
        "answer": "side"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "David Beckham expressed his relief at Real Madrid's passage to the Champions League knockout phase.",
    "id": "N_238",
    "features": {
        "noun": "David",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "expressed",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "David who expressed his relief at Real Madrid's passage to the Champions League knockout phase.?",
        "answer": "Beckham"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Exeter had chances of their own, Sean Devine twice volleying wide and Andrew Taylor forcing Tim Howard to save.\r\nScholes played a lovely pass in to Ronaldo on the left-hand side of the six-yard box and the Portuguese winger slid the ball between the legs of Jones to open the scoring.\r\nUnited sensed a chance to finish the tie as a contest early on and Ronaldo blazed over before Jones saved well from Scholes and then Rooney.\r\nIn stoppage time Exeter created their best chance as Alex Jeannin swung in a cross from the left that Devine managed to flick goalwards, but the ball flew wide of Howard's goal.\r\nMoments later Devine had the chance to make himself a hero, but he could only volley Jeannin's brilliant cross wide of Howard's goal after being left unmarked six yards out.",
    "id": "N_239",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Exeter",
        "pronoun": "himself",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "own,",
        "adverb": "twice"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Exeterwhohadwhochanceswhoofwhotheirwhoown,whoSeanwhoDevinewhotwicewhovolleyingwhowidewhoandwhoAndrewwhoTaylorwhoforcingwhoTimwhoHowardwhotowhosave.\r\nScholeswhoplayedwhoawholovelywhopasswhoinwhotowhoRonaldowhoonwhothewholeft-handwhosidewhoofwhothewhosix-yardwhoboxwhoandwhothewhoPortuguesewhowingerwhoslidwhothewhoballwhobetweenwhothewholegswhoofwhoJoneswhotowhoopenwhothewhoscoring.\r\nUnitedwhosensedwhoawhochancewhotowhofinishwhothewhotiewhoaswhoawhocontestwhoearlywhoonwhoandwhoRonaldowhoblazedwhooverwhobeforewhoJoneswhosavedwhowellwhofromwhoScholeswhoandwhothenwhoRooney.\r\nInwhostoppagewhotimewhoExeterwhocreatedwhotheirwhobestwhochancewhoaswhoAlexwhoJeanninwhoswungwhoinwhoawhocrosswhofromwhothewholeftwhothatwhoDevinewhomanagedwhotowhoflickwhogoalwards,whobutwhothewhoballwhoflewwhowidewhoofwhoHoward'swhogoal.\r\nMomentswholaterwhoDevinewhohadwhothewhochancewhotowhomakewhohimselfwhoawhohero,whobutwhohewhocouldwhoonlywhovolleywhoJeannin'swhobrilliantwhocrosswhowidewhoofwhoHoward'swhogoalwhoafterwhobeingwholeftwhounmarkedwhosixwhoyardswhoout.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Hamm, 32, who officially retired after this year's Athens Olympics, took to the field for the last time to help the US claim a 5-0 win over Mexico.\r\nHamm will now embark on a new life with husband, Chicago Cubs shortstop Nomar Garciaparra, who was in the stands to watch her final game.",
    "id": "N_240",
    "features": {
        "noun": "year's",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "retired",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "officially"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Hamm, 32, who officially retired after this year's Athens Olympics, took to the field for the last time to help the US claim a 5-0 win over which location.\r\nHamm will now embark on a new life with husband, Chicago Cubs shortstop Nomar Garciaparra, who was in the stands to watch her final game.?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arsenal boss Arsene Wenger says he has no plans to sign a new goalkeeper during the January transfer window.\r\nWenger has brought in Manuel Almunia for the last three games for the out-of-form Jens Lehmann - but the Spaniard himself has been prone to mistakes.",
    "id": "N_241",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arsenal",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Arsenal boss Arsene Wenger says who has no plans to sign a new goalkeeper during twho January transfer window.\r\nWenger has brought in Manuel Almunia for twho last three games for twho out-of-form Jens Lehmann - but twho Spaniard himself has been prone to mistakes.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Liverpool chief executive Rick Parry insists the club will never sell Steven Gerrard amid reports Chelsea will renew their bid to lure him from Anfield.\r\nReds manager Rafael Benitez believes Gerrard can win everything he wants to without moving clubs.\r\n\"Steven can win all he wants with us and we need him.\r\n\"But if we want to win more games, important games, we need Steven in the team.",
    "id": "N_242",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Liverpool",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "insists",
        "adjective": "chief",
        "adverb": "never"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Liverpool chief executive Rick Parry insists the club will never sell Steven Gerrard amid reports who will renew their bid to lure him from Anfield.\r\nReds manager Rafael Benitez believes Gerrard can win everything he wants to without moving clubs.\r\n\"Steven can win all he wants with us and we need him.\r\n\"But if we want to win more games, important games, we need Steven in the team.?",
        "answer": "Chelsea"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Joint assistant boss Stuart Pearce has admitted he would like to succeed Kevin Keegan as manager at Manchester City.\r\n\"I will certainly be applying for it, although whether the board deem me good enough to take it, I do not know.\" Pearce initially joined City as a player under Keegan in 2001 before becoming part of the coaching staff.",
    "id": "N_243",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Joint",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "good",
        "adverb": "certainly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Joint assistant boss Stuart Pearce has admitted who would like to succeed Kevin Keegan as manager at Mancwhoster City.\r\n\"I will certainly be applying for it, although wwhotwhor twho board deem me good enough to take it, I do not know.\" Pearce initially joined City as a player under Keegan in 2001 before becoming part of twho coaching staff.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Spectators were evacuated from Real Madrid's Bernabeu stadium on Sunday following a bomb scare during the game between the hosts and Real Sociedad.\r\nThe Bernabeu was targeted by ETA on 1 May, 2002, when Madrid were about to play FC Barcelona in a Champions League semi-final.",
    "id": "N_244",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Spectators",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "Real",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Thierry Henry produced a sublime strike to put Arsenal ahead but John Terry levelled with a powerful header.\r\nHenry's quickly-taken free-kick put Arsenal back in front but Eidur Gudjohnsen equalised with a header from William Gallas' knockback.\r\nGunners keeper Manuel Almunia, who got the nod ahead of Jens Lehmann, did well to save a well-struck Frank Lampard shot.\r\nAlmost immediately, Henry went close and Chelsea gathered the loose ball before going straight up the other end where Gudjohnsen fluffed an effort.\r\nAlmunia, Lauren, Toure, Campbell, Cole, Pires, Flamini, Fabregas, Reyes (Clichy 82), Bergkamp (Van Persie 82), Henry.\r\nCech, Paulo Ferreira, Ricardo Carvalho (Drogba 45), Terry, Gallas, Duff, Tiago (Bridge 45), Makelele, Lampard, Robben, Gudjohnsen (Parker 77).",
    "id": "N_245",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Thierry",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "produced",
        "adjective": "sublime",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThierrywhoHenrywhoproducedwhoawhosublimewhostrikewhotowhoputwhoArsenalwhoaheadwhobutwhoJohnwhoTerrywholevelledwhowithwhoawhopowerfulwhoheader.\r\nHenry'swhoquickly-takenwhofree-kickwhoputwhoArsenalwhobackwhoinwhofrontwhobutwhoEidurwhoGudjohnsenwhoequalisedwhowithwhoawhoheaderwhofromwhoWilliamwhoGallas'whoknockback.\r\nGunnerswhokeeperwhoManuelwhoAlmunia,whowhowhogotwhothewhonodwhoaheadwhoofwhoJenswhoLehmann,whodidwhowellwhotowhosavewhoawhowell-struckwhoFrankwhoLampardwhoshot.\r\nAlmostwhoimmediately,whoHenrywhowentwhoclosewhoandwhoChelseawhogatheredwhothewholoosewhoballwhobeforewhogoingwhostraightwhoupwhothewhootherwhoendwhowherewhoGudjohnsenwhofluffedwhoanwhoeffort.\r\nAlmunia,whoLauren,whoToure,whoCampbell,whoCole,whoPires,whoFlamini,whoFabregas,whoReyeswho(Clichywho82),whoBergkampwho(VanwhoPersiewho82),whoHenry.\r\nCech,whoPaulowhoFerreira,whoRicardowhoCarvalhowho(Drogbawho45),whoTerry,whoGallas,whoDuff,whoTiagowho(Bridgewho45),whoMakelele,whoLampard,whoRobben,whoGudjohnsenwho(Parkerwho77).?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Real Sociedad president Jose Luis Astiazaran said: \"We thought the best thing was to play the time remaining.\"\r\nThe two clubs met the Spanish FA on Monday and Astiazaran added: \"We thought about giving the game as concluded but after talking with the FA we decided there was no precedent for that and the best thing was to play the time that was remaining.\" Real Madrid director of sport Emilio Butragueno praised the spectators inside the ground for their conduct.",
    "id": "N_246",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sociedad",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "thought",
        "adjective": "Real",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Real Sociedad president Jose Luis Astiazaran said: \"We thought the best what was to play the time remaining.\"\r\nThe two clubs met the Spanish FA on Monday and Astiazaran added: \"We thought about giving the game as concluded but after talking with the FA we decided there was no precedent for that and the best what was to play the time that was remaining.\" Real Madrid director of sport Emilio Butragueno praised the spectators inside the ground for their conduct.?",
        "answer": "thing"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Referee Graham Poll said he applied the laws of the game in allowing Arsenal striker Thierry Henry's free-kick in Sunday's 2-2 draw with Chelsea.\r\nKeeper Petr Cech was organising his defensive wall when Henry's quick free-kick flew in, which angered Chelsea.\r\nHenry told BBC Radio Five Live: \"The ref asked me if I wanted 10 yards or if I wanted to take it straight away and I said that I wanted to take it straight away.\r\n\"Referees have been told to ask the player 'do you want to take the quick free-kick?' or 'do you want me to get the wall back 9.15 metres?' \"If they say 'quick', the referee tends to move away and allow the kick.\" Don was head of the referees for the Premier League and revealed all clubs were informed of free-kick options.",
    "id": "N_247",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Referee",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "2-2",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Referee Graham Poll said who applied twho laws of twho game in allowing Arsenal striker Thierry Henry's free-kick in Sunday's 2-2 draw with Cwholsea.\r\nKeeper Petr Cech was organising his defensive wall wwhon Henry's quick free-kick flew in, which angered Cwholsea.\r\nHenry told BBC Radio Five Live: \"Twho ref asked me if I wanted 10 yards or if I wanted to take it straight away and I said that I wanted to take it straight away.\r\n\"Referees have been told to ask twho player 'do you want to take twho quick free-kick?' or 'do you want me to get twho wall back 9.15 metres?' \"If twhoy say 'quick', twho referee tends to move away and allow twho kick.\" Don was whoad of twho referees for twho Premier League and revealed all clubs were informed of free-kick options.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Manchester United striker Ole Gunnar Solskjaer said he hoped to return next season following a career-threatening injury to his right knee.",
    "id": "N_248",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Manchester",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Mancwhoster United striker Ole Gunnar Solskjaer said who hoped to return next season following a career-threatening injury to his right knee.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He was once threatened with the sack by City boss Kevin Keegan but has since responded with impressive performances, prompting interest from other clubs.\r\n\"I definitely want to stay at City because I have really improved as a player here.\" Newcastle boss Graeme Souness is said to have been impressed enough by Dunne's turnaround in form to be ready to make a bid for the big stopper in the January transfer window.",
    "id": "N_249",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sack",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "impressive",
        "adverb": "once"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "HewhowaswhooncewhothreatenedwhowithwhothewhosackwhobywhoCitywhobosswhoKevinwhoKeeganwhobutwhohaswhosincewhorespondedwhowithwhoimpressivewhoperformances,whopromptingwhointerestwhofromwhootherwhoclubs.\r\n\"IwhodefinitelywhowantwhotowhostaywhoatwhoCitywhobecausewhoIwhohavewhoreallywhoimprovedwhoaswhoawhoplayerwhohere.\"whoNewcastlewhobosswhoGraemewhoSounesswhoiswhosaidwhotowhohavewhobeenwhoimpressedwhoenoughwhobywhoDunne'swhoturnaroundwhoinwhoformwhotowhobewhoreadywhotowhomakewhoawhobidwhoforwhothewhobigwhostopperwhoinwhothewhoJanuarywhotransferwhowindow.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ken Bates has completed his takeover of Leeds United.\r\nFor the past year it has been a matter of firefighting - now we can start running the club again.\" Outgoing Leeds chairman Gerald Krasner said: \"This deal ensures the medium to long term survival of the club and I believe Mr Bates' proposals are totally for the benefit of the club.\r\n\"When we took over Leeds United in March 2004, the club had a debt of \u00c2\u00a3103m, since that date, my board has succeeded in reducing the debt to under \u00c2\u00a325m.\r\nOn Leeds' new-look board it is understood that Lorimer will be joined by former Chelsea finance director Yvonne Todd and Bates' lawyer Mark Taylor.\r\nI am not stretching figures, we don't discuss internal arrangements.\" Bates stepped down as Chelsea chairman in March last year following Roman Abramovich's \u00c2\u00a3140m takeover at Stamford Bridge.",
    "id": "N_250",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ken",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "past",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ken who has completed his takeover of Leeds United.\r\nFor the past year it has been a matter of firefighting - now we can start running the club again.\" Outgoing Leeds chairman Gerald Krasner said: \"This deal ensures the medium to long term survival of the club and I believe Mr who' proposals are totally for the benefit of the club.\r\n\"When we took over Leeds United in March 2004, the club had a debt of \u00c2\u00a3103m, since that date, my board has succeeded in reducing the debt to under \u00c2\u00a325m.\r\nOn Leeds' new-look board it is understood that Lorimer will be joined by former Chelsea finance director Yvonne Todd and who' lawyer Mark Taylor.\r\nI am not stretching figures, we don't discuss internal arrangements.\" who stepped down as Chelsea chairman in March last year following Roman Abramovich's \u00c2\u00a3140m takeover at Stamford Bridge.?",
        "answer": "Bates"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"In fairness, it's a fantastic strike from the Fulham player.\" The result leaves Ferguson's side fourth in the league on 31 points - four points behind Arsenal and a further five back from Chelsea.",
    "id": "N_251",
    "features": {
        "noun": "fairness,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "it's",
        "adjective": "\"In",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"In fairness, who's a fantastic strike from the Fulham player.\" The result leaves Ferguson's side fourth in the league on 31 points - four points behind Arsenal and a further five back from Chelsea.?",
        "answer": "it"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Celtic's Henri Camara and Nacho Novo of Rangers have both been suspended for offences missed by the referee in a recent Old Firm game.\r\nThe additional bans come into effect from 28 December meaning Camara will also be unavailable for the home game against Livingston while Novo will miss the meetings with Dundee United and Dunfermline.\r\nAn SFA spokesman said: \"They have seven days to appeal but with matches coming along at the weekend they would need to do so before Friday.",
    "id": "N_252",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Celtic's",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "recent",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Celtic'swhoHenriwhoCamarawhoandwhoNachowhoNovowhoofwhoRangerswhohavewhobothwhobeenwhosuspendedwhoforwhooffenceswhomissedwhobywhothewhorefereewhoinwhoawhorecentwhoOldwhoFirmwhogame.\r\nThewhoadditionalwhobanswhocomewhointowhoeffectwhofromwho28whoDecemberwhomeaningwhoCamarawhowillwhoalsowhobewhounavailablewhoforwhothewhohomewhogamewhoagainstwhoLivingstonwhowhilewhoNovowhowillwhomisswhothewhomeetingswhowithwhoDundeewhoUnitedwhoandwhoDunfermline.\r\nAnwhoSFAwhospokesmanwhosaid:who\"TheywhohavewhosevenwhodayswhotowhoappealwhobutwhowithwhomatcheswhocomingwhoalongwhoatwhothewhoweekendwhotheywhowouldwhoneedwhotowhodowhosowhobeforewhoFriday.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But Wardle added: \"There's been no bids for Nicolas Anelka.\r\nNo-one has come to me and said I would like to buy Nicolas Anelka.\r\n\"If a bid comes in for Nicolas Anelka I will speak to the board and then speak to Kevin Keegan.\r\n\"He was an academy kid here, he's just signed a new four-year deal, I don't think he'd do that unless he wanted to play for Manchester City Football Club.\" City recently announced debts of \u00c2\u00a362m, but Wardle confirmed they would try and find funds to bring in players in the January transfer window.",
    "id": "N_253",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wardle",
        "pronoun": "me",
        "verb": "added:",
        "adjective": "academy",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"In fairness, it's a fantastic strike from the Fulham player.\" The result leaves Ferguson's side fourth in the league on 31 points - four points behind Arsenal and a further five back from Chelsea.",
    "id": "N_254",
    "features": {
        "noun": "fairness,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "it's",
        "adjective": "\"In",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"In fairness, who's a fantastic strike from the Fulham player.\" The result leaves Ferguson's side fourth in the league on 31 points - four points behind Arsenal and a further five back from Chelsea.?",
        "answer": "it"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Everton defender David Weir has played down talk of European football, despite his team lying in second place in the Premiership after beating Liverpool.",
    "id": "N_255",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Everton",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "European",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Everton defender David who has played down talk of European football, despite his team lying in second place in the Premiership after beating Liverpool.?",
        "answer": "Weir"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Spain's Football Federation has initiated disciplinary action against national coach Luis Aragones over racist comments about Thierry Henry.\r\nAragones insisted the comments, made to Henry's Arsenal club-mate Jose Antonio Reyes, were meant to motivate the player, and were not intended to be offensive.",
    "id": "N_256",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Spain's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "disciplinary",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Spain's Football who has initiated disciplinary action against national coach Luis Aragones over racist comments about Thierry Henry.\r\nAragones insisted the comments, made to Henry's Arsenal club-mate Jose Antonio Reyes, were meant to motivate the player, and were not intended to be offensive.?",
        "answer": "Federation"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Spain's Football Federation has initiated disciplinary action against national coach Luis Aragones over racist comments about Thierry Henry.\r\nAragones insisted the comments, made to Henry's Arsenal club-mate Jose Antonio Reyes, were meant to motivate the player, and were not intended to be offensive.",
    "id": "N_257",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Spain's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "disciplinary",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Spain's Football who has initiated disciplinary action against national coach Luis Aragones over racist comments about Thierry Henry.\r\nAragones insisted the comments, made to Henry's Arsenal club-mate Jose Antonio Reyes, were meant to motivate the player, and were not intended to be offensive.?",
        "answer": "Federation"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Liverpool manager Rafael Benitez has refused to point the finger of blame at goalkeeper Jerzy Dudek after Portsmouth claimed a draw at Anfield.\r\nBenitez said: \"It was difficult for Jerzy.",
    "id": "N_258",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Liverpool",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "goalkeeper",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Liverpool manager Rafael Benitez has refused to point the finger of blame at goalkeeper Jerzy Dudek after who claimed a draw at Anfield.\r\nBenitez said: \"It was difficult for Jerzy.?",
        "answer": "Portsmouth"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newcastle have fined their Welsh striker Craig Bellamy two weeks' wages - about \u00c2\u00a380,000 - following his row with manager Graeme Souness.\r\n\"No individual is, be it the chairman, the manager or a player.\" Souness dropped Bellamy for Sunday's game against Arsenal, claiming the Welshman had feigned injury after being asked to play out of position.\r\nBellamy's claim that Souness had lied about the background to the bust-up was strongly denied by Shepherd, who accused the striker of \"cheating\" the club.\r\n\"At that meeting Bellamy admitted to Graeme and I that he had told the players that he was going to \"fake\" an injury in training and walk off.\r\n\"In my book this is cheating on the club, the supporters, the manager and his own team-mates.",
    "id": "N_259",
    "features": {
        "noun": "striker",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "Welsh",
        "adverb": "Newcastle"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who have fined their Welsh striker Craig Bellamy two weeks' wages - about \u00c2\u00a380,000 - following his row with manager Graeme Souness.\r\n\"No individual is, be it the chairman, the manager or a player.\" Souness dropped Bellamy for Sunday's game against Arsenal, claiming the Welshman had feigned injury after being asked to play out of position.\r\nBellamy's claim that Souness had lied about the background to the bust-up was strongly denied by Shepherd, who accused the striker of \"cheating\" the club.\r\n\"At that meeting Bellamy admitted to Graeme and I that he had told the players that he was going to \"fake\" an injury in training and walk off.\r\n\"In my book this is cheating on the club, the supporters, the manager and his own team-mates.?",
        "answer": "Newcastle"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Steve McClaren wants his Middlesbrough team to win their Uefa Cup group by beating Partizan Belgrade.",
    "id": "N_260",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Steve",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "wants",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Steve who wants his Middlesbrough team to win their Uefa Cup group by beating Partizan Belgrade.?",
        "answer": "McClaren"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"He is a left-sided player, a position we have been looking at and he showed so much talent in his time here that we decided to take him.",
    "id": "N_261",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"He",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "left-sided",
        "adverb": "so"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Hewhoiswhoawholeft-sidedwhoplayer,whoawhopositionwhowewhohavewhobeenwholookingwhoatwhoandwhohewhoshowedwhosowhomuchwhotalentwhoinwhohiswhotimewhoherewhothatwhowewhodecidedwhotowhotakewhohim.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "McLeish told BBC Radio Five Live: \"We were in pole position to get through to the next stage but we blew it, we absolutely blew it.\r\n\"I'm very disappointed because we didn't give ourselves a chance, losing the first goal from our own corner.",
    "id": "N_262",
    "features": {
        "noun": "BBC",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "McLeish",
        "adverb": "absolutely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "McLeishwhotoldwhoBBCwhoRadiowhoFivewhoLive:who\"Wewhowerewhoinwhopolewhopositionwhotowhogetwhothroughwhotowhothewhonextwhostagewhobutwhowewhoblewwhoit,whowewhoabsolutelywhoblewwhoit.\r\n\"I'mwhoverywhodisappointedwhobecausewhowewhodidn'twhogivewhoourselveswhoawhochance,wholosingwhothewhofirstwhogoalwhofromwhoourwhoownwhocorner.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Aston Villa boss David O'Leary signed a three-and-a-half year contract extension on Thursday, securing his future at the club until summer 2008.\r\nO'Leary's future was in question, but Villa chairman Doug Ellis said he was happy to secure the deal.\r\n\"It was important to me Roy and Steve, an integral part of my team, should stay for the same time,\" O'Leary said on Thursday ahead of signing his new deal.",
    "id": "N_263",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Aston",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "signed",
        "adjective": "three-and-a-half",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Aston Villa boss David who signed a three-and-a-half year contract extension on Thursday, securing his future at the club until summer 2008.\r\nwho's future was in question, but Villa chairman Doug Ellis said he was happy to secure the deal.\r\n\"It was important to me Roy and Steve, an integral part of my team, should stay for the same time,\" who said on Thursday ahead of signing his new deal.?",
        "answer": "O'Leary"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jesper Gronkjaer has agreed a move to Atletico Madrid from Birmingham City.\r\nGronkjaer has been targeted by Blues fans and was sarcastically applauded when taken off against Everton last month.",
    "id": "N_264",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jesper",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "sarcastically"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jesper who has agreed a move to Atletico Madrid from Birmingham City.\r\nwho has been targeted by Blues fans and was sarcastically applauded when taken off against Everton last month.?",
        "answer": "Gronkjaer"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "I'm under contract to Real and they will make any decisions.\" The fee could put Liverpool off a prospective deal but Real are keen to net the cash as they are reported to be preparing a massive summer bid for Inter Milan striker Adriano.",
    "id": "N_265",
    "features": {
        "noun": "I'm",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "Real",
        "adjective": "prospective",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "I'mwhounderwhocontractwhotowhoRealwhoandwhotheywhowillwhomakewhoanywhodecisions.\"whoThewhofeewhocouldwhoputwhoLiverpoolwhooffwhoawhoprospectivewhodealwhobutwhoRealwhoarewhokeenwhotowhonetwhothewhocashwhoaswhotheywhoarewhoreportedwhotowhobewhopreparingwhoawhomassivewhosummerwhobidwhoforwhoInterwhoMilanwhostrikerwhoAdriano.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Hearts manager John Robertson hopes a place in the knock-out stages of the Uefa Cup could help keep some of his out-of-contract players at the club.\r\n\"It's very much the player's prerogative but the fact that we've been playing European football for the last three or four years is obviously an incentive,\" added Robertson.\r\n\"But we want players who want to play for the football club, who are committed and a run in Europe always helps a little bit.\" With the game being played at Murrayfield instead of Tynecastle because of Uefa regulations, Robertson sees both positive and negative aspects to the change of venue.",
    "id": "N_266",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Hearts",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "hopes",
        "adjective": "knock-out",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Hearts manager John Robertson hopes a what in the knock-out stages of the Uefa Cup could help keep some of his out-of-contract players at the club.\r\n\"It's very much the player's prerogative but the fact that we've been playing European football for the last three or four years is obviously an incentive,\" added Robertson.\r\n\"But we want players who want to play for the football club, who are committed and a run in Europe always helps a little bit.\" With the game being played at Murrayfield instead of Tynecastle because of Uefa regulations, Robertson sees both positive and negative aspects to the change of venue.?",
        "answer": "place"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But a delightful touch by Robin van Persie gave Henry a sight of goal, although the angle was too tight for his shot to trouble Jamie Ashdown.\r\nAshdown caused hearts to flutter on 28 minutes when he missed his punch at a corner and Kolo Toure headed just wide and, as Arsenal began to press, Van Persie blasted over a good opportunity after Henry had set him up.\r\nHenry took a quick return pass from Vieira but Ashdown was out quickly to block, and there were some anxious seconds for Pompey as the ball ran loose before Matthew Taylor cleared.\r\nReferee Howard Webb played a good advantage to allow Steve Stone to send Gary O'Neil away but, having shrugged off Toure, the Pompey midfielder planted his shot wide from 10 yards.\r\nFuller was given the best chance of the match so far on 48 minutes when Patrik Berger's break and slipped pass played him clear.\r\nAlmunia, Lauren, Toure, Campbell, Cole, Pires, Flamini, Vieira, Clichy, Van Persie (Bergkamp 68), Henry.",
    "id": "N_267",
    "features": {
        "noun": "touch",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "gave",
        "adjective": "delightful",
        "adverb": "too"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Patrick Kluivert's close-range finish put Newcastle ahead after 31 minutes, but they were pegged back as Bramble headed in Steven Gerrard's corner.\r\nNeil Mellor gave Liverpool the lead before half-time from Milan Baros' pass before the Czech added a third after rounding Shay Given on the hour.\r\nAnd Liverpool were ahead after 37 minutes when Baros slid a perfect pass into Mellor's path for the youngster to slip a slide-rule finish into Given's bottom corner.\r\nAny hopes of a Newcastle recovery looked to be snuffed out on the hour when a brilliant turn and pass by Harry Kewell set Baros free and he rounded Given to score.\r\nGiven, Andrew O'Brien, Elliott, Bramble, Bernard, Bowyer, Dyer (Ambrose 80), Jenas, Milner (N'Zogbia 72), Kluivert (Robert 58), Ameobi.",
    "id": "N_268",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Patrick",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "put",
        "adjective": "close-range",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "PatrickwhatKluivert'swhatclose-rangewhatfinishwhatputwhatNewcastlewhataheadwhatafterwhat31whatminutes,whatbutwhattheywhatwerewhatpeggedwhatbackwhataswhatBramblewhatheadedwhatinwhatStevenwhatGerrard'swhatcorner.\r\nNeilwhatMellorwhatgavewhatLiverpoolwhatthewhatleadwhatbeforewhathalf-timewhatfromwhatMilanwhatBaros'whatpasswhatbeforewhatthewhatCzechwhataddedwhatawhatthirdwhatafterwhatroundingwhatShaywhatGivenwhatonwhatthewhathour.\r\nAndwhatLiverpoolwhatwerewhataheadwhatafterwhat37whatminuteswhatwhenwhatBaroswhatslidwhatawhatperfectwhatpasswhatintowhatMellor'swhatpathwhatforwhatthewhatyoungsterwhattowhatslipwhatawhatslide-rulewhatfinishwhatintowhatGiven'swhatbottomwhatcorner.\r\nAnywhathopeswhatofwhatawhatNewcastlewhatrecoverywhatlookedwhattowhatbewhatsnuffedwhatoutwhatonwhatthewhathourwhatwhenwhatawhatbrilliantwhatturnwhatandwhatpasswhatbywhatHarrywhatKewellwhatsetwhatBaroswhatfreewhatandwhathewhatroundedwhatGivenwhattowhatscore.\r\nGiven,whatAndrewwhatO'Brien,whatElliott,whatBramble,whatBernard,whatBowyer,whatDyerwhat(Ambrosewhat80),whatJenas,whatMilnerwhat(N'Zogbiawhat72),whatKluivertwhat(Robertwhat58),whatAmeobi.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Scot was Pompey chairman Milan Mandaric's first choice to replace Harry Redknapp, who left Fratton Park for rivals Saints earlier in December.\r\n\"There's lots to do but it's not right for somebody who has just been the Southampton manager.\" Since Redknapp's departure, executive director Velimir Zajec and coach Joe Jordan have overseen first-team affairs.",
    "id": "N_269",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Scot",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "earlier"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "who"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Fifa president Sepp Blatter hopes Arsenal's Thierry Henry will be named World Player of the Year on Monday.",
    "id": "N_270",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Fifa",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "hopes",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Fifa president Sepp Blatter hopes Arsenal's Thierry who will be named World Player of the Year on Monday.?",
        "answer": "Henry"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newcastle have joined the race to sign Real Madrid striker Fernando Morientes and scupper Liverpool's bid to snap up the player, according to reports.\r\nBut the Liverpool Echo newspaper has said Anfield boss Rafa Benitez will avoid a bidding war and instead turn his attentions to Nicolas Anelka.\r\nBut Benitez could yet turn his attentions to the younger Anelka should Morientes be reluctant to pledge his future to Liverpool.",
    "id": "N_271",
    "features": {
        "noun": "race",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "scupper",
        "adverb": "Newcastle"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "NewcastlewhohavewhojoinedwhothewhoracewhotowhosignwhoRealwhoMadridwhostrikerwhoFernandowhoMorienteswhoandwhoscupperwhoLiverpool'swhobidwhotowhosnapwhoupwhothewhoplayer,whoaccordingwhotowhoreports.\r\nButwhothewhoLiverpoolwhoEchowhonewspaperwhohaswhosaidwhoAnfieldwhobosswhoRafawhoBenitezwhowillwhoavoidwhoawhobiddingwhowarwhoandwhoinsteadwhoturnwhohiswhoattentionswhotowhoNicolaswhoAnelka.\r\nButwhoBenitezwhocouldwhoyetwhoturnwhohiswhoattentionswhotowhothewhoyoungerwhoAnelkawhoshouldwhoMorienteswhobewhoreluctantwhotowhopledgewhohiswhofuturewhotowhoLiverpool.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Birmingham have confirmed Blackburn made a bid for Robbie Savage - but managing director Karen Brady has called it \"derisory\".\r\nBut he's not for sale.\" Savage's future at Birmingham has been the source of speculation for several weeks, with some fans criticising his performances for the club earlier in the season.\r\nIt's not up to me.\" Birmingham manager Steve Bruce insists he does not want to sell Savage.",
    "id": "N_272",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Birmingham",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "sale.\"",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "BirminghamwhohavewhoconfirmedwhoBlackburnwhomadewhoawhobidwhoforwhoRobbiewhoSavagewho-whobutwhomanagingwhodirectorwhoKarenwhoBradywhohaswhocalledwhoitwho\"derisory\".\r\nButwhohe'swhonotwhoforwhosale.\"whoSavage'swhofuturewhoatwhoBirminghamwhohaswhobeenwhothewhosourcewhoofwhospeculationwhoforwhoseveralwhoweeks,whowithwhosomewhofanswhocriticisingwhohiswhoperformanceswhoforwhothewhoclubwhoearlierwhoinwhothewhoseason.\r\nIt'swhonotwhoupwhotowhome.\"whoBirminghamwhomanagerwhoStevewhoBrucewhoinsistswhohewhodoeswhonotwhowantwhotowhosellwhoSavage.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"As club captain all I want to do is help us get back up the table and into the Champions League again.\" Gerrard looked set to move to Chelsea during the summer and speculation of a switch to Stamford Bridge has again arisen, with the January transfer window approaching.\r\nLiverpool boss Rafael Benitez has insisted that Gerrard has promised him he wants to stay at Anfield.\r\n\"I really think he wants to stay so now what we must do is make the squad stronger for him.\" Meanwhile, Gerrard has urged the Anfield board to sign Real Madrid striker Fernando Morientes in the January transfer window.",
    "id": "N_273",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"As",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "captain",
        "adjective": "approaching.",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"AswhoclubwhocaptainwhoallwhoIwhowantwhotowhodowhoiswhohelpwhouswhogetwhobackwhoupwhothewhotablewhoandwhointowhothewhoChampionswhoLeaguewhoagain.\"whoGerrardwholookedwhosetwhotowhomovewhotowhoChelseawhoduringwhothewhosummerwhoandwhospeculationwhoofwhoawhoswitchwhotowhoStamfordwhoBridgewhohaswhoagainwhoarisen,whowithwhothewhoJanuarywhotransferwhowindowwhoapproaching.\r\nLiverpoolwhobosswhoRafaelwhoBenitezwhohaswhoinsistedwhothatwhoGerrardwhohaswhopromisedwhohimwhohewhowantswhotowhostaywhoatwhoAnfield.\r\n\"Iwhoreallywhothinkwhohewhowantswhotowhostaywhosowhonowwhowhatwhowewhomustwhodowhoiswhomakewhothewhosquadwhostrongerwhoforwhohim.\"whoMeanwhile,whoGerrardwhohaswhourgedwhothewhoAnfieldwhoboardwhotowhosignwhoRealwhoMadridwhostrikerwhoFernandowhoMorienteswhoinwhothewhoJanuarywhotransferwhowindow.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Real Madrid midfielder David Beckham has no plans to become a manager when his playing career is over.\r\n\"I would really like to win La Liga with Real Madrid - I have been here two years and we still have not done it.\" In a wide-ranging interview, Beckham also revealed that his sending-off against Argentina - and the resulting media storm - had been the most significant moment in his career.",
    "id": "N_274",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Madrid",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Real",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Real Madrid midfielder David Beckham has no plans to become a manager when his playing what is over.\r\n\"I would really like to win La Liga with Real Madrid - I have been here two years and we still have not done it.\" In a wide-ranging interview, Beckham also revealed that his sending-off against Argentina - and the resulting media storm - had been the most significant moment in his what.?",
        "answer": "career"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mexican outfit Red Sharks Veracruz hope to sign Juninho if the Brazilian decides to leave Celtic frustrated at his lack of first-team action.\r\nHe is not a little kid.\" Hassell warns that Juninho could reconsider his future at Celtic unless he is given a run of games by the end of the January transfer window.\r\nHe deserves much more respect.\" Sanchez is bullish about his hopes of prising Juninho from the Scottish champions, although Hassell believes Mexico would not be his preferred destination.",
    "id": "N_275",
    "features": {
        "noun": "outfit",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "hope",
        "adjective": "Mexican",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Mexican outfit Red Sharks Veracruz hope to sign Juninho if the Brazilian decides to leave who frustrated at his lack of first-team action.\r\nHe is not a little kid.\" Hassell warns that Juninho could reconsider his future at who unless he is given a run of games by the end of the January transfer window.\r\nHe deserves much more respect.\" Sanchez is bullish about his hopes of prising Juninho from the Scottish champions, although Hassell believes Mexico would not be his preferred destination.?",
        "answer": "Celtic"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I can't say I was overly pleased at the fixture being played just after Christmas,\" said O'Neill.\r\n\"I have said this before, but Bulgaria are the one nation who seem to organise a lot of friendly games.\"",
    "id": "N_276",
    "features": {
        "noun": "can't",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "say",
        "adjective": "\"I",
        "adverb": "overly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"I can't say I was overly pleased at the fixture being played just after Christmas,\" said who.\r\n\"I have said this before, but Bulgaria are the one nation who seem to organise a lot of friendly games.\"?",
        "answer": "O'Neill"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arjen Robben curled in a late deflected left-footed shot from the right side of Pompey's box to break the home side's brave resistance.\r\nStriker Didier Drogba snapped in an angled shot to force home keeper Shaka Hislop into a smart save while an unmarked Frank Lampard had a strike blocked by Arjan De Zeeuw.\r\nBut, just like against Arsenal, Portsmouth let in a late goal when Robben's shot took a deflection off Matthew Taylor on its way past a wrong-footed Hislop.\r\nCech, Paulo Ferreira, Gallas, Terry, Johnson, Duff, Makelele, Smertin (Cole 73), Lampard, Robben (Geremi 81), Drogba (Gudjohnsen 58).",
    "id": "N_277",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arjen",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "curled",
        "adjective": "late",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Arjen who curled in a late deflected left-footed shot from the right side of Pompey's box to break the home side's brave resistance.\r\nStriker Didier Drogba snapped in an angled shot to force home keeper Shaka Hislop into a smart save while an unmarked Frank Lampard had a strike blocked by Arjan De Zeeuw.\r\nBut, just like against Arsenal, Portsmouth let in a late goal when who's shot took a deflection off Matthew Taylor on its way past a wrong-footed Hislop.\r\nCech, Paulo Ferreira, Gallas, Terry, Johnson, Duff, Makelele, Smertin (Cole 73), Lampard, who (Geremi 81), Drogba (Gudjohnsen 58).?",
        "answer": "Robben"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newcastle manager Graeme Souness is closing in on signing Chelsea defender Celestine Babayaro when the transfer window reopens.",
    "id": "N_278",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Newcastle",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Newcastle manager Graeme Souness is closing in on signing Chelsea defender Celestine Babayaro when the transfer what reopens.?",
        "answer": "window"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Arsenal will play the Magpies a day after Chelsea beat Portsmouth during a busy festive programme.\r\nChelsea boss Jose Mourinho admitted his side were \"lucky\" to win at Fratton Park but is still unhappy with the amount of games in such a short space of time during this time of year.",
    "id": "N_279",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Arsenal",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "play",
        "adjective": "busy",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Arsenal will play the Magpies a day after who beat Portsmouth during a busy festive programme.\r\nwho boss Jose Mourinho admitted his side were \"lucky\" to win at Fratton Park but is still unhappy with the amount of games in such a short space of time during this time of year.?",
        "answer": "Chelsea"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "And Wenger said: \"At the beginning of the season you would expect them to be fighting for the top four.\r\nAnd Wenger added: \"The best way to prepare for a game is to win the previous one.\r\n\"We do not play a season with 11 players and I believe that all of our squad deserve a chance in the team.\" Striker Thierry Henry, along with Robert Pires, scored against Fulham.",
    "id": "N_280",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wenger",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "said:",
        "adjective": "top",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I look at that fixture and think we've been there and won, while Arsenal and Chelsea have yet to come and Villa may have some players back when they do.\" Ferguson also hailed senior stars Ryan Giggs and Roy Keane, who came off the bench for the injured John O'Shea.",
    "id": "N_281",
    "features": {
        "noun": "look",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "think",
        "adjective": "\"I",
        "adverb": "we've"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Iwholookwhoatwhothatwhofixturewhoandwhothinkwhowe'vewhobeenwhotherewhoandwhowon,whowhilewhoArsenalwhoandwhoChelseawhohavewhoyetwhotowhocomewhoandwhoVillawhomaywhohavewhosomewhoplayerswhobackwhowhenwhotheywhodo.\"whoFergusonwhoalsowhohailedwhoseniorwhostarswhoRyanwhoGiggswhoandwhoRoywhoKeane,whowhowhocamewhooffwhothewhobenchwhoforwhothewhoinjuredwhoJohnwhoO'Shea.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Spurs boss Martin Jol said his team were \"robbed\" at Manchester United after Pedro Mendes' shot clearly crossed the line but was not given.\r\n\"It's not every game you score from the halfway line.\" Manchester United manager Sir Alex Ferguson sympathised with Tottenham and said the incident highlighted the need for video technology.\r\n\"But I read an article the other day which suggested that if a referee can't make up his mind after 30 seconds of watching a video replay then the game should carry on.\r\n\"It's a great example of where the referee could have asked to see a replay and would have seen in five seconds that it was a goal.\"",
    "id": "N_282",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Spurs",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "given.",
        "adverb": "clearly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "SpurswhatbosswhatMartinwhatJolwhatsaidwhathiswhatteamwhatwerewhat\"robbed\"whatatwhatManchesterwhatUnitedwhatafterwhatPedrowhatMendes'whatshotwhatclearlywhatcrossedwhatthewhatlinewhatbutwhatwaswhatnotwhatgiven.\r\n\"It'swhatnotwhateverywhatgamewhatyouwhatscorewhatfromwhatthewhathalfwaywhatline.\"whatManchesterwhatUnitedwhatmanagerwhatSirwhatAlexwhatFergusonwhatsympathisedwhatwithwhatTottenhamwhatandwhatsaidwhatthewhatincidentwhathighlightedwhatthewhatneedwhatforwhatvideowhattechnology.\r\n\"ButwhatIwhatreadwhatanwhatarticlewhatthewhatotherwhatdaywhatwhichwhatsuggestedwhatthatwhatifwhatawhatrefereewhatcan'twhatmakewhatupwhathiswhatmindwhatafterwhat30whatsecondswhatofwhatwatchingwhatawhatvideowhatreplaywhatthenwhatthewhatgamewhatshouldwhatcarrywhaton.\r\n\"It'swhatawhatgreatwhatexamplewhatofwhatwherewhatthewhatrefereewhatcouldwhathavewhataskedwhattowhatseewhatawhatreplaywhatandwhatwouldwhathavewhatseenwhatinwhatfivewhatsecondswhatthatwhatitwhatwaswhatawhatgoal.\"?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Fly-half Charlie Hodgson admitted his wayward kicking played a big part in England's 18-17 defeat to France.\r\nHodgson failed to convert three penalties and also missed a relatively easy drop goal attempt which would have given England a late win.\r\nEngland went in at half-time with a 17-6 lead but they failed to score in the second half and Dimitri Yachvili slotted over four penalties as France overhauled the deficit.\r\nEngland skipper Jason Robinson admitted his side failed to cope with France's improved second-half display.",
    "id": "N_283",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Charlie",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "admitted",
        "adjective": "Fly-half",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Fly-half Charlie Hodgson admitted his wayward kicking played a big part in England's 18-17 defeat to which location.\r\nHodgson failed to convert three penalties and also missed a relatively easy drop goal attempt which would have given England a late win.\r\nEngland went in at half-time with a 17-6 lead but they failed to score in the second half and Dimitri Yachvili slotted over four penalties as which location overhauled the deficit.\r\nEngland skipper Jason Robinson admitted his side failed to cope with which location's improved second-half display.?",
        "answer": "France"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England tight-head prop Phil Vickery has been ruled out of the rest of the 2005 RBS Six Nations after breaking a bone in his right forearm.\r\nAnd the Gloucester prop was only recalled after Leicester tight-head Julian White suffered a neck injury which has already seen him ruled out of the Ireland game.\r\nBath prop Matt Stevens is the only remaining tight-head in England's training squad and could be involved against Ireland.",
    "id": "N_284",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "tight-head",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England tight-head prop Phil who has been ruled out of the rest of the 2005 RBS Six Nations after breaking a bone in his right forearm.\r\nAnd the Gloucester prop was only recalled after Leicester tight-head Julian White suffered a neck injury which has already seen him ruled out of the Ireland game.\r\nBath prop Matt Stevens is the only remaining tight-head in England's training squad and could be involved against Ireland.?",
        "answer": "Vickery"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "France scrum-half Dimitri Yachvili praised his team after they fought back to beat England 18-17 in the Six Nations clash at Twickenham.\r\nYachvili kicked all of France's points as they staged a second-half revival.\r\nWe were just defending in the first half and we said we had to put them under pressure.",
    "id": "N_285",
    "features": {
        "noun": "France",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "praised",
        "adjective": "scrum-half",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "France scrum-half Dimitri Yachvili praised his team after who fought back to beat England 18-17 in the Six Nations clash at Twickenham.\r\nYachvili kicked all of France's points as who staged a second-half revival.\r\nWe were just defending in the first half and we said we had to put them under pressure.?",
        "answer": "they"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Other changes see Julien Laharrague win his first cap at full-back, Aurelien Rougerie return after injury on the wing and Yannick Jauzion in at centre.\r\n\"We are launching him into the great international level,\" said team manager Jo Maso.\r\n\"The return of Jauzion is going to be a plus for us,\" said Laporte.",
    "id": "N_286",
    "features": {
        "noun": "changes",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "see",
        "adjective": "Other",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "OtherwhochangeswhoseewhoJulienwhoLaharraguewhowinwhohiswhofirstwhocapwhoatwhofull-back,whoAurelienwhoRougeriewhoreturnwhoafterwhoinjurywhoonwhothewhowingwhoandwhoYannickwhoJauzionwhoinwhoatwhocentre.\r\n\"Wewhoarewholaunchingwhohimwhointowhothewhogreatwhointernationalwholevel,\"whosaidwhoteamwhomanagerwhoJowhoMaso.\r\n\"ThewhoreturnwhoofwhoJauzionwhoiswhogoingwhotowhobewhoawhopluswhoforwhous,\"whosaidwhoLaporte.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Wasps wing insisted he grounded the ball when he was bundled over the line and said referee Jonathan Kaplan had made a wrong decision.\r\nThe whistle went and I let go of the ball.\" Lewsey added: \"One of the Irish players scooped it back after the whistle and to our surprise the referee then gave a turnover.",
    "id": "N_287",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wasps",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "insisted",
        "adjective": "referee",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoWaspswhowingwhoinsistedwhohewhogroundedwhothewhoballwhowhenwhohewhowaswhobundledwhooverwhothewholinewhoandwhosaidwhorefereewhoJonathanwhoKaplanwhohadwhomadewhoawhowrongwhodecision.\r\nThewhowhistlewhowentwhoandwhoIwholetwhogowhoofwhothewhoball.\"whoLewseywhoadded:who\"OnewhoofwhothewhoIrishwhoplayerswhoscoopedwhoitwhobackwhoafterwhothewhowhistlewhoandwhotowhoourwhosurprisewhothewhorefereewhothenwhogavewhoawhoturnover.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England coach Andy Robinson insisted he was \"livid\" after his side were denied two tries in Sunday's 19-13 Six Nations loss to Ireland in Dublin.\r\nKaplan then declined the chance to consult the fourth official when Josh Lewsey took the ball over the Irish line under a pile of bodies for what could have been the game-winning try.\r\n\"I think Mark Cueto scored a perfectly legal try and I think he should have gone to the video referee on Josh Lewsey,\" said Robinson.\r\nThey defended magnificently and they've got every chance of winning this Six Nations.\" England have lost their first three matches in this year's Six Nations and four out of their six games since Robinson took over from Sir Clive Woodward in September.",
    "id": "N_288",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "insisted",
        "adjective": "19-13",
        "adverb": "\"livid\""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England coach Andy Robinson insisted he was \"livid\" after his what were denied two tries in Sunday's 19-13 Six Nations loss to Ireland in Dublin.\r\nKaplan then declined the chance to consult the fourth official when Josh Lewsey took the ball over the Irish line under a pile of bodies for what could have been the game-winning try.\r\n\"I think Mark Cueto scored a perfectly legal try and I think he should have gone to the video referee on Josh Lewsey,\" said Robinson.\r\nThey defended magnificently and they've got every chance of winning this Six Nations.\" England have lost their first three matches in this year's Six Nations and four out of their six games since Robinson took over from Sir Clive Woodward in September.?",
        "answer": "side"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "All round it was fantastic.\" Ireland captain Brian O'Driscoll, who scored his side's only try, said: \"We are delighted, we felt if we performed well then we would win but with England also having played very well it makes it all the sweeter.\r\nIreland coach Eddie O'Sullivan was surprised that England coach Andy Robinson said he was certain Mark Cueto was onside for a disallowed try just before the break.\r\n\"What I do know is that England played well and when that happens it makes a very good victory for us.\r\n\"I think our try was very well worked, it was a gem, as good a try as we have scored for a while.\" O'Sullivan also rejected Robinson's contention England dominated the forward play.",
    "id": "N_289",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ireland",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "round",
        "adjective": "fantastic.\"",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "All round who was fantastic.\" Ireland captain Brian O'Driscoll, who scored his side's only try, said: \"We are delighted, we felt if we performed well then we would win but wwhoh England also having played very well who makes who all the sweeter.\r\nIreland coach Eddie O'Sullivan was surprised that England coach Andy Robinson said he was certain Mark Cueto was onside for a disallowed try just before the break.\r\n\"What I do know is that England played well and when that happens who makes a very good victory for us.\r\n\"I think our try was very well worked, who was a gem, as good a try as we have scored for a while.\" O'Sullivan also rejected Robinson's contention England dominated the forward play.?",
        "answer": "it"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Bennett told BBC Sport: \"Such is the spirit in the camp, they'll put Kevin Morgan at 15, Rhys Williams at wing and just carry on.\" Thomas will miss the match against Scotland on 13 March, and what promises to be a huge encounter against the Irish six days later.\r\nHe's a great captain, he leads from the front and the boys love him.\" Thomas was replaced at half-time by Williams as his side turned around a 15-6 deficit in Paris.\r\nBennett, an inspirational fly-half for Llanelli and Wales in the 1970s, insisted the national team were entering a new golden period.",
    "id": "N_290",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Bennett",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "told",
        "adjective": "huge",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "BennettwhotoldwhoBBCwhoSport:who\"Suchwhoiswhothewhospiritwhoinwhothewhocamp,whothey'llwhoputwhoKevinwhoMorganwhoatwho15,whoRhyswhoWilliamswhoatwhowingwhoandwhojustwhocarrywhoon.\"whoThomaswhowillwhomisswhothewhomatchwhoagainstwhoScotlandwhoonwho13whoMarch,whoandwhowhatwhopromiseswhotowhobewhoawhohugewhoencounterwhoagainstwhothewhoIrishwhosixwhodayswholater.\r\nHe'swhoawhogreatwhocaptain,whohewholeadswhofromwhothewhofrontwhoandwhothewhoboyswholovewhohim.\"whoThomaswhowaswhoreplacedwhoatwhohalf-timewhobywhoWilliamswhoaswhohiswhosidewhoturnedwhoaroundwhoawho15-6whodeficitwhoinwhoParis.\r\nBennett,whoanwhoinspirationalwhofly-halfwhoforwhoLlanelliwhoandwhoWaleswhoinwhothewho1970s,whoinsistedwhothewhonationalwhoteamwhowerewhoenteringwhoawhonewwhogoldenwhoperiod.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"After going two tries down in 12 minutes we had to show character,\" said the national team coach.\r\nTwo years ago we didn't win a single game in the Six Nations.\r\nWe've got hard matches to come, so we're just happy with the start.\" Double try scorer Martyn Williams was keen not to talk about a possible Grand Slam for Wales.",
    "id": "N_291",
    "features": {
        "noun": "tries",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "going",
        "adjective": "national",
        "adverb": "\"After"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"After going two tries down in 12 minutes we had to show character,\" said the national team what.\r\nTwo years ago we didn't win a single game in the Six Nations.\r\nWe've got hard matches to come, so we're just happy with the start.\" Double try scorer Martyn Williams was keen not to talk about a possible Grand Slam for Wales.?",
        "answer": "coach"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newcastle centre Mathew Tait answered his critics as he scored one try and made another, but he could not stop Gloucester grabbing a draw.\r\nMayerhofler then scythed through the middle for a try after Hall Charlton popped the ball up, and Walder's conversion took Newcastle 27-22 ahead.\r\nHenry missed the conversion but Gloucester nearly won it when Kiole broke through only to be hauled down by Charlton and Tom May.",
    "id": "N_292",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Newcastle",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "answered",
        "adjective": "27-22",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "NewcastlewhocentrewhoMathewwhoTaitwhoansweredwhohiswhocriticswhoaswhohewhoscoredwhoonewhotrywhoandwhomadewhoanother,whobutwhohewhocouldwhonotwhostopwhoGloucesterwhograbbingwhoawhodraw.\r\nMayerhoflerwhothenwhoscythedwhothroughwhothewhomiddlewhoforwhoawhotrywhoafterwhoHallwhoCharltonwhopoppedwhothewhoballwhoup,whoandwhoWalder'swhoconversionwhotookwhoNewcastlewho27-22whoahead.\r\nHenrywhomissedwhothewhoconversionwhobutwhoGloucesterwhonearlywhowonwhoitwhowhenwhoKiolewhobrokewhothroughwhoonlywhotowhobewhohauledwhodownwhobywhoCharltonwhoandwhoTomwhoMay.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tom Voyce powered through the Irish defence for Wasps' second try before Richard Birkett went over unchallenged.\r\nReplacements: Everitt for Mapletoft (53), Hodgson for Edwards (77), Wheatley for Hatley (71), Paice for van der Walt (60), Strudwick for Kennedy (60), Danaher for Gustard (66), Reid for Murphy (47)\r\nVan Gisbergen; Voyce, Erinle, Hoadley, Roberts; King, Richards; Payne, Greening, Dowd; Shaw, Purdy; Hart, Rees, Dallaglio.\r\nReplacements: Priscott for Roberts (71), Green for Dowd (71), Skivington for Shaw (71), Birkett for Hart (57), Gotting for Rees (39).",
    "id": "N_293",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tom",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "powered",
        "adjective": "Irish",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tom Voyce powered through the Irish defence for Wasps' second try before Richard who went over unchallenged.\r\nReplacements: Everitt for Mapletoft (53), Hodgson for Edwards (77), Wheatley for Hatley (71), Paice for van der Walt (60), Strudwick for Kennedy (60), Danaher for Gustard (66), Reid for Murphy (47)\r\nVan Gisbergen; Voyce, Erinle, Hoadley, Roberts; King, Richards; Payne, Greening, Dowd; Shaw, Purdy; Hart, Rees, Dallaglio.\r\nReplacements: Priscott for Roberts (71), Green for Dowd (71), Skivington for Shaw (71), who for Hart (57), Gotting for Rees (39).?",
        "answer": "Birkett"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Euan Murray has been named in the Scotland training squad after an eight-week ban, ahead of Saturday's Six Nations match with Ireland.",
    "id": "N_294",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Murray",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Euan",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Euan Murray has been named in the Scotland training squad after an eight-week ban, ahead of Saturday's Six Nations match with which location.?",
        "answer": "Ireland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"We will go to Twickenham with a little fear and it'll give us a boost,\" said the French coach.",
    "id": "N_295",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"We",
        "pronoun": "us",
        "verb": "go",
        "adjective": "little",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"WewhowillwhogowhotowhoTwickenhamwhowithwhoawholittlewhofearwhoandwhoit'llwhogivewhouswhoawhoboost,\"whosaidwhothewhoFrenchwhocoach.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales hooker Mefin Davies is likely to stay with English side Gloucester despite reported interest from the Neath-Swansea Ospreys.",
    "id": "N_296",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "likely",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wales hooker Mefin who is likely to stay with English side Gloucester despite reported interest from the Neath-Swansea Ospreys.?",
        "answer": "Davies"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The referee from Saturday's France v Scotland Six Nations match has defended the officials' handling of the game after criticism by Matt Williams.\r\nBut Nigel Williams said: \"I'm satisfied the game was handled correctly.\" Meanwhile, Matt Williams will not be punished by the Scottish Rugby Union for allegedly using bad language in his comments about the officials.",
    "id": "N_297",
    "features": {
        "noun": "referee",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "officials'",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "The referee from Saturday's France v Scotland Six Nations what has defended the officials' handling of the game after criticism by Matt Williams.\r\nBut Nigel Williams said: \"I'm satisfied the game was handled correctly.\" Meanwhile, Matt Williams will not be punished by the Scottish Rugby Union for allegedly using bad language in his comments about the officials.?",
        "answer": "match"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England coach Andy Robinson faces the first major test of his tenure as he tries to get back to winning ways after the Six Nations defeat by Wales.\r\nRobinson is likely to make changes in the back row and centre after the 11-9 loss as he contemplates Sunday's set-to with France at Twickenham.\r\nOlly Barkley immediately allowed England to generate better field position with his kicking game after replacing debutant Tait just before the hour.\r\nThe Bath fly-half-cum-centre is likely to start against France, with either Tait or Noon dropping out.",
    "id": "N_298",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "faces",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England coach Andy Robinson faces twho first major test of his tenure as who tries to get back to winning ways after twho Six Nations defeat by Wales.\r\nRobinson is likely to make changes in twho back row and centre after twho 11-9 loss as who contemplates Sunday's set-to with France at Twickenham.\r\nOlly Barkley immediately allowed England to generate better field position with his kicking game after replacing debutant Tait just before twho hour.\r\nTwho Bath fly-half-cum-centre is likely to start against France, with eitwhor Tait or Noon dropping out.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Bath prop Duncan Bell has been added to England's 30-man squad to face Ireland in the RBS Six Nations.\r\nRobinson also has an injury worry over centre Olly Barkley, who withdrew from Bath's starting line-up to face Gloucester last weekend.",
    "id": "N_299",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Bath",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "30-man",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Bath prop Duncan who has been added to England's 30-man squad to face Ireland in the RBS Six Nations.\r\nRobinson also has an injury worry over centre Olly Barkley, who withdrew from Bath's starting line-up to face Gloucester last weekend.?",
        "answer": "Bell"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"We had our first attack in the Italian half after 22 minutes,\" said O'Sullivan.\r\n\"They had a lot of ball in the first half but we got a few scores when we got into their 22.\"",
    "id": "N_300",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"We",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"We had our first attack in the Italian half after 22 minutes,\" said who.\r\n\"They had a lot of ball in the first half but we got a few scores when we got into their 22.\"?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Italy led 9-8 early in the second half but Stringer's try gave Ireland a lead they never lost.\r\nThe only Ireland player offering a real threat was O'Driscoll, and it was his break that set up the second try for the visitors.\r\nAn O'Gara penalty put Ireland more than a converted try ahead and they made the game safe when Hickie latched onto an inside pass from Murphy and crossed for a converted try.\r\nMurphy, Horgan, O'Driscoll, D'Arcy, Hickie, O'Gara, Stringer, Corrigan, Byrne, Hayes, O'Kelly, O'Connell, S Easterby, Leamy, Foley.",
    "id": "N_301",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Italy",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "led",
        "adjective": "early",
        "adverb": "never"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Italywholedwho9-8whoearlywhoinwhothewhosecondwhohalfwhobutwhoStringer'swhotrywhogavewhoIrelandwhoawholeadwhotheywhoneverwholost.\r\nThewhoonlywhoIrelandwhoplayerwhoofferingwhoawhorealwhothreatwhowaswhoO'Driscoll,whoandwhoitwhowaswhohiswhobreakwhothatwhosetwhoupwhothewhosecondwhotrywhoforwhothewhovisitors.\r\nAnwhoO'GarawhopenaltywhoputwhoIrelandwhomorewhothanwhoawhoconvertedwhotrywhoaheadwhoandwhotheywhomadewhothewhogamewhosafewhowhenwhoHickiewholatchedwhoontowhoanwhoinsidewhopasswhofromwhoMurphywhoandwhocrossedwhoforwhoawhoconvertedwhotry.\r\nMurphy,whoHorgan,whoO'Driscoll,whoD'Arcy,whoHickie,whoO'Gara,whoStringer,whoCorrigan,whoByrne,whoHayes,whoO'Kelly,whoO'Connell,whoSwhoEasterby,whoLeamy,whoFoley.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales fly-half Stephen Jones admitted he was happy to hand Gavin Henson responsibility for taking the match-winning kick against England.\r\nJones had missed three earlier shots at goal when Wales, 9-8 down, were awarded a long-range penalty with four minutes left in Cardiff.\r\nHe had a superb game.\" Jones was happy to hail Henson's heroic contribution to Wales' first win over England in Cardiff since 1993.\r\n\"Physically he's a specimen: he's a balanced player, he glides when he runs and obviously he's got a great kicking game as well,\" Jones said.",
    "id": "N_302",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "admitted",
        "adjective": "fly-half",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wales fly-half Stephen Jones admitted he was happy to hand Gavin Henson responsibility for taking the match-winning kick against which location.\r\nJones had missed three earlier shots at goal when Wales, 9-8 down, were awarded a long-range penalty with four minutes left in Cardiff.\r\nHe had a superb game.\" Jones was happy to hail Henson's heroic contribution to Wales' first win over which location in Cardiff since 1993.\r\n\"Physically he's a specimen: he's a balanced player, he glides when he runs and obviously he's got a great kicking game as well,\" Jones said.?",
        "answer": "England"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales centre Sonny Parker and number eight Ryan Jones will miss Saturday's game with Italy because of injury.\r\nFirst-choice kicker Stephen Jones handed over responsibility because of Henson's greater kicking range, but the fly-half had already missed a number of shots at goal.",
    "id": "N_303",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "centre",
        "adjective": "injury.",
        "adverb": "already"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WaleswhocentrewhoSonnywhoParkerwhoandwhonumberwhoeightwhoRyanwhoJoneswhowillwhomisswhoSaturday'swhogamewhowithwhoItalywhobecausewhoofwhoinjury.\r\nFirst-choicewhokickerwhoStephenwhoJoneswhohandedwhooverwhoresponsibilitywhobecausewhoofwhoHenson'swhogreaterwhokickingwhorange,whobutwhothewhofly-halfwhohadwhoalreadywhomissedwhoawhonumberwhoofwhoshotswhoatwhogoal.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Italy coach John Kirwan has challenged his side to match the performance they produced in pushing Ireland close when they meet Wales on Saturday.\r\n\"Our goal is to match every side we face and against Ireland we showed we could do that,\" said Kirwan.",
    "id": "N_304",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Italy",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Italy coach John Kirwan has challenged his side to match the performance who produced in pushing Ireland close when who meet Wales on Saturday.\r\n\"Our goal is to match every side we face and against Ireland we showed we could do that,\" said Kirwan.?",
        "answer": "they"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Serge has a good case so we are confident he will play,\" said France coach Bernard Laporte.\r\nThe inexperienced Nicolas Mas, Jimmy Marlu and Jean-Philippe Grandclaude are also included in a 22-man squad.",
    "id": "N_305",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"Serge",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "good",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Serge has a good case so we are confident he will play,\" said France coach Bernard who.\r\nThe inexperienced Nicolas Mas, Jimmy Marlu and Jean-Philippe Grandclaude are also included in a 22-man squad.?",
        "answer": "Laporte"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales coach Mike Ruddock says England lock Danny Grewcock needs to review his actions after he kicked Dwayne Peel.\r\nTrouble flared at a ruck in the first half of Wales' 11-9 win in Cardiff as Grewcock came recklessly over the top with his boot, leaving Peel bloodied.\r\n\"If the ball is at the back of the ruck and I feel I can step over and disrupt it then I will do that,\" said Grewcock.",
    "id": "N_306",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "coach",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "recklessly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wales coach Mike Ruddock says England lock Danny Grewcock needs to review his actions after who kicked Dwayne Peel.\r\nTrouble flared at a ruck in twho first half of Wales' 11-9 win in Cardiff as Grewcock came recklessly over twho top with his boot, leaving Peel bloodied.\r\n\"If twho ball is at twho back of twho ruck and I feel I can step over and disrupt it twhon I will do that,\" said Grewcock.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He once showed a clean pair of heels to Mathew Tait when he got outside him, his defence was very good and he made some great kicks out of hand.\r\nWales fly-half Stephen Jones was another player who impressed me.\r\nWith Jonny Wilkinson not playing at the moment due to inury the number 10 shirt could be up for grabs and Jones, or maybe even Henson, could make the Lions team at fly-half.\r\nGordon D'Arcy was unlucky to go off injured early on but I think you could get a Henson, D'Arcy, O'Driscoll combination in the Lions midfield.\r\nOne player who didn't impress me was Wales scrum-half Dwayne Peel.\r\nThey had good possession and he kicked the ball away - I wouldn't want him as my Lions scrum-half after that.",
    "id": "N_307",
    "features": {
        "noun": "pair",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "showed",
        "adjective": "clean",
        "adverb": "once"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "HewhatoncewhatshowedwhatawhatcleanwhatpairwhatofwhatheelswhattowhatMathewwhatTaitwhatwhenwhathewhatgotwhatoutsidewhathim,whathiswhatdefencewhatwaswhatverywhatgoodwhatandwhathewhatmadewhatsomewhatgreatwhatkickswhatoutwhatofwhathand.\r\nWaleswhatfly-halfwhatStephenwhatJoneswhatwaswhatanotherwhatplayerwhatwhowhatimpressedwhatme.\r\nWithwhatJonnywhatWilkinsonwhatnotwhatplayingwhatatwhatthewhatmomentwhatduewhattowhatinurywhatthewhatnumberwhat10whatshirtwhatcouldwhatbewhatupwhatforwhatgrabswhatandwhatJones,whatorwhatmaybewhatevenwhatHenson,whatcouldwhatmakewhatthewhatLionswhatteamwhatatwhatfly-half.\r\nGordonwhatD'ArcywhatwaswhatunluckywhattowhatgowhatoffwhatinjuredwhatearlywhatonwhatbutwhatIwhatthinkwhatyouwhatcouldwhatgetwhatawhatHenson,whatD'Arcy,whatO'DriscollwhatcombinationwhatinwhatthewhatLionswhatmidfield.\r\nOnewhatplayerwhatwhowhatdidn'twhatimpresswhatmewhatwaswhatWaleswhatscrum-halfwhatDwaynewhatPeel.\r\nTheywhathadwhatgoodwhatpossessionwhatandwhathewhatkickedwhatthewhatballwhatawaywhat-whatIwhatwouldn'twhatwantwhathimwhataswhatmywhatLionswhatscrum-halfwhatafterwhatthat.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "It was very physical and fair play to the Italians they made us work very hard for our victory.\r\nIt was really hard work out there and the players have plenty of bumps and bruises to prove it.\r\nIt was great work by Brian and I always knew I had scored even though it went upstairs to the video referee.\r\nThat new ruck law made it a bit more difficult to get out of our own half.\r\nSo really we went back to playing a territory game and simplifying things and having more patience on the ball.",
    "id": "N_308",
    "features": {
        "noun": "play",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "physical",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ItwhowaswhoverywhophysicalwhoandwhofairwhoplaywhotowhothewhoItalianswhotheywhomadewhouswhoworkwhoverywhohardwhoforwhoourwhovictory.\r\nItwhowaswhoreallywhohardwhoworkwhooutwhotherewhoandwhothewhoplayerswhohavewhoplentywhoofwhobumpswhoandwhobruiseswhotowhoprovewhoit.\r\nItwhowaswhogreatwhoworkwhobywhoBrianwhoandwhoIwhoalwayswhoknewwhoIwhohadwhoscoredwhoevenwhothoughwhoitwhowentwhoupstairswhotowhothewhovideowhoreferee.\r\nThatwhonewwhoruckwholawwhomadewhoitwhoawhobitwhomorewhodifficultwhotowhogetwhooutwhoofwhoourwhoownwhohalf.\r\nSowhoreallywhowewhowentwhobackwhotowhoplayingwhoawhoterritorywhogamewhoandwhosimplifyingwhothingswhoandwhohavingwhomorewhopatiencewhoonwhothewhoball.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales coach Mike Ruddock has made two changes from the team that beat Italy 38-8 for Saturday's trip to France.\r\n\"Due to his impressive performances from the bench, Kevin was very much in the selection mix anyway, and the unfortunate injury to Hal gives him the chance to start,\" said Ruddock.\r\n\"Obviously, it's a 22-man game these days, and there is every chance that Jonathan will be making an impact from the bench.\" Wales have beaten France on two of their last three visits to Paris, and another victory this time around would keep them firmly on course for a first Five or Six Nations title triumph since 1994.",
    "id": "N_309",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "coach",
        "adjective": "38-8",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wales coach Mike Ruddock has made two changes from the team that beat Italy 38-8 for Saturday's trip to which location.\r\n\"Due to his impressive performances from the bench, Kevin was very much in the selection mix anyway, and the unfortunate injury to Hal gives him the chance to start,\" said Ruddock.\r\n\"Obviously, it's a 22-man game these days, and there is every chance that Jonathan will be making an impact from the bench.\" Wales have beaten which location on two of their last three visits to Paris, and another victory this time around would keep them firmly on course for a first Five or Six Nations title triumph since 1994.?",
        "answer": "France"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Hugo Southwell's try gave the Scots an early 8-0 lead but scores from locks Malcolm O'Kelly and Paul O'Connell put the visitors in command by half-time.\r\nA powerful charge from flanker Jason White was carried on by Ali Hogg and when Ireland conceded a penalty close to their own line, Scotland kicked it to touch.\r\nIf that was a paltry reward for their early pressure, Scotland got the try they deserved when Paterson's searing break and Andy Craig's pass sent Southwell streaking to the right corner.\r\nScotland suffered a further blow on the resumption when Ireland flanker Johnny O'Connor won another vital turnover, and O'Gara's basketball pass sent Hickie over in the left corner.\r\nPeter Stringer and O'Kelly combined to put giant prop Hayes over in the right corner before replacement Gavin Duffy scorched away on the left, David Humphreys adding the final flourish with a touchline conversion.",
    "id": "N_310",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Hugo",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "gave",
        "adjective": "early",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "HugowhatSouthwell'swhattrywhatgavewhatthewhatScotswhatanwhatearlywhat8-0whatleadwhatbutwhatscoreswhatfromwhatlockswhatMalcolmwhatO'KellywhatandwhatPaulwhatO'Connellwhatputwhatthewhatvisitorswhatinwhatcommandwhatbywhathalf-time.\r\nAwhatpowerfulwhatchargewhatfromwhatflankerwhatJasonwhatWhitewhatwaswhatcarriedwhatonwhatbywhatAliwhatHoggwhatandwhatwhenwhatIrelandwhatconcededwhatawhatpenaltywhatclosewhattowhattheirwhatownwhatline,whatScotlandwhatkickedwhatitwhattowhattouch.\r\nIfwhatthatwhatwaswhatawhatpaltrywhatrewardwhatforwhattheirwhatearlywhatpressure,whatScotlandwhatgotwhatthewhattrywhattheywhatdeservedwhatwhenwhatPaterson'swhatsearingwhatbreakwhatandwhatAndywhatCraig'swhatpasswhatsentwhatSouthwellwhatstreakingwhattowhatthewhatrightwhatcorner.\r\nScotlandwhatsufferedwhatawhatfurtherwhatblowwhatonwhatthewhatresumptionwhatwhenwhatIrelandwhatflankerwhatJohnnywhatO'Connorwhatwonwhatanotherwhatvitalwhatturnover,whatandwhatO'Gara'swhatbasketballwhatpasswhatsentwhatHickiewhatoverwhatinwhatthewhatleftwhatcorner.\r\nPeterwhatStringerwhatandwhatO'KellywhatcombinedwhattowhatputwhatgiantwhatpropwhatHayeswhatoverwhatinwhatthewhatrightwhatcornerwhatbeforewhatreplacementwhatGavinwhatDuffywhatscorchedwhatawaywhatonwhatthewhatleft,whatDavidwhatHumphreyswhataddingwhatthewhatfinalwhatflourishwhatwithwhatawhattouchlinewhatconversion.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tries from Jonathan Thomas, Tom Shanklin and Martyn Williams gave the visitors a 19-5 half-time advantage.\r\nLuciano Orquera did reply with one for Italy but second-half efforts from Brent Cockbain, Shane Williams and Robert Sidoli sealed victory.\r\nFly-half Stephen Jones added four conversions as Wales maintained their superb start to this year's tournament.\r\nBut a clever high kick from Henson almost brought a try for Hal Luscombe when Roland de Marigny and Ludovico Nitoglia made a hash of claiming it as the ball bounced into touch.\r\nWales regained control with a second try in the 21st minute, Henson lobbing up a high kick to the left corner where Shanklin jumped higher than Nitoglia to dot down his 15th Test try.\r\nHenson sent Luscombe streaking away and when he off-loaded to Martyn Williams, the flanker showed his nous to ground the ball against the padding of the post, Jones adding the conversion.",
    "id": "N_311",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tries",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "gave",
        "adjective": "19-5",
        "adverb": "almost"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tough-scrummaging prop Julian White is expecting a resurgent Wales to give him a rough ride in England's Six Nations opener in Cardiff on Saturday.\r\nThe Leicester tight-head is in the form of his life, making the England number three shirt his own.\r\nThe 31-year-old has made a massive contribution to the England and Leicester cause of late and is arguably the form tight-head prop in the world.\r\n\"But my form is helped by the people I play with at Leicester - people like Martin Johnson and Graham Rowntree.\r\n\"I don't know how much experience a tight-head can give a centre but you are there to give them a pat on the back if things go wrong or to be there if they want to talk in any way,\" he added.",
    "id": "N_312",
    "features": {
        "noun": "prop",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "Tough-scrummaging",
        "adverb": "arguably"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tough-scrummagingwhopropwhoJulianwhoWhitewhoiswhoexpectingwhoawhoresurgentwhoWaleswhotowhogivewhohimwhoawhoroughwhoridewhoinwhoEngland'swhoSixwhoNationswhoopenerwhoinwhoCardiffwhoonwhoSaturday.\r\nThewhoLeicesterwhotight-headwhoiswhoinwhothewhoformwhoofwhohiswholife,whomakingwhothewhoEnglandwhonumberwhothreewhoshirtwhohiswhoown.\r\nThewho31-year-oldwhohaswhomadewhoawhomassivewhocontributionwhotowhothewhoEnglandwhoandwhoLeicesterwhocausewhoofwholatewhoandwhoiswhoarguablywhothewhoformwhotight-headwhopropwhoinwhothewhoworld.\r\n\"ButwhomywhoformwhoiswhohelpedwhobywhothewhopeoplewhoIwhoplaywhowithwhoatwhoLeicesterwho-whopeoplewholikewhoMartinwhoJohnsonwhoandwhoGrahamwhoRowntree.\r\n\"Iwhodon'twhoknowwhohowwhomuchwhoexperiencewhoawhotight-headwhocanwhogivewhoawhocentrewhobutwhoyouwhoarewhotherewhotowhogivewhothemwhoawhopatwhoonwhothewhobackwhoifwhothingswhogowhowrongwhoorwhotowhobewhotherewhoifwhotheywhowantwhotowhotalkwhoinwhoanywhoway,\"whohewhoadded.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Italy led 9-8 early in the second half but Stringer's try gave Ireland a lead they never lost.\r\nThe hosts cut the gap to 18-12 with 10 minutes left and nearly scored through Ludovico Nitoglia, but Denis Hickie's try ensured an Irish victory.\r\nThe only Ireland player offering a real threat was O'Driscoll, and it was his break that set up the second try for the visitors.\r\nMurphy, Horgan, O'Driscoll, D'Arcy, Hickie, O'Gara, Stringer, Corrigan, Byrne, Hayes, O'Kelly, O'Connell, S Easterby, Leamy, Foley.",
    "id": "N_313",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Italy",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "led",
        "adjective": "early",
        "adverb": "never"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Italywholedwho9-8whoearlywhoinwhothewhosecondwhohalfwhobutwhoStringer'swhotrywhogavewhoIrelandwhoawholeadwhotheywhoneverwholost.\r\nThewhohostswhocutwhothewhogapwhotowho18-12whowithwho10whominuteswholeftwhoandwhonearlywhoscoredwhothroughwhoLudovicowhoNitoglia,whobutwhoDeniswhoHickie'swhotrywhoensuredwhoanwhoIrishwhovictory.\r\nThewhoonlywhoIrelandwhoplayerwhoofferingwhoawhorealwhothreatwhowaswhoO'Driscoll,whoandwhoitwhowaswhohiswhobreakwhothatwhosetwhoupwhothewhosecondwhotrywhoforwhothewhovisitors.\r\nMurphy,whoHorgan,whoO'Driscoll,whoD'Arcy,whoHickie,whoO'Gara,whoStringer,whoCorrigan,whoByrne,whoHayes,whoO'Kelly,whoO'Connell,whoSwhoEasterby,whoLeamy,whoFoley.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England coach Andy Robinson, who names his team on Wednesday, has called up Bath prop Duncan Bell following Phil Vickery's broken arm.\r\nBell, who featured in the England A side which beat France 30-20 10 days ago, added: \"I recognise that I got into the England A squad because of injuries.",
    "id": "N_314",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "names",
        "adjective": "arm.",
        "adverb": "ago,"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England coach Andy Robinson, who names his team on Wednesday, has called up what prop Duncan Bell following Phil Vickery's broken arm.\r\nBell, who featured in the England A side which beat France 30-20 10 days ago, added: \"I recognise that I got into the England A squad because of injuries.?",
        "answer": "Bath"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Once we're in the Six Nations, the players will only be released in his and the WRU's best interests.\" The Ospreys and Scarlets say they are happy to support the Wales cause, but the Dragons have expressed disappointment at not being able to use their national squad players in Friday's game with Ulster.\r\n\"I'm sure the guys would want to come back to get some game time,\" Forster told BBC Wales Sport.",
    "id": "N_315",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"Once",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "best",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Munster's Heineken Cup quarter-final tie against Biarritz on 3 April has been switched to Real Sociedad's Paseo de Anoeta stadium in San Sebastian.",
    "id": "N_316",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Munster's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "quarter-final",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Munster's Heineken Cup quarter-final what against Biarritz on 3 April has been switched to Real Sociedad's Paseo de Anoeta stadium in San Sebastian.?",
        "answer": "tie"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Defiant Matt Williams says he will not quit as Scotland coach even if his side slump to a new low with defeat by Italy at Murrayfield.\r\nIt is so absurd that it borders on the humorous.\" Williams insists that he is revelling in the pressure, despite the possibility of a second Six Nations series without a victory.",
    "id": "N_317",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Defiant",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Defiant Matt Williams says who will not quit as Scotland coach even if his side slump to a new low with defeat by Italy at Murrayfield.\r\nIt is so absurd that it borders on twho humorous.\" Williams insists that who is revelling in twho pressure, despite twho possibility of a second Six Nations series without a victory.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Northampton coach Budge Pountney has been fined \u00c2\u00a32,000 and banned from match-day coaching for six weeks for calling a referee \"a disgrace\".",
    "id": "N_318",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Northampton",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "match-day",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "NorthamptonwhocoachwhoBudgewhoPountneywhohaswhobeenwhofinedwho\u00c2\u00a32,000whoandwhobannedwhofromwhomatch-daywhocoachingwhoforwhosixwhoweekswhoforwhocallingwhoawhorefereewho\"awhodisgrace\".?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "They also have a good record at the Stade de France, having won their first two games there, in 1999 and 2001.\r\nWales coach Mike Ruddock is determined that his team will not go into their shells after their promising start to the championship.\r\n\"Graham Henry (former Wales coach) said a couple of years ago that we should 'be bold' when going to France, and he was proved right,\" said Ruddock.\r\n\"Against Wales, which is different from the teams we have beaten, I hope we can show our proper game.\"",
    "id": "N_319",
    "features": {
        "noun": "record",
        "pronoun": "They",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "good",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "TheywhoalsowhohavewhoawhogoodwhorecordwhoatwhothewhoStadewhodewhoFrance,whohavingwhowonwhotheirwhofirstwhotwowhogameswhothere,whoinwho1999whoandwho2001.\r\nWaleswhocoachwhoMikewhoRuddockwhoiswhodeterminedwhothatwhohiswhoteamwhowillwhonotwhogowhointowhotheirwhoshellswhoafterwhotheirwhopromisingwhostartwhotowhothewhochampionship.\r\n\"GrahamwhoHenrywho(formerwhoWaleswhocoach)whosaidwhoawhocouplewhoofwhoyearswhoagowhothatwhowewhoshouldwho'bewhobold'whowhenwhogoingwhotowhoFrance,whoandwhohewhowaswhoprovedwhoright,\"whosaidwhoRuddock.\r\n\"AgainstwhoWales,whowhichwhoiswhodifferentwhofromwhothewhoteamswhowewhohavewhobeaten,whoIwhohopewhowewhocanwhoshowwhoourwhoproperwhogame.\"?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Toulouse's former Irish international Trevor Brennan could be one of Clive Woodward's many surprises when the 44-man Lions tour squad is announced.\r\n\"If you speak to the players there's a huge amount of respect for the guy,\" Woodward told the Sunday Independent.",
    "id": "N_320",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Toulouse's",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "former",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Toulouse's former Irish international Trevor Brennan could be one of Clive Woodward's many surprises when the 44-man Lions tour what is announced.\r\n\"If you speak to the players there's a huge amount of respect for the guy,\" Woodward told the Sunday Independent.?",
        "answer": "squad"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "And the pressure is on Scotland coach Matt Williams as he seeks a first Six Nations victory at the eighth attempt.\r\nItaly have lost both their opening games at home to Ireland and Wales, but travel to Edinburgh with high hopes.\r\n\"It will be fundamental to keep cool in the difficult moments - in the key situations of the game.\" Kirwan has recalled the experienced Cristian Stoica at centre and drafted in David dal Maso at open-side after star flanker Mauro Bergamasco was ruled out for the rest of the tournament.\r\n\"I actually really enjoy seeing how you cope with such pressure as a coach,\" he said, optimistic despite opening defeats to France and Ireland.",
    "id": "N_321",
    "features": {
        "noun": "pressure",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "open-side"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ireland are going for their first Grand Slam since 1948 after two opening wins, and England represent their sternest test of the Championship so far.\r\nDespite England's dramatic dip in form since the World Cup final - they have lost eight of their last 13 matches - Ireland coach Eddie O'Sullivan says his side should not underestimate the visitors.\r\nIreland, despite having Gordon D'Arcy still out injured, have been boosted by the return of star skipper Brian O'Driscoll who missed the Scotland game with a hamstring injury.\r\nBut Robinson was bullish during the week about the game, saying that his side \"are going there to get in their faces\", and has identified the line-out and tackle area as the key to England's chances.\r\nAnd despite the recent results, skipper Jason Robinson believes there is nothing wrong with the mood in the camp.",
    "id": "N_322",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ireland",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "IrelandwhoarewhogoingwhoforwhotheirwhofirstwhoGrandwhoSlamwhosincewho1948whoafterwhotwowhoopeningwhowins,whoandwhoEnglandwhorepresentwhotheirwhosternestwhotestwhoofwhothewhoChampionshipwhosowhofar.\r\nDespitewhoEngland'swhodramaticwhodipwhoinwhoformwhosincewhothewhoWorldwhoCupwhofinalwho-whotheywhohavewholostwhoeightwhoofwhotheirwholastwho13whomatcheswho-whoIrelandwhocoachwhoEddiewhoO'Sullivanwhosayswhohiswhosidewhoshouldwhonotwhounderestimatewhothewhovisitors.\r\nIreland,whodespitewhohavingwhoGordonwhoD'Arcywhostillwhooutwhoinjured,whohavewhobeenwhoboostedwhobywhothewhoreturnwhoofwhostarwhoskipperwhoBrianwhoO'DriscollwhowhowhomissedwhothewhoScotlandwhogamewhowithwhoawhohamstringwhoinjury.\r\nButwhoRobinsonwhowaswhobullishwhoduringwhothewhoweekwhoaboutwhothewhogame,whosayingwhothatwhohiswhosidewho\"arewhogoingwhotherewhotowhogetwhoinwhotheirwhofaces\",whoandwhohaswhoidentifiedwhothewholine-outwhoandwhotacklewhoareawhoaswhothewhokeywhotowhoEngland'swhochances.\r\nAndwhodespitewhothewhorecentwhoresults,whoskipperwhoJasonwhoRobinsonwhobelieveswhotherewhoiswhonothingwhowrongwhowithwhothewhomoodwhoinwhothewhocamp.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Leeds: Balshaw; Rees, Christophers, Bell, Doherty; McMullen, Dickens; McGee, Rawlinson, Gerber; Murphy, Palmer (capt), Morgan, Parks, Popham.\r\nSaracens: Bartholomeusz; Castaignede, Sorrell, Harris, Vaikona; Jackson, Bracken; Yates, Ibanez, Visagie; Raiwalui, Fullarton; Randell, Russell, Vyvyan (capt).",
    "id": "N_323",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Leeds:",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "They make just one change, with Tim Collier replacing Phil Murphy in the second row.\r\nHanley; Mayor, Payne, Rhys Jones, Wigglesworth; Hercus, Redpath (capt); Turner, Roddam, Stewart; Day, Schofield; Caillet, Carter, Chabal.",
    "id": "N_324",
    "features": {
        "noun": "change,",
        "pronoun": "They",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "They make just one change, with Tim who replacing Phil Murphy in the second row.\r\nHanley; Mayor, Payne, Rhys Jones, Wigglesworth; Hercus, Redpath (capt); Turner, Roddam, Stewart; Day, Schofield; Caillet, Carter, Chabal.?",
        "answer": "Collier"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Robinson said: \"We are certainly not on the decline.\r\nBut full-back Robinson believes the new-look England team can stop the rot against France.\r\nWe will come out fighting this week.\" Robinson also had words of comfort for 18-year-old Newcastle centre Mathew Tait, who made his international debut against Wales but has been demoted from the squad to face France.",
    "id": "N_325",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Robinson",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "full-back",
        "adverb": "certainly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Robinson said: \"who are certainly not on the decline.\r\nBut full-back Robinson believes the new-look England team can stop the rot against France.\r\nwho will come out fighting this week.\" Robinson also had words of comfort for 18-year-old Newcastle centre Mathew Tait, who made his international debut against Wales but has been demoted from the squad to face France.?",
        "answer": "We"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former France centre Philippe Sella believes coach Bernard Laporte must recall Frederic Michalak to give his side any chance of beating Ireland.\r\n\"This season is very important for shaping a team for the 2007 World Cup,\" said Sella, \"which Laporte is doing very well.\r\n\"Ok, the flair may not have been so good, but the discipline, organisation and defence was there, which are all important ahead of 2007.\" France play what Sella believes is their hardest game of the Six Nations against Ireland in Dublin on Saturday 12 March.\r\nBut Sella added: \"People forget that France can still win the Six Nations and they'll be focused on that.",
    "id": "N_326",
    "features": {
        "noun": "France",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "Former",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former France centre Philippe Sella believes coach Bernard who must recall Frederic Michalak to give his side any chance of beating Ireland.\r\n\"This season is very important for shaping a team for the 2007 World Cup,\" said Sella, \"which who is doing very well.\r\n\"Ok, the flair may not have been so good, but the discipline, organisation and defence was there, which are all important ahead of 2007.\" France play what Sella believes is their hardest game of the Six Nations against Ireland in Dublin on Saturday 12 March.\r\nBut Sella added: \"People forget that France can still win the Six Nations and they'll be focused on that.?",
        "answer": "Laporte"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "All Blacks captain Tama Umaga has warned the British and Irish Lions will be his most fearsome opponents yet ahead of their summer tour.\r\nBut Umaga, in England for Saturday's IRB Rugby Aid match, also backed New Zealand to win the three-Test series against the Lions.\r\nUmaga will meet O'Driscoll in Saturday's Rugby Aid match at Twickenham, with the Irish captain leading the Northern Hemisphere side.\r\nO'Driscoll is among a host of players in the Northern Hemisphere squad, coached by Woodward, that are tipped for Lions call-ups.\r\nThe 31-year-old admitted interest in the Lions tour was immense, calling it \"the biggest thing to hit New Zealand since Lord of the Rings\".",
    "id": "N_327",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Blacks",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "captain",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "most"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "All Blacks captain Tama Umaga has warned the British and Irish Lions will be his most fearsome opponents yet ahead of their summer tour.\r\nBut Umaga, in England for Saturday's IRB Rugby Aid match, also backed New Zealand to win the three-Test series against the Lions.\r\nUmaga will meet O'Driscoll in Saturday's Rugby Aid match at Twickenham, with the Irish captain leading the Northern Hemisphere side.\r\nO'Driscoll is among a host of players in the Northern Hemisphere squad, coached by Woodward, that are tipped for Lions call-ups.\r\nThe 31-year-old admitted interest in the Lions tour was immense, calling it \"the biggest thing to hit New Zealand since Lord of the Rings\".",
    "id": "N_328",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Blacks",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "captain",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "most"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former Australian wing David Campese has told England to stop whingeing in the wake of their defeat to Ireland.\r\nEngland coach Andy Robinson lambasted referee Jonathan Kaplan for costing them the game after disallowing tries from Mark Cueto and Josh Lewsey.\r\nBut Campese added: \"Scotland could have beaten France in the same way, but do you see them whingeing?\r\nCampese, a veteran of 101 international caps, said full-back Jason Robinson would now be the sole Englishman in his World XV.\r\nThat said, I don't think they will.\" Campese has tipped Wales to win both the Six Nations and Grand Slam come the end of the tournament.",
    "id": "N_329",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "them",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "referee",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former Australian wing David Campese has told England to stop whingeing in the wake of their defeat to which location.\r\nEngland coach Andy Robinson lambasted referee Jonathan Kaplan for costing them the game after disallowing tries from Mark Cueto and Josh Lewsey.\r\nBut Campese added: \"Scotland could have beaten France in the same way, but do you see them whingeing?\r\nCampese, a veteran of 101 international caps, said full-back Jason Robinson would now be the sole Englishman in his World XV.\r\nThat said, I don't think they will.\" Campese has tipped Wales to win both the Six Nations and Grand Slam come the end of the tournament.?",
        "answer": "Ireland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "But Leicester's England centre Ollie Smith has been added to the squad, giving him an opportunity to impress Lions coach Sir Clive Woodward, who takes charge of the North side.\r\n\"He was probably going to have the weekend off this week and I hope Clive gets the chance to see the qualities that Leicester and England have been seeing all year.\" Woodward will also assess other potential Lions candidates such as Scotland pair Simon Taylor and Chris Paterson, Wales scrum-half Dwayne Peel and Ireland lock Paul O'Connell.\r\n\"Both teams are fielding top-quality sides and I really hope that the rugby public and community get behind this game to raise as much money as possible for such a deserving cause.\" Despite the withdrawal of Wales wing Rhys Williams, who is required for the Blues' Celtic League match with Munster, three other members of their Six Nations squad - Ceri Sweeney, John Yapp and Jonathan Thomas - will also play.",
    "id": "N_330",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Leicester's",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Clive",
        "adverb": "probably"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Number eight Imanol Harinordoquy has been dropped from France's squad for the Six Nations match with Ireland in Dublin on 12 March.\r\nHarinordoquy was a second-half replacement in last Saturday's 24-18 defeat to Wales.\r\n\"It will be a very exciting game because Ireland have three wins under their belt, have just defeated England and have their eyes set on a Grand Slam.\" France, who lost to Wales last week, must defeat the Irish to keep alive their hopes of retaining the Six Nations trophy.",
    "id": "N_331",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Number",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "second-half",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Number eight Imanol who has been dropped from France's squad for the Six Nations match with Ireland in Dublin on 12 March.\r\nwho was a second-half replacement in last Saturday's 24-18 defeat to Wales.\r\n\"It will be a very exciting game because Ireland have three wins under their belt, have just defeated England and have their eyes set on a Grand Slam.\" France, who lost to Wales last week, must defeat the Irish to keep alive their hopes of retaining the Six Nations trophy.?",
        "answer": "Harinordoquy"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tom Shanklin will start in the centre for Wales against England in Cardiff on Saturday after Sonny Parker failed to recover from a trapped neck nerve.\r\nWilliams, Sidoli's team-mate at Cardiff, is set to win his 50th cap, replacing the injured Colin Charvis after making a quicker-than-expected recovery from a neck disc problem.\r\n\"They were back-ups behind Richard Hill, Neil Back and Lawrence Dallaglio, but now they have come forward and proved what good players they are - there are no weaknesses there.\" Luscombe gets the nod on the wing ahead of Dragons team-mate Kevin Morgan, who wins a place on the bench alongside uncapped Blues prop John Yapp.",
    "id": "N_332",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tom",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "start",
        "adjective": "50th",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tom Shanklin will start in the centre for Wales against England in Cardiff on Saturday after Sonny who failed to recover from a trapped neck nerve.\r\nWilliams, Sidoli's team-mate at Cardiff, is set to win his 50th cap, replacing the injured Colin Charvis after making a quicker-than-expected recovery from a neck disc problem.\r\n\"They were back-ups behind Richard Hill, Neil Back and Lawrence Dallaglio, but now they have come forward and proved what good players they are - there are no weaknesses there.\" Luscombe gets the nod on the wing ahead of Dragons team-mate Kevin Morgan, who wins a place on the bench alongside uncapped Blues prop John Yapp.?",
        "answer": "Parker"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England have named Bath prop Matt Stevens in the starting line-up for their Six Nations match against Ireland at Lansdowne Road on Sunday.\r\nFellow Bath prop Duncan Bell will start on the bench, as coach Andy Robinson makes just one change to the team that was beaten by France.",
    "id": "N_333",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England have named who prop Matt Stevens in the starting line-up for their Six Nations match against Ireland at Lansdowne Road on Sunday.\r\nFellow who prop Duncan Bell will start on the bench, as coach Andy Robinson makes just one change to the team that was beaten by France.?",
        "answer": "Bath"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Italy skipper Marco Bortolami believes Saturday's Six Nations contest against Scotland will be a scrappy encounter.\r\n\"Scotland played extremely well against France in Paris but not so well when Ireland came to Edinburgh,\" said Bortolami.",
    "id": "N_334",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Italy",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "scrappy",
        "adverb": "extremely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Italy skipper Marco Bortolami believes Saturday's Six Nations contest against which location will be a scrappy encounter.\r\n\"which location played extremely well against France in Paris but not so well when Ireland came to Edinburgh,\" said Bortolami.?",
        "answer": "Scotland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England forward Martin Corry says Jason Robinson is the right man to lead the national team back to winning ways.\r\nBut Corry has backed Robinson, who was given the role after the injury to fly-half Jonny Wilkinson, ahead of this weekend's trip to Ireland.\r\n\"There are a lot of changes taking place with England and we are at the start of something.\r\n\"They are full of confidence and are playing a great team game,\" he said.\r\n\"Lansdowne Road is a tremendous venue to play in and we have to use it to our advantage.\"",
    "id": "N_335",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "right",
        "adverb": "forward"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England forward Martin Corry says Jason who is the right man to lead the national team back to winning ways.\r\nBut Corry has backed who, who was given the role after the injury to fly-half Jonny Wilkinson, ahead of this weekend's trip to Ireland.\r\n\"There are a lot of changes taking place with England and we are at the start of something.\r\n\"They are full of confidence and are playing a great team game,\" he said.\r\n\"Lansdowne Road is a tremendous venue to play in and we have to use it to our advantage.\"?",
        "answer": "Robinson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Adam Jones says the Wales forwards are determined to set the perfect attacking platform for the backs by dominating the powerful France pack in Paris.\r\nIt's just up to us in the forwards to win the ball and give them the opportunity.\" Wales have won two of their last three visits to Stade de France, having secured back-to-back wins under Graham Henry in 1999 and 2001.\r\n\"Gethin [Jenkins] won't be intimidated tomorrow, none of us will,\" said Jones, who will be facing France for the first time.\r\n\"Me and Gethin are quite young so it is good to have someone of Mefin's experience in there.",
    "id": "N_336",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Adam",
        "pronoun": "us",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "perfect",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Adam Jones says the Wales forwards are determined to set the perfect attacking platform for the backs by dominating the powerful France pack in which location.\r\nIt's just up to us in the forwards to win the ball and give them the opportunity.\" Wales have won two of their last three visits to Stade de France, having secured back-to-back wins under Graham Henry in 1999 and 2001.\r\n\"Gethin [Jenkins] won't be intimidated tomorrow, none of us will,\" said Jones, who will be facing France for the first time.\r\n\"Me and Gethin are quite young so it is good to have someone of Mefin's experience in there.?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Lewis Moody has flown to Dublin to join England's camp ahead of their RBS Six Nations game against Ireland on Sunday.\r\nDespite joining the squad, the Leicester flanker only has a \"slim\" chance of playing because of an infection in his finger.\r\n\"The chances of him playing are very slim,\" said coach Andy Robinson.\r\nHe suffered the cut playing against France at Twickenham and it became infected during a 10-minute outing as a replacement for Leicester against Newcastle last Saturday.\r\nRobinson has confirmed that fly-half Charlie Hodgson will be the first-choice kicker despite his three missed penalties and a drop goal against France.",
    "id": "N_337",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Lewis",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "camp",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Lewis who has flown to Dublin to join England's camp ahead of their RBS Six Nations game against Ireland on Sunday.\r\nDespite joining the squad, the Leicester flanker only has a \"slim\" chance of playing because of an infection in his finger.\r\n\"The chances of him playing are very slim,\" said coach Andy Robinson.\r\nHe suffered the cut playing against France at Twickenham and it became infected during a 10-minute outing as a replacement for Leicester against Newcastle last Saturday.\r\nRobinson has confirmed that fly-half Charlie Hodgson will be the first-choice kicker despite his three missed penalties and a drop goal against France.?",
        "answer": "Moody"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ireland's Brian O'Driscoll is one of four Six Nations captains included in the Northern Hemisphere squad for the IRB Rugby Aid match on 5 March.\r\nSir Clive Woodward will coach the Northern team against Rod Macqueen's Southern Hemisphere team in a tsumani fund-raising match at Twickenham.",
    "id": "N_338",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ireland's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "tsumani",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ireland's Brian who is one of four Six Nations captains included in the Northern Hemisphere squad for the IRB Rugby Aid match on 5 March.\r\nSir Clive Woodward will coach the Northern team against Rod Macqueen's Southern Hemisphere team in a tsumani fund-raising match at Twickenham.?",
        "answer": "O'Driscoll"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former France fly-half Thomas Castaignede has warned the pressure is mounting on coach Bernard Laporte following their defeat by Wales.\r\nFrance suffered a shock loss against the Welsh at the weekend after looking on course for an easy win.\r\nCastaignede told BBC Sport: \"The pressure is big on Laporte after a huge loss to New Zealand, a slim win over Scotland and a miracle against England.\r\n\"Going to Ireland is never easy but the way they're playing right now, it's harder than ever,\" said Castaignede.",
    "id": "N_339",
    "features": {
        "noun": "France",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Former",
        "adverb": "never"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former France fly-half Thomas Castaignede has warned the what is mounting on coach Bernard Laporte following their defeat by Wales.\r\nFrance suffered a shock loss against the Welsh at the weekend after looking on course for an easy win.\r\nCastaignede told BBC Sport: \"The what is big on Laporte after a huge loss to New Zealand, a slim win over Scotland and a miracle against England.\r\n\"Going to Ireland is never easy but the way they're playing right now, it's harder than ever,\" said Castaignede.?",
        "answer": "pressure"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sonny Parker is continuing to struggle with a neck injury, but Hal Luscombe should be fit for the Murrayfield trip.\r\nSaid Wales assistant coach Scott Johnson: \"We're positive about Hal and hope he'll be raring to go.",
    "id": "N_340",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sonny",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "assistant",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "SonnywhoParkerwhoiswhocontinuingwhotowhostrugglewhowithwhoawhoneckwhoinjury,whobutwhoHalwhoLuscombewhoshouldwhobewhofitwhoforwhothewhoMurrayfieldwhotrip.\r\nSaidwhoWaleswhoassistantwhocoachwhoScottwhoJohnson:who\"We'rewhopositivewhoaboutwhoHalwhoandwhohopewhohe'llwhobewhoraringwhotowhogo.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England captain Jason Robinson will miss the rest of the Six Nations because of injury.\r\nRobinson, stand-in captain in the absence of Jonny Wilkinson, had been due to lead England in their final two games against Italy and Scotland.\r\nRobinson said: \"This is very disappointing for me as this means I miss England's last two games in the Six Nations at Twickenham and two games for my club, Sale Sharks.",
    "id": "N_341",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "me",
        "verb": "miss",
        "adjective": "injury.",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England captain Jason who will miss the rest of the Six Nations because of injury.\r\nwho, stand-in captain in the absence of Jonny Wilkinson, had been due to lead England in their final two games against Italy and Scotland.\r\nwho said: \"This is very disappointing for me as this means I miss England's last two games in the Six Nations at Twickenham and two games for my club, Sale Sharks.?",
        "answer": "Robinson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England coach Andy Robinson is facing disciplinary action after criticising referee Jonathan Kaplan in his side's Six Nations defeat to Ireland.\r\nAfter reviewing tapes of the match, the RFU decided not to formally complain to the IRB over the standard of Kaplan's refereeing.",
    "id": "N_342",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "disciplinary",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England coach Andy Robinson is facing disciplinary action after criticising referee Jonathan Kaplan in his side's Six Nations defeat to which location.\r\nAfter reviewing tapes of the match, the RFU decided not to formally complain to the IRB over the standard of Kaplan's refereeing.?",
        "answer": "Ireland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Number eight Imanol Harinordoquy has been dropped from France's squad for the Six Nations match with Ireland in Dublin on 12 March.\r\nHarinordoquy was a second-half replacement in last Saturday's 24-18 defeat to Wales.\r\n\"It will be a very exciting game because Ireland have three wins under their belt, have just defeated England and have their eyes set on a Grand Slam.\" France, who lost to Wales last week, must defeat the Irish to keep alive their hopes of retaining the Six Nations trophy.",
    "id": "N_343",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Number",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "second-half",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Number eight Imanol who has been dropped from France's squad for the Six Nations match with Ireland in Dublin on 12 March.\r\nwho was a second-half replacement in last Saturday's 24-18 defeat to Wales.\r\n\"It will be a very exciting game because Ireland have three wins under their belt, have just defeated England and have their eyes set on a Grand Slam.\" France, who lost to Wales last week, must defeat the Irish to keep alive their hopes of retaining the Six Nations trophy.?",
        "answer": "Harinordoquy"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England's World Cup-winning fly-half said last week he was hoping to recover from his latest injury in time to play some role in the championship.\r\nBut Rob Andrew, coach of Wilkinson's club side Newcastle, said that with only two games left to play Wilkinson was unlikely to be fit in time.\r\n\"It would be irresponsible to put him straight into a Test match,\" Andrew told the Times.",
    "id": "N_344",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England's",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England's World Cup-winning fly-half said last week who was hoping to recover from his latest injury in time to play some role in twho championship.\r\nBut Rob Andrew, coach of Wilkinson's club side Newcastle, said that with only two games left to play Wilkinson was unlikely to be fit in time.\r\n\"It would be irresponsible to put him straight into a Test match,\" Andrew told twho Times.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England will protest to the International Rugby Board (IRB) about the referee's performance in the defeat by Ireland, reports the Daily Mail.\r\nEngland coach Andy Robinson has called on ex-international referees Colin High and Steve Lander to analyse several of Jonathan Kaplan's decisions.",
    "id": "N_345",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "protest",
        "adjective": "ex-international",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England will protest to the International Rugby Board (IRB) about the referee's performance in the defeat by which location, reports the Daily Mail.\r\nEngland coach Andy Robinson has called on ex-international referees Colin High and Steve Lander to analyse several of Jonathan Kaplan's decisions.?",
        "answer": "Ireland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "That's not a reflection on Robinson personally.\" He added: \"I just think the point of influence needs to move closer to the pack - which is, after all, where games usually start and finish.\" Moore says a lack of cohesion in the forwards is one of the reasons why England have lost against Wales, France and Ireland in this year's tournament.\r\n\"Wer'e not getting quick ball, which means the backs are being stifled.\r\n\"The problem is the players that are around to replace the icons which have been lost because of retirement and injury don't have the requisite experience,\" Moore added.",
    "id": "N_346",
    "features": {
        "noun": "That's",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "added:",
        "adjective": "\"I",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "That"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"It's an easy job really because there are so many experienced players in the side, but it will be a massive honour.\" Coach Mike Ruddock says the 24-year-old should take the armband from broken thumb victim Thomas against Scotland.\r\nRuddock praised Owen's contribution as vice-captain and pack leader in this year's wins over England, Italy and France, notably his role in the second-half in Paris following Thomas' injury.\r\n\"Gareth is going to be a massive loss because he is a brilliant player and he has done a fantastic job since he has been captain,\" said Owen.",
    "id": "N_347",
    "features": {
        "noun": "job",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "\"It's",
        "adjective": "easy",
        "adverb": "really"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"But I have a lot of confidence in my players and I am positive we can put everything together against England.\" England, meanwhile, are licking their wounds and rueing what might have been had two decisions from referee Jonathan Kaplan not gone against them in the second half in Dublin.\r\n\"We have got to make sure we now take the form and positives into the Italy game.\r\nWe are under no illusions that it is going to be easy, but we definitely need a win.\" England have now equalled an 18-year low of four successive championship defeats, including France in Paris last season, and have lost four in a row under Andy Robinson.",
    "id": "N_348",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"But",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "positive",
        "adverb": "together"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "David dal Maso has been handed the task of replacing the injured Mauro Bergamasco at flanker in Italy's team to face Scotland on Saturday.",
    "id": "N_349",
    "features": {
        "noun": "David",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "injured",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "David dal who has been handed the task of replacing the injured Mauro Bergamasco at flanker in Italy's team to face Scotland on Saturday.?",
        "answer": "Maso"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "In another change to the side that lost to Australia in November, Leicester lock Ben Kay replaces Bath second row Steve Borthwick.\r\nJ Robinson (Sale Sharks, capt); M Cueto (Sale Sharks), M Tait (Newcastle), J Noon (Newcastle), J Lewsey (Wasps); C Hodgson (Sale Sharks), M Dawson (Wasps); G Rowntree (Leicester), S Thompson (Northampton), J White (Leicester), D Grewcock (Bath), B Kay (Leicester), L Moody (Leicester), A Hazell (Gloucester), J Worsley (Wasps).",
    "id": "N_350",
    "features": {
        "noun": "change",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "lost",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "In another change to the side that lost to Australia in November, Leicester lock Ben who replaces Bath second row Steve Borthwick.\r\nJ Robinson (Sale Sharks, capt); M Cueto (Sale Sharks), M Tait (Newcastle), J Noon (Newcastle), J Lewsey (Wasps); C Hodgson (Sale Sharks), M Dawson (Wasps); G Rowntree (Leicester), S Thompson (Northampton), J White (Leicester), D Grewcock (Bath), B who (Leicester), L Moody (Leicester), A Hazell (Gloucester), J Worsley (Wasps).?",
        "answer": "Kay"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former captain Keith Wood believes Ireland can win only their second Grand Slam - and first since 1948 - in this year's RBS Six Nations Championship.\r\n\"Wales have had four brilliant games in the last year or so and lost all four, so the time is right for them now to beat one of the major teams.\"",
    "id": "N_351",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "them",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "FormerwhocaptainwhoKeithwhoWoodwhobelieveswhoIrelandwhocanwhowinwhoonlywhotheirwhosecondwhoGrandwhoSlamwho-whoandwhofirstwhosincewho1948who-whoinwhothiswhoyear'swhoRBSwhoSixwhoNationswhoChampionship.\r\n\"Waleswhohavewhohadwhofourwhobrilliantwhogameswhoinwhothewholastwhoyearwhoorwhosowhoandwholostwhoallwhofour,whosowhothewhotimewhoiswhorightwhoforwhothemwhonowwhotowhobeatwhoonewhoofwhothewhomajorwhoteams.\"?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Scotland's back row crisis has worsened ahead of the RBS Six Nations with news that Scott Gray will miss out on the opening matches.\r\nScotland doctor James Robson said: \"A scan has shown damage to the medial ligaments of Scott's right knee ruling him out of the first part of the Championship.",
    "id": "N_352",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Scotland's",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "\"A",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Scotland's back row crisis has worsened ahead of the RBS Six Nations with news that Scott who will miss out on the opening matches.\r\nScotland doctor James Robson said: \"A scan has shown damage to the medial ligaments of Scott's right knee ruling him out of the first part of the Championship.?",
        "answer": "Gray"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ireland coach Eddie O'Sullivan appears to have done that quite successfully in the run-up to this season's Six Nations Championship.\r\nBar Keith Gleeson who is just returning from a broken leg, everyone of O'Sullivan's squad is fit, fresh and standing at the oche ready to launch this season's campaign.\r\nAlready Ireland are being earmarked as hot favourites in many quarters to go the whole hog this season.\r\nThey were expected to up the ante further for a Grand Slam, only the second in Ireland's history.\r\nBut O'Sullivan's side are very capable of proving a salient point this season.\r\nHe has some old dogs in his squad, but he will come to this season's championship with a different box of tricks, and a new verve to succeed.",
    "id": "N_353",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ireland",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "appears",
        "adjective": "broken",
        "adverb": "quite"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ireland coach Eddie who appears to have done that quite successfully in the run-up to this season's Six Nations Championship.\r\nBar Keith Gleeson who is just returning from a broken leg, everyone of who's squad is fit, fresh and standing at the oche ready to launch this season's campaign.\r\nAlready Ireland are being earmarked as hot favourites in many quarters to go the whole hog this season.\r\nThey were expected to up the ante further for a Grand Slam, only the second in Ireland's history.\r\nBut who's side are very capable of proving a salient point this season.\r\nHe has some old dogs in his squad, but he will come to this season's championship with a different box of tricks, and a new verve to succeed.?",
        "answer": "O'Sullivan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales' other injury concern is Pugh's fellow Neath-Swansea Ospreys player Sonny Parker, as the centre has a trapped nerve in his neck.\r\n\"Sonny's injury is still an issue,\" Davies said.",
    "id": "N_354",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales'",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "other",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wales' other injury concern is Pugh's fellow Neath-Swansea Ospreys player Sonny Parker, as the what has a trapped nerve in his neck.\r\n\"Sonny's injury is still an issue,\" Davies said.?",
        "answer": "centre"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Scrum-half Matt Dawson is an injury doubt for England's Six Nations opener against Wales next weekend.",
    "id": "N_355",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Matt",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "Scrum-half",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Scrum-half Matt who is an injury doubt for England's Six Nations opener against Wales next weekend.?",
        "answer": "Dawson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales could follow England's lead by training with a rugby league club.\r\nEngland have already had a three-day session with Leeds Rhinos, and Wales are thought to be interested in a similar clinic with rivals St Helens.",
    "id": "N_356",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "follow",
        "adjective": "three-day",
        "adverb": "already"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who could follow England's lead by training with a rugby league club.\r\nEngland have already had a three-day session with Leeds Rhinos, and who are thought to be interested in a similar clinic with rivals St Helens.?",
        "answer": "Wales"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sale Sharks director of rugby Philippe Saint-Andre has re-opened rugby's club-versus-country debate.\r\nSale host Bath in the Powergen Cup on Friday, but the Frenchman has endured a \"difficult week\" with six players away on England's Six Nations training camp.\r\nUnless the authorities agree to make changes, Saint-Andre believes England's national team will suffer as clubs opt to sign foreigners and retired internationals.\r\nGloucester have also been caught in a club-versus-country conflict after England sought a second medical opinion on James Simpson-Daniel's fitness.",
    "id": "N_357",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sale",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "rugby",
        "adverb": "away"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Sale Sharks director of rugby Philippe which location has re-opened rugby's club-versus-country debate.\r\nSale host Bath in the Powergen Cup on Friday, but the Frenchman has endured a \"difficult week\" with six players away on England's Six Nations training camp.\r\nUnless the authorities agree to make changes, which location believes England's national team will suffer as clubs opt to sign foreigners and retired internationals.\r\nGloucester have also been caught in a club-versus-country conflict after England sought a second medical opinion on James Simpson-Daniel's fitness.?",
        "answer": "Saint-Andre"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The 21-year-old Blues prop is the only uncapped player in Wales' Six Nations squad, gaining a chance in the absence of Ospreys loose-head Duncan Jones.\r\n\"He has international size, is a big, physical lad and a good ball-carrier with a high tackle-count.\" Ruddock's assessment was backed up by Yapp's coach at the Blues, former Wales and Lions prop Dai Young.\r\nRuddock hopes that the selection of Yapp and Dragons lock Ian Gough - out of the international reckoning since falling out with former coach Steve Hansen - will send a message to other players in Wales.",
    "id": "N_358",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Blues",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "21-year-old",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "Blues"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I think players are probably going to have three or four years taken off their careers.\" Robinson will be missing an entire midfield for the Six Nations with the likes of Jonny Wilkinson, Mike Tindall and Will Greenwood injured.\r\nRugby union has become far more physically demanding since the game went professional nearly 10 years ago.",
    "id": "N_359",
    "features": {
        "noun": "think",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "\"I",
        "adverb": "probably"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Realising I would be unable to play this season, the club and I agreed to end my contract early,\" said Hodges.\r\n\"I'm positive about the future of the Scarlets both on and off the field.\" Gallacher was keen to pay tribute to the role back-five forward Hodges has played at Stradey Park, though.",
    "id": "N_360",
    "features": {
        "noun": "season,",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "\"Realising",
        "adjective": "unable",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"RealisingwhatIwhatwouldwhatbewhatunablewhattowhatplaywhatthiswhatseason,whatthewhatclubwhatandwhatIwhatagreedwhattowhatendwhatmywhatcontractwhatearly,\"whatsaidwhatHodges.\r\n\"I'mwhatpositivewhataboutwhatthewhatfuturewhatofwhatthewhatScarletswhatbothwhatonwhatandwhatoffwhatthewhatfield.\"whatGallacherwhatwaswhatkeenwhattowhatpaywhattributewhattowhatthewhatrolewhatback-fivewhatforwardwhatHodgeswhathaswhatplayedwhatatwhatStradeywhatPark,whatthough.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Welsh Students Rugby Football Union feels that it is unable to properly prepare for or stage the matches.\r\nThe secretary of the Welsh Students Rugby Football Union, Reverend Eldon Phillips, said: \"It is a shame that fixtures cannot be maintained this year.",
    "id": "N_361",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Welsh",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "feels",
        "adjective": "unable",
        "adverb": "properly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoWelshwhoStudentswhoRugbywhoFootballwhoUnionwhofeelswhothatwhoitwhoiswhounablewhotowhoproperlywhopreparewhoforwhoorwhostagewhothewhomatches.\r\nThewhosecretarywhoofwhothewhoWelshwhoStudentswhoRugbywhoFootballwhoUnion,whoReverendwhoEldonwhoPhillips,whosaid:who\"Itwhoiswhoawhoshamewhothatwhofixtureswhocannotwhobewhomaintainedwhothiswhoyear.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former Scotland international Finlay Calder fears civil war at the SRU could seriously hamper his country's RBS Six Nations campaign.\r\nAnd Calder said: \"This is terrible news for every level of Scottish rugby.\r\n\"He has been driven out by people who seem happier waging civil war than addressing the central issue that professional rugby can't be run by amateurs,\" said Calder.",
    "id": "N_362",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "fears",
        "adjective": "international",
        "adverb": "seriously"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former Scotland international Finlay Calder fears civil what at the SRU could seriously hamper his country's RBS Six Nations campaign.\r\nAnd Calder said: \"This is terrible news for every level of Scottish rugby.\r\n\"He has been driven out by people who seem happier waging civil what than addressing the central issue that professional rugby can't be run by amateurs,\" said Calder.?",
        "answer": "war"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "It has been quite a year for the Irish, and not just with Eddie O'Sullivan's Triple Crown winning international outfit either.\r\nFor the second year in succession they also finished in the runners-up spot in the RBS Six Nations.\r\nThe young Irish boys had stated their intentions earlier in the season when they finished runners-up to England in the Six Nations under-21 tournament.\r\nOn the provincial front, Leinster, for second year in succession, blew it when the Heineken Cup looked a good wager.\r\nWhile Ulster finished runners-up in their very tight group for the second season in succession, it was Munster again flying the flag for the Irish.\r\nUlster, meanwhile, just lost out to adding the inaugural Celtic Cup in winning the Celtic League when they were pipped at the post by the Scarlets in the final game.\r\nTeenage star John McCall died while playing for the Ireland against New Zealand in the under-19 World Cup game in Durban.",
    "id": "N_363",
    "features": {
        "noun": "year",
        "pronoun": "It",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "international",
        "adverb": "quite"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ItwhohaswhobeenwhoquitewhoawhoyearwhoforwhothewhoIrish,whoandwhonotwhojustwhowithwhoEddiewhoO'Sullivan'swhoTriplewhoCrownwhowinningwhointernationalwhooutfitwhoeither.\r\nForwhothewhosecondwhoyearwhoinwhosuccessionwhotheywhoalsowhofinishedwhoinwhothewhorunners-upwhospotwhoinwhothewhoRBSwhoSixwhoNations.\r\nThewhoyoungwhoIrishwhoboyswhohadwhostatedwhotheirwhointentionswhoearlierwhoinwhothewhoseasonwhowhenwhotheywhofinishedwhorunners-upwhotowhoEnglandwhoinwhothewhoSixwhoNationswhounder-21whotournament.\r\nOnwhothewhoprovincialwhofront,whoLeinster,whoforwhosecondwhoyearwhoinwhosuccession,whoblewwhoitwhowhenwhothewhoHeinekenwhoCupwholookedwhoawhogoodwhowager.\r\nWhilewhoUlsterwhofinishedwhorunners-upwhoinwhotheirwhoverywhotightwhogroupwhoforwhothewhosecondwhoseasonwhoinwhosuccession,whoitwhowaswhoMunsterwhoagainwhoflyingwhothewhoflagwhoforwhothewhoIrish.\r\nUlster,whomeanwhile,whojustwholostwhooutwhotowhoaddingwhothewhoinauguralwhoCelticwhoCupwhoinwhowinningwhothewhoCelticwhoLeaguewhowhenwhotheywhowerewhopippedwhoatwhothewhopostwhobywhothewhoScarletswhoinwhothewhofinalwhogame.\r\nTeenagewhostarwhoJohnwhoMcCallwhodiedwhowhilewhoplayingwhoforwhothewhoIrelandwhoagainstwhoNewwhoZealandwhoinwhothewhounder-19whoWorldwhoCupwhogamewhoinwhoDurban.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Matt Williams insists he has no thoughts of quitting as national coach as a result of the power struggle currently gripping Scottish rugby.\r\nBut Williams said: \"I want to make it clear that I'm committed totally to Scottish rugby.\r\n\"I'd like to stress that the national team is separate to the political situation,\" he said.\r\n\"There was some very unhelpful and uninformed comment that the national team had received a massive increase in budget at the expense of other parts of Scottish rugby and that is simply not the case.",
    "id": "N_364",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Matt",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "insists",
        "adjective": "national",
        "adverb": "currently"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Matt Williams insists who has no thoughts of quitting as national coach as a result of twho power struggle currently gripping Scottish rugby.\r\nBut Williams said: \"I want to make it clear that I'm committed totally to Scottish rugby.\r\n\"I'd like to stress that twho national team is separate to twho political situation,\" who said.\r\n\"Twhore was some very unwholpful and uninformed comment that twho national team had received a massive increase in budget at twho expense of otwhor parts of Scottish rugby and that is simply not twho case.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"The match on 4 June will be my first 15-man game but I have a training schedule which is quite testing and combines with sevens and a whole lot of things,\" said Lomu.\r\nComing back to rugby, people said 'you are dreaming' but it always starts off with a dream.\r\n\"I have talked this over, had a chat with the donor and this is to set my soul at peace and finish something I started in 1994 [when he made his All Blacks debut].\" At his lowest ebb Lomu was so ill he could barely walk, but he says he is now getting stronger every day and his long-term target is to play for New Zealand again.",
    "id": "N_365",
    "features": {
        "noun": "match",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "\"The",
        "adverb": "quite"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Thewhatmatchwhatonwhat4whatJunewhatwillwhatbewhatmywhatfirstwhat15-manwhatgamewhatbutwhatIwhathavewhatawhattrainingwhatschedulewhatwhichwhatiswhatquitewhattestingwhatandwhatcombineswhatwithwhatsevenswhatandwhatawhatwholewhatlotwhatofwhatthings,\"whatsaidwhatLomu.\r\nComingwhatbackwhattowhatrugby,whatpeoplewhatsaidwhat'youwhatarewhatdreaming'whatbutwhatitwhatalwayswhatstartswhatoffwhatwithwhatawhatdream.\r\n\"Iwhathavewhattalkedwhatthiswhatover,whathadwhatawhatchatwhatwithwhatthewhatdonorwhatandwhatthiswhatiswhattowhatsetwhatmywhatsoulwhatatwhatpeacewhatandwhatfinishwhatsomethingwhatIwhatstartedwhatinwhat1994what[whenwhathewhatmadewhathiswhatAllwhatBlackswhatdebut].\"whatAtwhathiswhatlowestwhatebbwhatLomuwhatwaswhatsowhatillwhathewhatcouldwhatbarelywhatwalk,whatbutwhathewhatsayswhathewhatiswhatnowwhatgettingwhatstrongerwhateverywhatdaywhatandwhathiswhatlong-termwhattargetwhatiswhattowhatplaywhatforwhatNewwhatZealandwhatagain.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former England captain Martin Johnson has announced he is to retire from rugby union at the end of the season.\r\nJohnson, who captained England to World Cup glory in 2003, will play his final match in June.\r\n\"This game against Jonah will be a great way to end the season and end my career,\" said Johnson.",
    "id": "N_366",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "final",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former England captain Martin Johnson has announced who is to retire from rugby union at twho end of twho season.\r\nJohnson, who captained England to World Cup glory in 2003, will play his final match in June.\r\n\"This game against Jonah will be a great way to end twho season and end my career,\" said Johnson.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "And for the first time in more than a decade, it will not simply be a straightforward choice between England and France for the Six Nations title.\r\nNot that England or France, who have won nine of the last 10 Six Nations titles between them, will lay down quietly.\r\nThe narrow defeat to Australia was a timely reminder that not everything is blooming in the red rose garden, but the fresh shoots of post-World Cup recovery have been sown by new head coach Andy Robinson.\r\nA fresh desire to regain former heights is evident, and if England emerge triumphant from an opening Six Nations engagement in Cardiff, a fourth title in six years is within reach.\r\nAfter two reasonable performances against Australia, the Scots' humbling by the Springboks forced coach Matt Williams to reassess his belief that a win over one of the major nations was imminent.\r\n, who start with home games against Ireland and Wales before travelling to Scotland, are also hopeful of registering more than one victory for the first time in the Championship.",
    "id": "N_367",
    "features": {
        "noun": "time",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "be",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "South Africa's Schalk Burger was named player of the year as the Tri-Nations champions swept the top honours at the International Rugby Board's awards.\r\n\"Schalk's emergence as a major force has meant a lot to South African rugby, but has also influenced world rugby,\" said White.",
    "id": "N_368",
    "features": {
        "noun": "South",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "top",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "champions"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England rugby union captain Jason Robinson has targeted dual code success over Australia on Saturday.\r\nAnd at 1815 GMT, Great Britain's rugby league team take on Australia in the final of the Tri-Nations tournament.\r\n\"If we beat Australia it would be the end to a great autumn series for England.",
    "id": "N_369",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "rugby",
        "adjective": "dual",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England rugby union captain Jason who has targeted dual code success over Australia on Saturday.\r\nAnd at 1815 GMT, Great Britain's rugby league team take on Australia in the final of the Tri-Nations tournament.\r\n\"If we beat Australia it would be the end to a great autumn series for England.?",
        "answer": "Robinson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "New Zealand played their first international against Australia in 1903, the Kiwis triumphing 22-3 in Sydney, and the following year an official British touring team came to New Zealand for the first time.\r\nThe first South Africa tour of New Zealand in 1921 saw honours shared in a three-Test series, starting the greatest rivalry in rugby - and the long-running controversy between the countries over the All Blacks' inclusion of Maori players.\r\nEmploying the modern 3-4-1 scrum line-up against the New Zealand 'rover' system for the first time, South African teams defeated the All Blacks in five games and the Test series was drawn two-all.\r\nThe All Blacks were on top in the Test with Wales at the Arms Park, but the teams were locked at 8-8 when a Clem Thomas cross kick was gathered by Ken Jones for a famous, match-winning try.\r\nWilson Whinneray's side rallied to beat Wales 6-0, their first win at the Arms Park in four attempts, and went unbeaten through the rest of the tour, but when they returned home the first question put to them was: \"What happened in Newport?\" The only blemish on the record of the awesome 1967 tourists was a draw with East Wales, as they beat the full Wales team 13-6 in Cardiff to take the lead in the series between the countries for the first time.\r\nThat lead was increased with two comfortable wins for the home side in New Zealand in 1969, the first time Wales had toured the country as an independent team.\r\nJames guided Llanelli to a famous 9-3 win over the tourists at Stradey Park, though, and in the final game of the tour the Barbarians defeated the All Blacks 23-11 in Cardiff in a game regarded by many as the greatest ever played.\r\nNew Zealand defeated a Wales XV 12-3 at the Arms Park in a non-cap game in 1974, but it was the 1978 game in Cardiff that would reignite the history of controversy between the two countries.\r\nA crushing 23-3 win for New Zealand in Cardiff in the Welsh Rugby Union's 1980 centenary game was a sign of things to come.\r\nThe new professionalism in the southern hemisphere game that had left Europe behind was shown as the All Blacks swatted Wales aside 49-6 in Brisbane in the semi-final of the inaugural World Cup. The Kiwis went on to claim the Cup, and would inflict further misery on Wales on their ill-fated 1988 tour of New Zealand.\r\nA 34-9 win in Cardiff followed for New Zealand in 1989, and at the 1995 World Cup Wales' big talk was made to look embarrassing as the All Blacks eased to victory in Johannesburg.",
    "id": "N_370",
    "features": {
        "noun": "New",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "played",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "New Zealand played their first international against Australia in 1903, the Kiwis triumphing 22-3 in which location, and the following year an official British touring team came to New Zealand for the first time.\r\nThe first South Africa tour of New Zealand in 1921 saw honours shared in a three-Test series, starting the greatest rivalry in rugby - and the long-running controversy between the countries over the All Blacks' inclusion of Maori players.\r\nEmploying the modern 3-4-1 scrum line-up against the New Zealand 'rover' system for the first time, South African teams defeated the All Blacks in five games and the Test series was drawn two-all.\r\nThe All Blacks were on top in the Test with Wales at the Arms Park, but the teams were locked at 8-8 when a Clem Thomas cross kick was gathered by Ken Jones for a famous, match-winning try.\r\nWilson Whinneray's side rallied to beat Wales 6-0, their first win at the Arms Park in four attempts, and went unbeaten through the rest of the tour, but when they returned home the first question put to them was: \"What happened in Newport?\" The only blemish on the record of the awesome 1967 tourists was a draw with East Wales, as they beat the full Wales team 13-6 in Cardiff to take the lead in the series between the countries for the first time.\r\nThat lead was increased with two comfortable wins for the home side in New Zealand in 1969, the first time Wales had toured the country as an independent team.\r\nJames guided Llanelli to a famous 9-3 win over the tourists at Stradey Park, though, and in the final game of the tour the Barbarians defeated the All Blacks 23-11 in Cardiff in a game regarded by many as the greatest ever played.\r\nNew Zealand defeated a Wales XV 12-3 at the Arms Park in a non-cap game in 1974, but it was the 1978 game in Cardiff that would reignite the history of controversy between the two countries.\r\nA crushing 23-3 win for New Zealand in Cardiff in the Welsh Rugby Union's 1980 centenary game was a sign of things to come.\r\nThe new professionalism in the southern hemisphere game that had left Europe behind was shown as the All Blacks swatted Wales aside 49-6 in Brisbane in the semi-final of the inaugural World Cup. The Kiwis went on to claim the Cup, and would inflict further misery on Wales on their ill-fated 1988 tour of New Zealand.\r\nA 34-9 win in Cardiff followed for New Zealand in 1989, and at the 1995 World Cup Wales' big talk was made to look embarrassing as the All Blacks eased to victory in Johannesburg.?",
        "answer": "Sydney"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The season would start with the Celtic League in October, followed by the Heineken Cup in February and March, and the Six Nations moved to April and May. After a nine week break, the WRU then proposes a two-month period of away and home international matches.",
    "id": "N_371",
    "features": {
        "noun": "season",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "start",
        "adjective": "two-month",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhatseasonwhatwouldwhatstartwhatwithwhatthewhatCelticwhatLeaguewhatinwhatOctober,whatfollowedwhatbywhatthewhatHeinekenwhatCupwhatinwhatFebruarywhatandwhatMarch,whatandwhatthewhatSixwhatNationswhatmovedwhattowhatAprilwhatandwhatMay.whatAfterwhatawhatninewhatweekwhatbreak,whatthewhatWRUwhatthenwhatproposeswhatawhattwo-monthwhatperiodwhatofwhatawaywhatandwhathomewhatinternationalwhatmatches.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"Captaincy offers a challenging environment for any player, especially following in the footsteps of Lawrence Dallaglio and before him the World Cup captain, Martin Johnson.\r\n\"I'm honoured Andy wants me to be his captain, and to follow Lawrence and Martin means a lot to me as they are inspirational men who have given so much to England rugby over many years.",
    "id": "N_372",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"Captaincy",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "offers",
        "adjective": "player,",
        "adverb": "especially"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"Captaincywhatofferswhatawhatchallengingwhatenvironmentwhatforwhatanywhatplayer,whatespeciallywhatfollowingwhatinwhatthewhatfootstepswhatofwhatLawrencewhatDallagliowhatandwhatbeforewhathimwhatthewhatWorldwhatCupwhatcaptain,whatMartinwhatJohnson.\r\n\"I'mwhathonouredwhatAndywhatwantswhatmewhattowhatbewhathiswhatcaptain,whatandwhattowhatfollowwhatLawrencewhatandwhatMartinwhatmeanswhatawhatlotwhattowhatmewhataswhattheywhatarewhatinspirationalwhatmenwhatwhowhathavewhatgivenwhatsowhatmuchwhattowhatEnglandwhatrugbywhatoverwhatmanywhatyears.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Hong Kong is hoping to join Japan as co-host of the 2011 Rugby World Cup.\r\nBut Hong Kong Rugby Football Union (HKRFU) chairman John Molloy has called for the territory to host one of the pools and a quarter-final.",
    "id": "N_373",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Hong",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "quarter-final.",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Hong who is hoping to join Japan as co-host of the 2011 Rugby World Cup.\r\nBut Hong who Rugby Football Union (HKRFU) chairman John Molloy has called for the territory to host one of the pools and a quarter-final.?",
        "answer": "Kong"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "An integral part of a sustained period of success for England, Dallaglio's crowning glory was his part in the side that won the Rugby World Cup in 2003.\r\nDallaglio arrived as part of the unheralded England side which became the shock winners of the first Rugby Sevens World Cup in 1993.\r\nWithin two years of his debut, Dallaglio was offered the England captain's band, and his career continued to go from strength to strength as he made the 1997 Lions tour to South Africa.\r\nAs a member of a new-look England side on the long road to World Cup glory - a journey not without mishaps as a succession of Grand Slams opportunities were spurned - Dallaglio emerged as a key performer once again.\r\nFollowing Johnson's retirement, Dallaglio's career came full circle as Woodward restored him as England captain.\r\nDallaglio walks away from the international game safe in the knowledge that he will go down as one of England's most accomplished players, if not one of the great captains despite his evident pride in leading his country.",
    "id": "N_374",
    "features": {
        "noun": "part",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "crowning",
        "adjective": "integral",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "that"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "European champions Wasps fought back through a Josh Lewsey try and Mark van Gisbergen's boot, and they were level at 31-31 with five minutes remaining.\r\nThe closing moments saw desperate defence from Leicester as Wasps turned down several penalties to go for the try they needed.\r\n\"We have got to get our scrum right next week, it is the biggest cause for concern.\" Leicester coach John Wells saluted the outstanding work of Graham Rowntree and Julian White, who were magnificent up front.\r\nMurphy; Rabeni, Smith, Gibson, Healey; Goode, Ellis; Rowntree, Chuter, White, M Johnson (capt), L Deacon; Moody, Back, Corry.",
    "id": "N_375",
    "features": {
        "noun": "champions",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "fought",
        "adjective": "European",
        "adverb": "right"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "EuropeanwhochampionswhoWaspswhofoughtwhobackwhothroughwhoawhoJoshwhoLewseywhotrywhoandwhoMarkwhovanwhoGisbergen'swhoboot,whoandwhotheywhowerewholevelwhoatwho31-31whowithwhofivewhominuteswhoremaining.\r\nThewhoclosingwhomomentswhosawwhodesperatewhodefencewhofromwhoLeicesterwhoaswhoWaspswhoturnedwhodownwhoseveralwhopenaltieswhotowhogowhoforwhothewhotrywhotheywhoneeded.\r\n\"Wewhohavewhogotwhotowhogetwhoourwhoscrumwhorightwhonextwhoweek,whoitwhoiswhothewhobiggestwhocausewhoforwhoconcern.\"whoLeicesterwhocoachwhoJohnwhoWellswhosalutedwhothewhooutstandingwhoworkwhoofwhoGrahamwhoRowntreewhoandwhoJulianwhoWhite,whowhowhowerewhomagnificentwhoupwhofront.\r\nMurphy;whoRabeni,whoSmith,whoGibson,whoHealey;whoGoode,whoEllis;whoRowntree,whoChuter,whoWhite,whoMwhoJohnsonwho(capt),whoLwhoDeacon;whoMoody,whoBack,whoCorry.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Another South African infringement a minute later led to Ireland's first points - O'Gara took a quick tap-penalty and charged over the opposition line for an Irish try.\r\nStung by the score, the South Africans almost replied with a try of their own within 60 seconds with Geordan Murphy's ankle-tap tackle denying a certain try for Percy Montgomery.\r\nAfter the sustained Springboks pressure, the Irish produced an attack of their own in the 34th minute which culminated with O'Gara's clever drop-goal to restore his side's lead to five points which remained the margin at half-time.\r\nMontgomery then burst through the Irish defence in the 48th minute and it took a superb Girvan Dempsey tackle to prevent a try.\r\nHowever, two Montgomery penalties had Ireland's lead in peril again as the Springboks closed to within five points with seven minutes remaining.",
    "id": "N_376",
    "features": {
        "noun": "infringement",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "led",
        "adjective": "South",
        "adverb": "later"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "AnotherwhatSouthwhatAfricanwhatinfringementwhatawhatminutewhatlaterwhatledwhattowhatIreland'swhatfirstwhatpointswhat-whatO'Garawhattookwhatawhatquickwhattap-penaltywhatandwhatchargedwhatoverwhatthewhatoppositionwhatlinewhatforwhatanwhatIrishwhattry.\r\nStungwhatbywhatthewhatscore,whatthewhatSouthwhatAfricanswhatalmostwhatrepliedwhatwithwhatawhattrywhatofwhattheirwhatownwhatwithinwhat60whatsecondswhatwithwhatGeordanwhatMurphy'swhatankle-tapwhattacklewhatdenyingwhatawhatcertainwhattrywhatforwhatPercywhatMontgomery.\r\nAfterwhatthewhatsustainedwhatSpringbokswhatpressure,whatthewhatIrishwhatproducedwhatanwhatattackwhatofwhattheirwhatownwhatinwhatthewhat34thwhatminutewhatwhichwhatculminatedwhatwithwhatO'Gara'swhatcleverwhatdrop-goalwhattowhatrestorewhathiswhatside'swhatleadwhattowhatfivewhatpointswhatwhichwhatremainedwhatthewhatmarginwhatatwhathalf-time.\r\nMontgomerywhatthenwhatburstwhatthroughwhatthewhatIrishwhatdefencewhatinwhatthewhat48thwhatminutewhatandwhatitwhattookwhatawhatsuperbwhatGirvanwhatDempseywhattacklewhattowhatpreventwhatawhattry.\r\nHowever,whattwowhatMontgomerywhatpenaltieswhathadwhatIreland'swhatleadwhatinwhatperilwhatagainwhataswhatthewhatSpringbokswhatclosedwhattowhatwithinwhatfivewhatpointswhatwithwhatsevenwhatminuteswhatremaining.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "We have guys coming into the team who are chomping at the bit.\" The Irish line-up shows nine changes from the team which started against South Africa with winger Tommy Bowe and flanker Denis Leamy making their international debuts.\r\nThe other changes see recalls for backs David Humphreys, Kevin Maggs and Guy Easterby with Eric Miller, Marcus Horan, Donnacha O'Callaghan and Frank Sheehan all returning to the pack.\r\nO'Sullivan said the players coming in had the opportunity to stake claims for inclusion against Argentina on 27 November.\r\nG Murphy; S Horgan, B O'Driscoll (capt), K Maggs, T Bowe; D Humphreys, G Easterby; M Horan.",
    "id": "N_377",
    "features": {
        "noun": "team",
        "pronoun": "We",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "Irish",
        "adverb": "all"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "who"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ulster scrum-half Kieran Campbell is one of five uncapped players included in Ireland's RBS Six Nations squad.\r\nCampbell is joined by Ulster colleagues Roger Wilson and Ronan McCormack along with Connacht's Bernard Jackman and Munster's Shaun Payne.\r\nThere were one or two players who were unfortunate just to miss out.\" Back-row forwards David Wallace and Victor Costello are omitted, with O'Sullivan having Quinlan, Wilson, Simon Easterby, Anthony Foley, Denis Leamy and Johnny O'Connor vying for the three positions.\r\nMunster and Leinster have 12 and 11 players in the squad respectively while Jackman is the sole Connacht representative.",
    "id": "N_378",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ulster",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "uncapped",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Ulster scrum-half Kieran who is one of five uncapped players included in Ireland's RBS Six Nations squad.\r\nwho is joined by Ulster colleagues Roger Wilson and Ronan McCormack along with Connacht's Bernard Jackman and Munster's Shaun Payne.\r\nThere were one or two players who were unfortunate just to miss out.\" Back-row forwards David Wallace and Victor Costello are omitted, with O'Sullivan having Quinlan, Wilson, Simon Easterby, Anthony Foley, Denis Leamy and Johnny O'Connor vying for the three positions.\r\nMunster and Leinster have 12 and 11 players in the squad respectively while Jackman is the sole Connacht representative.?",
        "answer": "Campbell"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "An injury-time dropped goal by Ronan O'Gara stole victory for Ireland from underneath the noses of Argentina at Lansdowne Road on Saturday.\r\nO'Gara kicked all of Ireland's points, with two dropped goals and five penalties, to give the home side a 100% record in their autumn internationals.\r\nO'Gara finally got Ireland on the board with a dropped goal in the ninth minute only for Contepomi to rifle over his second penalty two minutes later.\r\nO'Gara managed to land his second penalty in the 36th minute, but once again Contepomi replied in kind four minutes into first-half injury time.",
    "id": "N_379",
    "features": {
        "noun": "goal",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "dropped",
        "adjective": "injury-time",
        "adverb": "finally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "injury-time"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England beat Fiji 26-21 in a dramatic final in Dubai to win the first IRB Sevens event of the season.\r\n\"To be honest, England have wanted to win in Dubai for a very long time now, and the people here have wanted us to win for just as long,\" said Friday.",
    "id": "N_380",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "us",
        "verb": "win",
        "adjective": "dramatic",
        "adverb": "very"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who beat Fiji 26-21 in a dramatic final in Dubai to win the first IRB Sevens event of the season.\r\n\"To be honest, who have wanted to win in Dubai for a very long time now, and the people here have wanted us to win for just as long,\" said Friday.?",
        "answer": "England"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "New Zealand proved too strong for an Australian-dominated Barbarians to round off their unbeaten northern hemisphere tour with an easy win.\r\nThe Baa-Baas did threaten, scoring tries through Albert van den Bergh, Xavier Rush and Andrea Lo Cicero, but never looked like winning.\r\nMarty Holah got the All Blacks onslaught under way with his fifth-minute try before Rush hit back moments later.\r\nJermoe Keino and Piri Weepu both added tries to the All Blacks' tally before the final whistle, while van den Bergh gained some consolation for the Baa-Baas.",
    "id": "N_381",
    "features": {
        "noun": "New",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "proved",
        "adjective": "strong",
        "adverb": "too"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "Barbarians"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wasps scrum-half Matt Dawson has been recalled to England's training squad ahead of the RBS Six Nations and been reinstated in the Elite Player Squad.\r\nBalshaw, Cohen, Cueto, Lewsey, Robinson, Simpson-Daniel, Voyce, Abbott, Noon, Paul, Smith, Tait, Tindall, Barkley, Hodgson, King, Wilkinson, Dawson, Ellis, Gomarsall.\r\nChuter, Thompson, Titterrell, Rowntree, Sheridan, Stevens, Vickery, White, Borthwick, Brown, L Deacon, Grewcock, Kay, Shaw, Beattie, Corry, Forrester, Hazell, Jones, Moody, Vyvyan, J Worsley.\r\nAbbott, Balshaw, Borthwick, A Brown, Chuter, Cohen, Corry, Cueto, Dawson, Ellis, Flatman, Gomarsall, Greening, Greenwood, Grewcock, Hazell, Hill, Hodgson, Kay, King, Lewsey, Moody, Noon, Paul, Robinson, Rowntree, Shaw, Simpson-Daniel, Thompson, Tindall, Titterrell, Vickery, Vyvyan, White, Wilkinson, J Worsley, M Worsley.",
    "id": "N_382",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wasps",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "scrum-half",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Waspswhoscrum-halfwhoMattwhoDawsonwhohaswhobeenwhorecalledwhotowhoEngland'swhotrainingwhosquadwhoaheadwhoofwhothewhoRBSwhoSixwhoNationswhoandwhobeenwhoreinstatedwhoinwhothewhoElitewhoPlayerwhoSquad.\r\nBalshaw,whoCohen,whoCueto,whoLewsey,whoRobinson,whoSimpson-Daniel,whoVoyce,whoAbbott,whoNoon,whoPaul,whoSmith,whoTait,whoTindall,whoBarkley,whoHodgson,whoKing,whoWilkinson,whoDawson,whoEllis,whoGomarsall.\r\nChuter,whoThompson,whoTitterrell,whoRowntree,whoSheridan,whoStevens,whoVickery,whoWhite,whoBorthwick,whoBrown,whoLwhoDeacon,whoGrewcock,whoKay,whoShaw,whoBeattie,whoCorry,whoForrester,whoHazell,whoJones,whoMoody,whoVyvyan,whoJwhoWorsley.\r\nAbbott,whoBalshaw,whoBorthwick,whoAwhoBrown,whoChuter,whoCohen,whoCorry,whoCueto,whoDawson,whoEllis,whoFlatman,whoGomarsall,whoGreening,whoGreenwood,whoGrewcock,whoHazell,whoHill,whoHodgson,whoKay,whoKing,whoLewsey,whoMoody,whoNoon,whoPaul,whoRobinson,whoRowntree,whoShaw,whoSimpson-Daniel,whoThompson,whoTindall,whoTitterrell,whoVickery,whoVyvyan,whoWhite,whoWilkinson,whoJwhoWorsley,whoMwhoWorsley.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A late try by Borders substitute Jonny Weston had set up a dramatic finish, but the Scottish side could not complete the fightback.\r\nUlster had led 20-6 with tries from Paul Steinmetz and Bryn Cunningham.\r\nFirst, Mark Blair was yellow carded for killing the ball on the ground and then full-back Cunningham bagged the second touchdown in the wake of fine work by skipper Andy Ward.\r\nEven worse was to come for Borders when Larkin kicked two more penalties just before the break, the second of which also led to Kelly Brown being sin-binned.\r\nMorton, Moffat, MacRae, Hore, Berthinussen, Warnock, Moore, Thomson, Ford, Douglas, Blair, Stewart, Gray, Brown, McEntee.",
    "id": "N_383",
    "features": {
        "noun": "try",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "late",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "AwholatewhotrywhobywhoBorderswhosubstitutewhoJonnywhoWestonwhohadwhosetwhoupwhoawhodramaticwhofinish,whobutwhothewhoScottishwhosidewhocouldwhonotwhocompletewhothewhofightback.\r\nUlsterwhohadwholedwho20-6whowithwhotrieswhofromwhoPaulwhoSteinmetzwhoandwhoBrynwhoCunningham.\r\nFirst,whoMarkwhoBlairwhowaswhoyellowwhocardedwhoforwhokillingwhothewhoballwhoonwhothewhogroundwhoandwhothenwhofull-backwhoCunninghamwhobaggedwhothewhosecondwhotouchdownwhoinwhothewhowakewhoofwhofinewhoworkwhobywhoskipperwhoAndywhoWard.\r\nEvenwhoworsewhowaswhotowhocomewhoforwhoBorderswhowhenwhoLarkinwhokickedwhotwowhomorewhopenaltieswhojustwhobeforewhothewhobreak,whothewhosecondwhoofwhowhichwhoalsowholedwhotowhoKellywhoBrownwhobeingwhosin-binned.\r\nMorton,whoMoffat,whoMacRae,whoHore,whoBerthinussen,whoWarnock,whoMoore,whoThomson,whoFord,whoDouglas,whoBlair,whoStewart,whoGray,whoBrown,whoMcEntee.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"But I would have to have a compulsive reason to pick any player who is not available to international rugby.\" Dallaglio, Back and Johnson have all retired from international rugby over the last 12 months but continue to star for their club sides.\r\nBut Woodward added: \"The key thing that I want to stress is that I intend to use the Six Nations and the players who are available to international rugby as the key benchmark.\r\n\"I think it's absolutely critical and with the history of the Lions we have got to take players playing for the four countries.\" Woodward also revealed that the race for the captaincy was still wide open.\r\n\"There are some outstanding candidates from all four countries.\" And following the All Blacks' impressive displays in Europe in recent weeks, including a 45-6 humiliation of France, Woodward believes the three-test series in New Zealand will provide the ultimate rugby challenge.",
    "id": "N_384",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"But",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "compulsive",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former government communications chief Alastair Campbell will act as a media consultant to Sir Clive Woodward's 2005 Lions on their tour to New Zealand.\r\n\"The Lions is a massive media event,\" said Woodward, who will be the head coach.",
    "id": "N_385",
    "features": {
        "noun": "government",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "act",
        "adjective": "Former",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former government communications chief Alastair who will act as a media consultant to Sir Clive Woodward's 2005 Lions on their tour to New Zealand.\r\n\"The Lions is a massive media event,\" said Woodward, who will be the head coach.?",
        "answer": "Campbell"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"But I would have to have a compulsive reason to pick any player who is not available to international rugby.\" Dallaglio, Back and Johnson have all retired from international rugby over the last 12 months but continue to star for their club sides.\r\nBut Woodward added: \"The key thing that I want to stress is that I intend to use the Six Nations and the players who are available to international rugby as the key benchmark.\r\n\"I think it's absolutely critical and with the history of the Lions we have got to take players playing for the four countries.\" Woodward also revealed that the race for the captaincy was still wide open.\r\n\"There are some outstanding candidates from all four countries.\" And following the All Blacks' impressive displays in Europe in recent weeks, including a 45-6 humiliation of France, Woodward believes the three-test series in New Zealand will provide the ultimate rugby challenge.",
    "id": "N_386",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"But",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "compulsive",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England captain Jonny Wilkinson will make his long-awaited return from injury against Edinburgh on Saturday.",
    "id": "N_387",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "long-awaited",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England captain Jonny who will make his long-awaited return from injury against Edinburgh on Saturday.?",
        "answer": "Wilkinson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former England captain Lawrence Dallaglio still harbours hopes of a place on the British and Irish Lions tour to New Zealand.\r\n\"If Clive feels he has no need to look outside the international crop, then fine.",
    "id": "N_388",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Former",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "harbours",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "FormerwhoEnglandwhocaptainwhoLawrencewhoDallagliowhostillwhoharbourswhohopeswhoofwhoawhoplacewhoonwhothewhoBritishwhoandwhoIrishwhoLionswhotourwhotowhoNewwhoZealand.\r\n\"IfwhoClivewhofeelswhohewhohaswhonowhoneedwhotowholookwhooutsidewhothewhointernationalwhocrop,whothenwhofine.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "European champions Wasps are set to offer Matt Dawson a new deal.",
    "id": "N_389",
    "features": {
        "noun": "champions",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "European",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "Wasps"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Leicester wing Austin Healey hopes to use Sunday's return Heineken Cup clash with Wasps as a further springboard to an England recall for the Six Nations.\r\n\"We will have to see what happens after the previous (autumn) Tests but when I look at the current squad I definitely feel there is a place there for me.\" Healey, who has also played both half-back positions and full-back during his career, has reverted to the wing, where he won most of his England caps.\r\nThen, in the first of their Heineken cup double header last Sunday, Healey slotted in at stand-off and delivered a superb cross-kick for Martin Corry to score the Tigers' third try.\r\nThe same outcome this Sunday would put Leicester in pole position to top their Heineken pool with a home game against Biarritz and away trip to Calvisano to come.",
    "id": "N_390",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Leicester",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "wing",
        "adjective": "further",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Leicester wing Austin who hopes to use Sunday's return Heineken Cup clash with Wasps as a further springboard to an England recall for the Six Nations.\r\n\"We will have to see what happens after the previous (autumn) Tests but when I look at the current squad I definitely feel there is a place there for me.\" who, who has also played both half-back positions and full-back during his career, has reverted to the wing, where he won most of his England caps.\r\nThen, in the first of their Heineken cup double header last Sunday, who slotted in at stand-off and delivered a superb cross-kick for Martin Corry to score the Tigers' third try.\r\nThe same outcome this Sunday would put Leicester in pole position to top their Heineken pool with a home game against Biarritz and away trip to Calvisano to come.?",
        "answer": "Healey"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Bath have signed their former scrum-half Andy Williams on a short-term deal from the Neath-Swansea Ospreys.\r\nWales international Williams, whose contract with the Welsh region was due to expire in June, has agreed a contract until the end of the season.",
    "id": "N_391",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Bath",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "former",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "what have signed their former scrum-half Andy Williams on a short-term deal from the Neath-Swansea Ospreys.\r\nWales international Williams, whose contract with the Welsh region was due to expire in June, has agreed a contract until the end of the season.?",
        "answer": "Bath"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mike Tindall's agent has warned Bath they have until next week to improve their contract offer to the England man or risk losing him to a rival club.",
    "id": "N_392",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mike",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "next",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "MikewhoTindall'swhoagentwhohaswhowarnedwhoBathwhotheywhohavewhountilwhonextwhoweekwhotowhoimprovewhotheirwhocontractwhoofferwhotowhothewhoEnglandwhomanwhoorwhoriskwholosingwhohimwhotowhoawhorivalwhoclub.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England centre Mike Tindall is to seek a second opinion before having surgery on a foot injury that could force him to miss the entire Six Nations.\r\n\"Mike had a specialist review on a fracture in his right mid foot,\" said England doctor Simon Kemp.",
    "id": "N_393",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "that"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Those are the two questions occupying not just Wales supporters but rugby fans as a whole after a scintillating display in Paris.\r\nWelsh legend Mervyn Davies, a member of two of three Grand Slam-winning sides of the 1970s, hailed it as \"one of the great performances of the past three decades\".\r\nBut since they threw off the shackles against New Zealand in the 2003 World Cup, Wales have rediscovered much of what made them a great rugby nation in the first place.\r\nRuddock and Thomas can take much of the credit for that, ensuring the tribal and regional divisions that have often scarred Welsh rugby do not extend to the national squad.\r\nso evident in that magical second-half spell in Paris also stems from a style of play that first wooed supporters the world over in the 1970s.",
    "id": "N_394",
    "features": {
        "noun": "questions",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "rugby",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"That's the last thing on our minds at the moment,\" said Williams, a second- half replacement in Saturday's 24-18 win over France in Paris.\r\n\"We've come unstuck there a couple of times recently so our focus is on that game and we'll worry about Ireland hopefully after we've beaten Scotland.\" With captain Gareth Thomas ruled out of the rest of the campaign with a broken thumb, Williams is vying for his first start in the championship so far.\r\n\"Italy are really brave opposition and sometimes it's very hard to win,\" he said.",
    "id": "N_395",
    "features": {
        "noun": "thing",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "recently"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"That's the last thing on our minds at the moment,\" said Williams, a second- half replacement in Saturday's 24-18 win over France in which location.\r\n\"We've come unstuck there a couple of times recently so our focus is on that game and we'll worry about Ireland hopefully after we've beaten Scotland.\" With captain Gareth Thomas ruled out of the rest of the campaign with a broken thumb, Williams is vying for his first start in the championship so far.\r\n\"Italy are really brave opposition and sometimes it's very hard to win,\" he said.?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Paul Sculthorpe has admitted he would love to succeed Andy Farrell as Great Britain skipper if the Wigan star does switch codes to rugby union.\r\nIf he fancies a new challenge, then who could fault him?\" Sculthorpe also called on the rugby league authorities to have a serious look at the number of games the top players are being asked to play.\r\nSean Long, Sculthorpe's Saints and Lions team-mate, has expressed doubts about his international future \"I think Sean's situation is to do with the sheer number of games we're playing,\" he said.\r\n\"The way he's looking at it is that if he can extend his career by a couple of years by not playing international rugby, then he's willing to do that.",
    "id": "N_396",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Paul",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "union.",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Paul Sculthorpe has admitted he would love to succeed Andy Farrell as Great Britain skipper if the Wigan what does switch codes to rugby union.\r\nIf he fancies a new challenge, then who could fault him?\" Sculthorpe also called on the rugby league authorities to have a serious look at the number of games the top players are being asked to play.\r\nSean Long, Sculthorpe's Saints and Lions team-mate, has expressed doubts about his international future \"I think Sean's situation is to do with the sheer number of games we're playing,\" he said.\r\n\"The way he's looking at it is that if he can extend his career by a couple of years by not playing international rugby, then he's willing to do that.?",
        "answer": "star"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Leicester say they will not be rushed into making a bid for Andy Farrell should the Great Britain rugby league captain decide to switch codes.\r\nLeicester and Saracens are believed to head the list of rugby union clubs interested in signing Farrell if he decides to move to the 15-man game.",
    "id": "N_397",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Leicester",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "say",
        "adjective": "interested",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Leicester say they will not be rushed into making a bid for Andy Farrell should the Great Britain rugby league what decide to switch codes.\r\nLeicester and Saracens are believed to head the list of rugby union clubs interested in signing Farrell if he decides to move to the 15-man game.?",
        "answer": "captain"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wigan chairman Maurice Lindsay says he does not expect a quick solution to the on-going saga of captain Andy Farrell's possible switch to rugby union.\r\nAlthough the move would be a lucrative one for both Farrell and Wigan, Lindsay said money was not a motivating factor for the club.\r\nLindsay also said he understood why rugby union was so interested in signing up Farrell.",
    "id": "N_398",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wigan",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "says",
        "adjective": "quick",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wigan chairman Maurice Lindsay says who does not expect a quick solution to twho on-going saga of captain Andy Farrell's possible switch to rugby union.\r\nAlthough twho move would be a lucrative one for both Farrell and Wigan, Lindsay said money was not a motivating factor for twho club.\r\nLindsay also said who understood why rugby union was so interested in signing up Farrell.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England will have to negotiate their way through a tough draw if they are to win the Rugby World Cup Sevens in Hong Kong next month.\r\nThe second seeds have been drawn against Samoa, France, Italy, Georgia and Chinese Taipei.\r\nThe top two sides in each pool qualify but England could face 2001 winners New Zealand in the quarter-finals if they stumble against Samoa.",
    "id": "N_399",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "they",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "tough",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England will have to negotiate their way through a tough draw if who are to win the Rugby World Cup Sevens in Hong Kong next month.\r\nThe second seeds have been drawn against Samoa, France, Italy, Georgia and Chinese Taipei.\r\nThe top two sides in each pool qualify but England could face 2001 winners New Zealand in the quarter-finals if who stumble against Samoa.?",
        "answer": "they"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "His kicking game also prospered, particularly when he moved to full-back for 10 minutes either side of half-time when his captain Gareth Thomas was in the sin-bin.\r\nOne huge clearance from Tait's kick sent England retreating rapidly while another booming punt to the right corner kept the visitors pinned in their own half.\r\nHe also had a hand in the game's only try, finished superbly by Williams, and might have scored himself on the half-hour as he glided into space, only to be scragged by Tait.\r\nHenson was twice repelled as Wales laid siege to the English line after Charlie Hodgson's penalty had edged the visitors in front for the first time.\r\nBut it was Wales who finished the game on the attack, almost snatching a second try in a thunderous climax.",
    "id": "N_400",
    "features": {
        "noun": "kicking",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "prospered,",
        "adjective": "sin-bin.",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "His kicking game also prospered, particularly when he moved to full-back for 10 minutes either side of half-time when his captain Gareth who was in the sin-bin.\r\nOne huge clearance from Tait's kick sent England retreating rapidly while another booming punt to the right corner kept the visitors pinned in their own half.\r\nHe also had a hand in the game's only try, finished superbly by Williams, and might have scored himself on the half-hour as he glided into space, only to be scragged by Tait.\r\nHenson was twice repelled as Wales laid siege to the English line after Charlie Hodgson's penalty had edged the visitors in front for the first time.\r\nBut it was Wales who finished the game on the attack, almost snatching a second try in a thunderous climax.?",
        "answer": "Thomas"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sydney will host a northern versus southern hemisphere charity match in June or July, the Australian Rugby Union (ARU) said on Wednesday.\r\n\"The Australian Rugby Union has thrown its support behind a proposed North-South match to raise funds for the tsunami appeals,\" the ARU said.",
    "id": "N_401",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sydney",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "host",
        "adjective": "northern",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "SydneywhowillwhohostwhoawhonorthernwhoversuswhosouthernwhohemispherewhocharitywhomatchwhoinwhoJunewhoorwhoJuly,whothewhoAustralianwhoRugbywhoUnionwho(ARU)whosaidwhoonwhoWednesday.\r\n\"ThewhoAustralianwhoRugbywhoUnionwhohaswhothrownwhoitswhosupportwhobehindwhoawhoproposedwhoNorth-Southwhomatchwhotowhoraisewhofundswhoforwhothewhotsunamiwhoappeals,\"whothewhoARUwhosaid.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Six Nations has heralded a new order in northern hemisphere rugby this year and Wales and Ireland rather than traditional big guns France and England face a potential Grand Slam play-off in three weeks' time.\r\nEngland sat on rugby's summit 15 months ago as world champions and 2003 Grand Slam winners.\r\nThe same year that England ruled the roost, a woeful Wales lost all five matches in the Six Nations.\r\nWales' most recent championship title was in 1994, and their last Grand Slam success came in 1978 in the era of Gareth Edwards, Phil Bennett, JPR Williams et al.\r\nThe men from the Emerald Isle have been Six Nations runners-up for the past two years, to France and England.",
    "id": "N_402",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Six",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "new",
        "adverb": "hemisphere"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The International Rugby Board may have to step in to stop frustrated coaches and players from publicly haranguing referees when things go belly-up.\r\nThe game was as exciting as it comes, with a much-improved England side enraged at a few decisions that did not go their way.\r\nEngland coach Andy Robinson referred to a similar case at Ravenhill in January when Ulster were playing Gloucester in the Heineken Cup. On that occasion, David Humphreys kicked to Tommy Bowe, who touched down in the corner only for the try to be wiped out.\r\nThe referee also missed England's Danny Grewcock taking out Ronan O'Gara off the ball to allow Martin Corry a Sunday stroll to the line.\r\nBrian O'Driscoll's winning try was as well-conceived as they come, while Charlie Hodgson's brilliant kicking display was another highlight.\r\nTwo outstanding pieces of defensive play denied England and allowed Ireland to hold on.\r\nEngland had turned Ireland one way then the other, and the defence cordon was slowly disintegrating.",
    "id": "N_403",
    "features": {
        "noun": "International",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "frustrated",
        "adverb": "publicly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoInternationalwhoRugbywhoBoardwhomaywhohavewhotowhostepwhoinwhotowhostopwhofrustratedwhocoacheswhoandwhoplayerswhofromwhopubliclywhoharanguingwhorefereeswhowhenwhothingswhogowhobelly-up.\r\nThewhogamewhowaswhoaswhoexcitingwhoaswhoitwhocomes,whowithwhoawhomuch-improvedwhoEnglandwhosidewhoenragedwhoatwhoawhofewwhodecisionswhothatwhodidwhonotwhogowhotheirwhoway.\r\nEnglandwhocoachwhoAndywhoRobinsonwhoreferredwhotowhoawhosimilarwhocasewhoatwhoRavenhillwhoinwhoJanuarywhowhenwhoUlsterwhowerewhoplayingwhoGloucesterwhoinwhothewhoHeinekenwhoCup.whoOnwhothatwhooccasion,whoDavidwhoHumphreyswhokickedwhotowhoTommywhoBowe,whowhowhotouchedwhodownwhoinwhothewhocornerwhoonlywhoforwhothewhotrywhotowhobewhowipedwhoout.\r\nThewhorefereewhoalsowhomissedwhoEngland'swhoDannywhoGrewcockwhotakingwhooutwhoRonanwhoO'GarawhooffwhothewhoballwhotowhoallowwhoMartinwhoCorrywhoawhoSundaywhostrollwhotowhothewholine.\r\nBrianwhoO'Driscoll'swhowinningwhotrywhowaswhoaswhowell-conceivedwhoaswhotheywhocome,whowhilewhoCharliewhoHodgson'swhobrilliantwhokickingwhodisplaywhowaswhoanotherwhohighlight.\r\nTwowhooutstandingwhopieceswhoofwhodefensivewhoplaywhodeniedwhoEnglandwhoandwhoallowedwhoIrelandwhotowhoholdwhoon.\r\nEnglandwhohadwhoturnedwhoIrelandwhoonewhowaywhothenwhothewhoother,whoandwhothewhodefencewhocordonwhowaswhoslowlywhodisintegrating.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A second-half try from captain Brian O'Driscoll and 14 points from Ronan O'Gara kept Ireland on track for their first Grand Slam since 1948.\r\nIn front of a supercharged home crowd on a dry but blustery day in Dublin, Ireland tore into the white-shirted visitors from the kick-off and made their intentions clear when O'Gara landed a fourth-minute drop-goal.\r\nEngland were awarded a penalty of their own on the halfway line after 20 minutes, and Hodgson, the villain at Twickenham, coolly bisected the posts.\r\nFrom the line-out, the ball was recycled back to O'Gara, who stroked his second drop-goal, this time off the right upright.\r\nEngland's pressure continued, and a wave of attacks saw centre Jamie Noon dragged down yards from the line before Hodgson landed a drop-goal.\r\nO'Gara missed a penalty which would have put Ireland nine points clear, and the home crowd breathed a sigh of relief when Hodgson's cross-kick was fumbled by lock Ben Kay near the line.",
    "id": "N_404",
    "features": {
        "noun": "try",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "kept",
        "adjective": "second-half",
        "adverb": "tore"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Awhatsecond-halfwhattrywhatfromwhatcaptainwhatBrianwhatO'Driscollwhatandwhat14whatpointswhatfromwhatRonanwhatO'GarawhatkeptwhatIrelandwhatonwhattrackwhatforwhattheirwhatfirstwhatGrandwhatSlamwhatsincewhat1948.\r\nInwhatfrontwhatofwhatawhatsuperchargedwhathomewhatcrowdwhatonwhatawhatdrywhatbutwhatblusterywhatdaywhatinwhatDublin,whatIrelandwhattorewhatintowhatthewhatwhite-shirtedwhatvisitorswhatfromwhatthewhatkick-offwhatandwhatmadewhattheirwhatintentionswhatclearwhatwhenwhatO'Garawhatlandedwhatawhatfourth-minutewhatdrop-goal.\r\nEnglandwhatwerewhatawardedwhatawhatpenaltywhatofwhattheirwhatownwhatonwhatthewhathalfwaywhatlinewhatafterwhat20whatminutes,whatandwhatHodgson,whatthewhatvillainwhatatwhatTwickenham,whatcoollywhatbisectedwhatthewhatposts.\r\nFromwhatthewhatline-out,whatthewhatballwhatwaswhatrecycledwhatbackwhattowhatO'Gara,whatwhowhatstrokedwhathiswhatsecondwhatdrop-goal,whatthiswhattimewhatoffwhatthewhatrightwhatupright.\r\nEngland'swhatpressurewhatcontinued,whatandwhatawhatwavewhatofwhatattackswhatsawwhatcentrewhatJamiewhatNoonwhatdraggedwhatdownwhatyardswhatfromwhatthewhatlinewhatbeforewhatHodgsonwhatlandedwhatawhatdrop-goal.\r\nO'GarawhatmissedwhatawhatpenaltywhatwhichwhatwouldwhathavewhatputwhatIrelandwhatninewhatpointswhatclear,whatandwhatthewhathomewhatcrowdwhatbreathedwhatawhatsighwhatofwhatreliefwhatwhenwhatHodgson'swhatcross-kickwhatwaswhatfumbledwhatbywhatlockwhatBenwhatKaywhatnearwhatthewhatline.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England coach Andy Robinson said he was \"livid\" after his side were denied two tries in Sunday's 19-13 Six Nations loss to Ireland in Dublin.\r\nKaplan then declined the chance to consult the fourth official when Josh Lewsey took the ball over the Irish line under a pile of bodies for what could have been the game-winning try.\r\n\"I think Mark Cueto scored a perfectly legal try and I think he should have gone to the video referee on Josh Lewsey,\" said Robinson.\r\nThey defended magnificently and they've got every chance of winning this Six Nations.\" England have lost their first three matches in this year's Six Nations and four out of their six games since Robinson took over from Sir Clive Woodward in September.",
    "id": "N_405",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "19-13",
        "adverb": "\"livid\""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England coach Andy Robinson said he was \"livid\" after his what were denied two tries in Sunday's 19-13 Six Nations loss to Ireland in Dublin.\r\nKaplan then declined the chance to consult the fourth official when Josh Lewsey took the ball over the Irish line under a pile of bodies for what could have been the game-winning try.\r\n\"I think Mark Cueto scored a perfectly legal try and I think he should have gone to the video referee on Josh Lewsey,\" said Robinson.\r\nThey defended magnificently and they've got every chance of winning this Six Nations.\" England have lost their first three matches in this year's Six Nations and four out of their six games since Robinson took over from Sir Clive Woodward in September.?",
        "answer": "side"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Paterson slotted four more second-half penalties and Scotland were denied a try when wing Sean Lamont's touchdown was ruled out for a forward pass.\r\nScotland defended the initial thrusts but on 20 minutes Italy, after coming up yards short of the line, equalised through a De Marigny penalty.\r\nItaly were offered another penalty when Scottish flanker Simon Taylor was offside but the left-footed De Marigny pushed his kick wide.\r\nWith the pendulum of possession swinging towards Scotland, Lamont thought he had wriggled over in the left corner after 65 minutes but play was recalled for a marginal forward pass from Paterson.",
    "id": "N_406",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Paterson",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "slotted",
        "adjective": "more",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Italy skipper Marco Bortolami believes Saturday's Six Nations contest against Scotland will be a scrappy encounter.\r\n\"Scotland played extremely well against France in Paris but not so well when Ireland came to Edinburgh,\" said Bortolami.",
    "id": "N_407",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Italy",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "believes",
        "adjective": "scrappy",
        "adverb": "extremely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Italy skipper Marco Bortolami believes Saturday's Six Nations contest against which location will be a scrappy encounter.\r\n\"which location played extremely well against France in Paris but not so well when Ireland came to Edinburgh,\" said Bortolami.?",
        "answer": "Scotland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Ireland and Munster lock Paul O'Connell has dismissed media reports linking him to the captaincy of the Lions tour to New Zealand this summer.\r\nO'Connell is rumoured to be among the front-runners for the job, but says he is totally focused on Sunday's Six Nations crunch clash with England.\r\nHe also said he remains wary of wounded England's abilities coming into Sunday's game after two straight defeats, dismissing predictions of a certain Irish victory.\r\nNo Ireland team lining up to play England will ever fall into that trap,\" he said.",
    "id": "N_408",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Ireland",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "wary",
        "adverb": "totally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "IrelandwhoandwhoMunsterwholockwhoPaulwhoO'ConnellwhohaswhodismissedwhomediawhoreportswholinkingwhohimwhotowhothewhocaptaincywhoofwhothewhoLionswhotourwhotowhoNewwhoZealandwhothiswhosummer.\r\nO'Connellwhoiswhorumouredwhotowhobewhoamongwhothewhofront-runnerswhoforwhothewhojob,whobutwhosayswhohewhoiswhototallywhofocusedwhoonwhoSunday'swhoSixwhoNationswhocrunchwhoclashwhowithwhoEngland.\r\nHewhoalsowhosaidwhohewhoremainswhowarywhoofwhowoundedwhoEngland'swhoabilitieswhocomingwhointowhoSunday'swhogamewhoafterwhotwowhostraightwhodefeats,whodismissingwhopredictionswhoofwhoawhocertainwhoIrishwhovictory.\r\nNowhoIrelandwhoteamwholiningwhoupwhotowhoplaywhoEnglandwhowillwhoeverwhofallwhointowhothatwhotrap,\"whohewhosaid.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Edinburgh were not in action during the first two weeks of this season's Six Nations.\r\nBoth Scotland and Italy have lost their opening two Six Nations games and, just like last season's encounter which Italy won, this weekend's game could turn out to be a battle to avoid the wooden spoon.",
    "id": "N_409",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Edinburgh",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "were",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who were not in action during the first two weeks of this season's Six Nations.\r\nBoth Scotland and Italy have lost their opening two Six Nations games and, just like last season's encounter which Italy won, this weekend's game could turn out to be a battle to avoid the wooden spoon.?",
        "answer": "Edinburgh"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He said: \"This isn't an injury that will stop me from working hard on the fitness elements and being around the lads.\" He added: \"I've got the operation this afternoon and I could be back doing fitness work after a week.\" \"As frustrating as it is, I've got to be positive.\"\r\n\"There's no doubt that I'm going to get involved and be around this place as soon as I can after the operation.\" Gloucester director of rugby Nigel Melville said: \"Phil has broken his radius, which is the large bone in his forearm.",
    "id": "N_410",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"This",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "said:",
        "adjective": "\"I've",
        "adverb": "hard"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wing Christophe Dominici says France can claim another Six Nations Grand Slam despite two lacklustre wins so far against Scotland and England.\r\n\"We know our display was not perfect, but we can still win the Grand Slam, along with Ireland and Wales.\" France , Ireland and Wales all remain unbeaten after two rounds of this year's RBS Six Nations, with the two Celtic nations playing by far the more impressive rugby.",
    "id": "N_411",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Christophe",
        "pronoun": "we",
        "verb": "Wing",
        "adjective": "lacklustre",
        "adverb": "so"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wing Christophe Dominici says France can claim another Six Nations Grand Slam despite two lacklustre wins so far against which location and England.\r\n\"We know our display was not perfect, but we can still win the Grand Slam, along with Ireland and Wales.\" France , Ireland and Wales all remain unbeaten after two rounds of this year's RBS Six Nations, with the two Celtic nations playing by far the more impressive rugby.?",
        "answer": "Scotland"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Wales record cap holder Gareth Llewellyn will retire from Test rugby at the end of the Six Nations.\r\n\"I was going to retire at the end of the last Six Nations, I'd even told some of the boys in the squad about it.\r\n\"But Mike (Ruddock) asked me to carry on for another season, which I've done, still part of the squad, still trying to help them out as much as I can.\" Llewellyn made his Wales debut in 1989 against New Zealand as a 20-year-old, having caught the selectors' eyes in the All Blacks' tour match against Neath.",
    "id": "N_412",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wales",
        "pronoun": "me",
        "verb": "retire",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "even"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Wales record cap holder Gareth who will retire from Test rugby at the end of the Six Nations.\r\n\"I was going to retire at the end of the last Six Nations, I'd even told some of the boys in the squad about it.\r\n\"But Mike (Ruddock) asked me to carry on for another season, which I've done, still part of the squad, still trying to help them out as much as I can.\" who made his Wales debut in 1989 against New Zealand as a 20-year-old, having caught the selectors' eyes in the All Blacks' tour match against Neath.?",
        "answer": "Llewellyn"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England suffered an eighth defeat in 11 Tests as scrum-half Dimitri Yachvili booted France to victory at Twickenham.\r\nBut Charlie Hodgson and Barkley missed six penalties between them, while Yachvili landed six for France to put the visitors in front.\r\nEngland could have won the game with three minutes left, but Hodgson pushed an easy drop goal opportunity wide.\r\nBarkley also missed two longer-range efforts as the first half drew to a close, but by then England had scored a second converted try.\r\nAnd after seeing another attempt drop just short, Yachvili put France ahead with his sixth penalty with 11 minutes left.\r\nEngland sent on Ben Cohen and Matt Dawson, and after Barkley's kick saw Christophe Dominici take the ball over his own line, the stage was set for a victory platform.",
    "id": "N_413",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "suffered",
        "adjective": "eighth",
        "adverb": "also"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "England suffered an eighth defeat in 11 Tests as scrum-half Dimitri who booted France to victory at Twickenham.\r\nBut Charlie Hodgson and Barkley missed six penalties between them, while who landed six for France to put the visitors in front.\r\nEngland could have won the game with three minutes left, but Hodgson pushed an easy drop goal opportunity wide.\r\nBarkley also missed two longer-range efforts as the first half drew to a close, but by then England had scored a second converted try.\r\nAnd after seeing another attempt drop just short, who put France ahead with his sixth penalty with 11 minutes left.\r\nEngland sent on Ben Cohen and Matt Dawson, and after Barkley's kick saw Christophe Dominici take the ball over his own line, the stage was set for a victory platform.?",
        "answer": "Yachvili"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "England will have to take on Ireland in the Six Nations without captain and goal-kicker Jonny Wilkinson, according to his Newcastle boss Rob Andrew.\r\n\"Jonny Wilkinson has proved himself a cool customer with around an 80% kicking success rate,\" Hare told BBC Radio Five Live.\r\n\"You need that mental toughness as well to put the ball over, but great goal-kickers like Jonny Wilkinson come along very rarely.\"",
    "id": "N_414",
    "features": {
        "noun": "England",
        "pronoun": "himself",
        "verb": "have",
        "adjective": "cool",
        "adverb": "as"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "EnglandwhowillwhohavewhotowhotakewhoonwhoIrelandwhoinwhothewhoSixwhoNationswhowithoutwhocaptainwhoandwhogoal-kickerwhoJonnywhoWilkinson,whoaccordingwhotowhohiswhoNewcastlewhobosswhoRobwhoAndrew.\r\n\"JonnywhoWilkinsonwhohaswhoprovedwhohimselfwhoawhocoolwhocustomerwhowithwhoaroundwhoanwho80%whokickingwhosuccesswhorate,\"whoHarewhotoldwhoBBCwhoRadiowhoFivewhoLive.\r\n\"Youwhoneedwhothatwhomentalwhotoughnesswhoaswhowellwhotowhoputwhothewhoballwhoover,whobutwhogreatwhogoal-kickerswholikewhoJonnywhoWilkinsonwhocomewhoalongwhoverywhorarely.\"?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tries from Jonathan Thomas, Tom Shanklin and Martyn Williams gave the visitors a 19-5 half-time advantage.\r\nLuciano Orquera did reply with one for Italy but second-half efforts from Brent Cockbain, Shane Williams and Robert Sidoli sealed victory.\r\nFly-half Stephen Jones added four conversions as Wales maintained their superb start to this year's tournament.\r\nBut a clever high kick from Henson almost brought a try for Hal Luscombe when Roland de Marigny and Ludovico Nitoglia made a hash of claiming it as the ball bounced into touch.\r\nWales regained control with a second try in the 21st minute, Henson lobbing up a high kick to the left corner where Shanklin jumped higher than Nitoglia to dot down his 15th Test try.\r\nHenson sent Luscombe streaking away and when he off-loaded to Martyn Williams, the flanker showed his nous to ground the ball against the padding of the post, Jones adding the conversion.",
    "id": "N_415",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tries",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "gave",
        "adjective": "19-5",
        "adverb": "almost"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Maggs, who will win his 67th cap, was the obvious replacement at centre while Shane Horgan was always likely to be moved from the wing.\r\n: Murphy, Dempsey, Horgan, Maggs, Hickie, O'Gara, Stringer, Corrigan, Byrne, Hayes, O'Kelly, O'Connell, capt, S Easterby, O'Connor, Foley.",
    "id": "N_416",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Maggs,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "win",
        "adjective": "obvious",
        "adverb": "always"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Maggs, who will win his 67th cap, was the obvious replacement at centre while Shane who was always likely to be moved from the wing.\r\n: Murphy, Dempsey, who, Maggs, Hickie, O'Gara, Stringer, Corrigan, Byrne, Hayes, O'Kelly, O'Connell, capt, S Easterby, O'Connor, Foley.?",
        "answer": "Horgan"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "O'Driscoll was originally named in the starting line-up but has failed to recover from the hamstring injury he picked up in the win over Italy.\r\nFellow centre Gordon D'Arcy is also struggling with a hamstring injury and he will undergo a fitness test on Friday to see if he can play.",
    "id": "N_417",
    "features": {
        "noun": "O'Driscoll",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "starting",
        "adverb": "originally"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "O'Driscollwhatwaswhatoriginallywhatnamedwhatinwhatthewhatstartingwhatline-upwhatbutwhathaswhatfailedwhattowhatrecoverwhatfromwhatthewhathamstringwhatinjurywhathewhatpickedwhatupwhatinwhatthewhatwinwhatoverwhatItaly.\r\nFellowwhatcentrewhatGordonwhatD'ArcywhatiswhatalsowhatstrugglingwhatwithwhatawhathamstringwhatinjurywhatandwhathewhatwillwhatundergowhatawhatfitnesswhattestwhatonwhatFridaywhattowhatseewhatifwhathewhatcanwhatplay.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Bath and England centre Mike Tindall believes he can make this summer's Lions tour, despite missing most of the season through injury.\r\nBut Tindall, who recently signed for Bath's west-country rivals Gloucester, told Rugby Special he would be fit in time for the tour to New Zealand.",
    "id": "N_418",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Bath",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "centre",
        "adjective": "summer's",
        "adverb": "recently"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "BathwhoandwhoEnglandwhocentrewhoMikewhoTindallwhobelieveswhohewhocanwhomakewhothiswhosummer'swhoLionswhotour,whodespitewhomissingwhomostwhoofwhothewhoseasonwhothroughwhoinjury.\r\nButwhoTindall,whowhowhorecentlywhosignedwhoforwhoBath'swhowest-countrywhorivalswhoGloucester,whotoldwhoRugbywhoSpecialwhohewhowouldwhobewhofitwhoinwhotimewhoforwhothewhotourwhotowhoNewwhoZealand.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Wasps flanker replaces Denis Leamy but O'Connor knows that the Munster man will be pushing hard for a recall for the following game against England.\r\n\"Obviously the breakdown a big part of what I do on the pitch so I'm hoping to hold some influence there against what is a very solid Scottish pack.\" O'Connor will be winning his third cap after making his debut in the victory over South Africa last November.",
    "id": "N_419",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Wasps",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "knows",
        "adjective": "hard",
        "adverb": "\"Obviously"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhoWaspswhoflankerwhoreplaceswhoDeniswhoLeamywhobutwhoO'ConnorwhoknowswhothatwhothewhoMunsterwhomanwhowillwhobewhopushingwhohardwhoforwhoawhorecallwhoforwhothewhofollowingwhogamewhoagainstwhoEngland.\r\n\"ObviouslywhothewhobreakdownwhoawhobigwhopartwhoofwhowhatwhoIwhodowhoonwhothewhopitchwhosowhoI'mwhohopingwhotowhoholdwhosomewhoinfluencewhotherewhoagainstwhowhatwhoiswhoawhoverywhosolidwhoScottishwhopack.\"whoO'ConnorwhowillwhobewhowinningwhohiswhothirdwhocapwhoafterwhomakingwhohiswhodebutwhoinwhothewhovictorywhooverwhoSouthwhoAfricawholastwhoNovember.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tim Henman saved a match point before fighting back to defeat British rival Greg Rusedski 4-6 7-6 (8-6) 6-4 at the Dubai Tennis Championships on Tuesday.\r\nServe was held by both players with few alarms until the seventh game of the final set, when Rusedski's wild volley gave Henman a vital break.\r\nRusedski won his service game but Henman took the first of his three match points with a service winner to secure his place in the second round at Dubai for the first time in three years.",
    "id": "N_420",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tim",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "saved",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tim who saved a match point before fighting back to defeat British rival Greg Rusedski 4-6 7-6 (8-6) 6-4 at the Dubai Tennis Championships on Tuesday.\r\nServe was held by both players with few alarms until the seventh game of the final set, when Rusedski's wild volley gave who a vital break.\r\nRusedski won his service game but who took the first of his three match points with a service winner to secure his place in the second round at Dubai for the first time in three years.?",
        "answer": "Henman"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Marat Safin suffered a shock loss to unseeded Nicolas Kiefer in round one of the Dubai Tennis Championships.",
    "id": "N_421",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Marat",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "suffered",
        "adjective": "unseeded",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Marat who suffered a shock loss to unseeded Nicolas Kiefer in round one of the Dubai Tennis Championships.?",
        "answer": "Safin"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former world number one Juan Carlos Ferrero insists he can get back to his best despite a tough start to 2005.\r\nThe 2003 French Open champion has slipped to 64 in the world after a year of illness and injuries in 2004, but is confident that his form will return.\r\nAmong the low points of a difficult year for Ferrero was the decision of Spain captain Jordi Arrese to drop him for the Davis Cup final against the USA.\r\n\"It was difficult because I had been playing well for the whole year and the coaches told me that I would play,\" said Ferrero.",
    "id": "N_422",
    "features": {
        "noun": "world",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "insists",
        "adjective": "Former",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former world number one Juan Carlos Ferrero insists who can get back to his best despite a tough start to 2005.\r\nTwho 2003 French Open champion has slipped to 64 in twho world after a year of illness and injuries in 2004, but is confident that his form will return.\r\nAmong twho low points of a difficult year for Ferrero was twho decision of Spain captain Jordi Arrese to drop him for twho Davis Cup final against twho USA.\r\n\"It was difficult because I had been playing well for twho whole year and twho coacwhos told me that I would play,\" said Ferrero.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Roddick into San Jose final\r\nAndy Roddick will play Cyril Saulnier in the final of the SAP Open in San Jose on Sunday.\r\nAnd Saulnier survived an injury scare in his semi-final with seventh-seeded Austrian Jurgen Melzer.",
    "id": "N_423",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Roddick",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "play",
        "adjective": "final",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who into San Jose final\r\nAndy who will play Cyril Saulnier in the final of the SAP Open in San Jose on Sunday.\r\nAnd Saulnier survived an injury scare in his semi-final with seventh-seeded Austrian Jurgen Melzer.?",
        "answer": "Roddick"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World number one Roger Federer added the Dubai Championship trophy to his long list of successes - but not before he was given a test by Ivan Ljubicic.\r\nThe match was a re-run of last week's final at the World Indoor Tournament in Rotterdam, where Federer triumphed, but not until Ljubicic had stretched him for five sets.\r\n\"I really wanted to get off to a good start this time, and I did, and I could really play with confidence while he still looking for his rhythm,\" Federer said.",
    "id": "N_424",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "added",
        "adjective": "long",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhonumberwhoonewhoRogerwhoFedererwhoaddedwhothewhoDubaiwhoChampionshipwhotrophywhotowhohiswholongwholistwhoofwhosuccesseswho-whobutwhonotwhobeforewhohewhowaswhogivenwhoawhotestwhobywhoIvanwhoLjubicic.\r\nThewhomatchwhowaswhoawhore-runwhoofwholastwhoweek'swhofinalwhoatwhothewhoWorldwhoIndoorwhoTournamentwhoinwhoRotterdam,whowherewhoFedererwhotriumphed,whobutwhonotwhountilwhoLjubicicwhohadwhostretchedwhohimwhoforwhofivewhosets.\r\n\"Iwhoreallywhowantedwhotowhogetwhooffwhotowhoawhogoodwhostartwhothiswhotime,whoandwhoIwhodid,whoandwhoIwhocouldwhoreallywhoplaywhowithwhoconfidencewhowhilewhohewhostillwholookingwhoforwhohiswhorhythm,\"whoFedererwhosaid.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Fifteen-year-old Donald Young's first appearance in an ATP tennis tournament proved brief as the teenager went out in round one of the San Jose Open.\r\nYoung, who beat two players ranked in the top 200 when he was just 14, was only 2-1 down in the first set before losing 10 of the next 13 games.\r\nAgassi has won the San Jose five times, but his run of three straight titles ended last year when he fell to Mardy Fish in the semi-finals.",
    "id": "N_425",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Donald",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "proved",
        "adjective": "Fifteen-year-old",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Fifteen-year-old Donald Young's first appearance in an ATP tennis tournament proved brief as the what went out in round one of the San Jose Open.\r\nYoung, who beat two players ranked in the top 200 when he was just 14, was only 2-1 down in the first set before losing 10 of the next 13 games.\r\nAgassi has won the San Jose five times, but his run of three straight titles ended last year when he fell to Mardy Fish in the semi-finals.?",
        "answer": "teenager"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Second seed Andre Agassi suffered a comprehensive defeat by Jurgen Melzer in the quarter-finals of the SAP Open.\r\n\"It's always tough to come out to play Andre.\r\n\"I didn't want him to play his game.",
    "id": "N_426",
    "features": {
        "noun": "seed",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "suffered",
        "adjective": "Second",
        "adverb": "always"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Second seed Andre who suffered a comprehensive defeat by Jurgen Melzer in the quarter-finals of the SAP Open.\r\n\"It's always tough to come out to play Andre.\r\n\"I didn't want him to play his game.?",
        "answer": "Agassi"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Top seed Roger Federer had to save two match points before squeezing past Juan Carlos Ferrero at the Dubai Open.\r\nThe world number one took two hours 15 minutes to earn his 4-6 6-3 7-6 victory, saving match points at 6-4 in the tiebreak before claiming it 8-6.",
    "id": "N_427",
    "features": {
        "noun": "seed",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "Top",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Top seed Roger who had to save two match points before squeezing past Juan Carlos Ferrero at the Dubai Open.\r\nThe world number one took two hours 15 minutes to earn his 4-6 6-3 7-6 victory, saving match points at 6-4 in the tiebreak before claiming it 8-6.?",
        "answer": "Federer"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Rafael Nadal continued his run of fine form to beat Guillermo Canas and reach the Mexican Open semis in Acapulco.\r\nArgentine wild card Mariano Puerta continued his improbable run, outlasting Felix Mantilla 6-4 3-6 7-6.",
    "id": "N_428",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Rafael",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "continued",
        "adjective": "fine",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "RafaelwhoNadalwhocontinuedwhohiswhorunwhoofwhofinewhoformwhotowhobeatwhoGuillermowhoCanaswhoandwhoreachwhothewhoMexicanwhoOpenwhosemiswhoinwhoAcapulco.\r\nArgentinewhowildwhocardwhoMarianowhoPuertawhocontinuedwhohiswhoimprobablewhorun,whooutlastingwhoFelixwhoMantillawho6-4who3-6who7-6.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Daniela Hantuchova moved into the quarter-finals of the Dubai Open, after beating Elene Likhotseva of Russia 7-5 6-4, and now faces Serena Williams.\r\nDavenport defeated China's Jie Zheng 6-2 7-5, while French Open champion Myskina sailed through after her opponent Marion Bartoli retired hurt.\r\n\"I feel I have an advantage (over Serena) because I have already played two matches on these courts,\" she said.",
    "id": "N_429",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Daniela",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "moved",
        "adjective": "7-5",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Daniela Hantuchova moved into the quarter-finals of the Dubai Open, after beating Elene Likhotseva of which location 7-5 6-4, and now faces Serena Williams.\r\nDavenport defeated China's Jie Zheng 6-2 7-5, while French Open champion Myskina sailed through after her opponent Marion Bartoli retired hurt.\r\n\"I feel I have an advantage (over Serena) because I have already played two matches on these courts,\" she said.?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A knee injury has forced Arvind Parmar out of Great Britain's Davis Cup tie in Israel and left Alex Bogdanovic in line to take the second singles place.\r\nThe unheralded Sherwood was the surprise inclusion when the squad was announced last week, and Bates said: \"David has earned his place in this squad on the merit of his form and results over the last 12 months.\" The 6ft 4in Sherwood is ranked 264th in the world and the LTA have high hopes for him after Futures tournament wins in Wrexham and Edinburgh.",
    "id": "N_430",
    "features": {
        "noun": "injury",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "knee",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "A knee injury has forced Arvind Parmar out of Great Britain's Davis Cup tie in which location and left Alex Bogdanovic in line to take the second singles place.\r\nThe unheralded Sherwood was the surprise inclusion when the squad was announced last week, and Bates said: \"David has earned his place in this squad on the merit of his form and results over the last 12 months.\" The 6ft 4in Sherwood is ranked 264th in the world and the LTA have high hopes for him after Futures tournament wins in Wrexham and Edinburgh.?",
        "answer": "Israel"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Reacting to a disputed comment by All England Club chairman Tim Phillips, the American said: \"I think it is highly insulting if prize money is taken away.\r\nMen's tennis is exciting as well, but the women have it right now.",
    "id": "N_431",
    "features": {
        "noun": "comment",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "Reacting",
        "adjective": "insulting",
        "adverb": "highly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Reacting to a disputed comment by All England Club chairman Tim Phillips, the American said: \"I think it is highly insulting if prize what is taken away.\r\nMen's tennis is exciting as well, but the women have it right now.?",
        "answer": "money"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World number one Roger Federer added the Dubai Championship trophy to his long list of successes - but not before he was given a test by Ivan Ljubicic.\r\nThe match was a re-run of last week's final at the World Indoor Tournament in Rotterdam, where Federer triumphed, but not until Ljubicic had stretched him all the way.\r\n\"I really wanted to get off to a good start this time, and I did, and I could really play with confidence while he still looking for his rhythm,\" Federer said.",
    "id": "N_432",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "added",
        "adjective": "long",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "WorldwhonumberwhoonewhoRogerwhoFedererwhoaddedwhothewhoDubaiwhoChampionshipwhotrophywhotowhohiswholongwholistwhoofwhosuccesseswho-whobutwhonotwhobeforewhohewhowaswhogivenwhoawhotestwhobywhoIvanwhoLjubicic.\r\nThewhomatchwhowaswhoawhore-runwhoofwholastwhoweek'swhofinalwhoatwhothewhoWorldwhoIndoorwhoTournamentwhoinwhoRotterdam,whowherewhoFedererwhotriumphed,whobutwhonotwhountilwhoLjubicicwhohadwhostretchedwhohimwhoallwhothewhoway.\r\n\"Iwhoreallywhowantedwhotowhogetwhooffwhotowhoawhogoodwhostartwhothiswhotime,whoandwhoIwhodid,whoandwhoIwhocouldwhoreallywhoplaywhowithwhoconfidencewhowhilewhohewhostillwholookingwhoforwhohiswhorhythm,\"whoFedererwhosaid.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Third seed Tim Henman slumped to a straight sets defeat in his rain-interrupted Dubai Open quarter-final against Ivan Ljubicic.\r\nAfterwards, Henman was left cursing the weather and the umpire after seven breaks for rain during the match.",
    "id": "N_433",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Third",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "slumped",
        "adjective": "straight",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Third seed Tim who slumped to a straight sets defeat in his rain-interrupted Dubai Open quarter-final against Ivan Ljubicic.\r\nAfterwards, who was left cursing the weather and the umpire after seven breaks for rain during the match.?",
        "answer": "Henman"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mirza needed attention to an ankle injury after the second game against Kuznetsova.\r\n\"I played a great match and I think (the crowd) did it again.\r\n\"It was such a tough first-round match and I am glad to come through,\" said Hantuchova.",
    "id": "N_434",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mirza",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "needed",
        "adjective": "ankle",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who needed attention to an ankle injury after the second game against Kuznetsova.\r\n\"I played a great match and I think (the crowd) did it again.\r\n\"It was such a tough first-round match and I am glad to come through,\" said Hantuchova.?",
        "answer": "Mirza"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Daniela Hantuchova moved into the quarter-finals of the Dubai Open, after beating Elene Likhotseva of Russia 7-5 6-4, and now faces Serena Williams.\r\nDavenport defeated China's Jie Zheng 6-2 7-5, while French Open champion Myskina sailed through after her opponent Marion Bartoli retired hurt.\r\n\"I feel I have an advantage (over Serena) because I have already played two matches on these courts,\" she said.",
    "id": "N_435",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Daniela",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "moved",
        "adjective": "7-5",
        "adverb": "now"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Daniela Hantuchova moved into the quarter-finals of the Dubai Open, after beating Elene Likhotseva of which location 7-5 6-4, and now faces Serena Williams.\r\nDavenport defeated China's Jie Zheng 6-2 7-5, while French Open champion Myskina sailed through after her opponent Marion Bartoli retired hurt.\r\n\"I feel I have an advantage (over Serena) because I have already played two matches on these courts,\" she said.?",
        "answer": "Russia"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Andrew Murray will become Britain's youngest-ever Davis Cup player after it was confirmed he will play in the doubles against Israel on Saturday.\r\nIsrael have some really good players - and their doubles pair of Andy Ram and Jonathan Erlich are among the top eight in the world - but I fancy our chances,\" he said.",
    "id": "N_436",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Andrew",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "become",
        "adjective": "youngest-ever",
        "adverb": "really"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Andrew Murray will become Britain's youngest-ever Davis Cup player after it was confirmed who will play in twho doubles against Israel on Saturday.\r\nIsrael have some really good players - and twhoir doubles pair of Andy Ram and Jonathan Erlich are among twho top eight in twho world - but I fancy our chances,\" who said.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "World number one Lindsay Davenport has criticised Wimbledon over the issue of equal prize money for women.\r\nReacting to a disputed comment by All England Club chairman Tim Phillips, the American said: \"I think it is highly insulting if prize money is taken away.",
    "id": "N_437",
    "features": {
        "noun": "World",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "equal",
        "adverb": "highly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "World number one Lindsay who has criticised Wimbledon over the issue of equal prize money for women.\r\nReacting to a disputed comment by All England Club chairman Tim Phillips, the American said: \"I think it is highly insulting if prize money is taken away.?",
        "answer": "Davenport"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Venus Williams suffered a first-round defeat for the first time in four years at the Dubai Championships.\r\n\"But everyone is beatable and I am looking forward to a great match.\" Williams though blamed her defeat by Farina Elia on injuries.",
    "id": "N_438",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Venus",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "suffered",
        "adjective": "first-round",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Venus who suffered a first-round defeat for the first time in four years at the Dubai Championships.\r\n\"But everyone is beatable and I am looking forward to a great match.\" who though blamed her defeat by Farina Elia on injuries.?",
        "answer": "Williams"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The veteran Martinez found herself in trouble early on against Vinci with the Italian clinching the set thanks to breaks in the third and 11th games.",
    "id": "N_439",
    "features": {
        "noun": "veteran",
        "pronoun": "herself",
        "verb": "found",
        "adjective": "early",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhatveteranwhatMartinezwhatfoundwhatherselfwhatinwhattroublewhatearlywhatonwhatagainstwhatVinciwhatwithwhatthewhatItalianwhatclinchingwhatthewhatsetwhatthankswhattowhatbreakswhatinwhatthewhatthirdwhatandwhat11thwhatgames.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Men's champion Marat Safin remains fourth in the ATP rankings while beaten finalist Lleyton Hewitt replaces Andy Roddick as world number two.",
    "id": "N_440",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Men's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "remains",
        "adjective": "fourth",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Men's champion Marat Safin remains fourth in the ATP rankings while beaten finalist Lleyton who replaces Andy Roddick as world number two.?",
        "answer": "Hewitt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Only last year she insisted that a comeback was unlikely, but speaking in Thaliand Hingis admitted: \"I said that because I didn't know what would happen with my body.\" Her appearance will also benefit charities in the region and the Swiss star will donate her prize money.",
    "id": "N_441",
    "features": {
        "noun": "year",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "insisted",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "Only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Onlywhatlastwhatyearwhatshewhatinsistedwhatthatwhatawhatcomebackwhatwaswhatunlikely,whatbutwhatspeakingwhatinwhatThaliandwhatHingiswhatadmitted:what\"IwhatsaidwhatthatwhatbecausewhatIwhatdidn'twhatknowwhatwhatwhatwouldwhathappenwhatwithwhatmywhatbody.\"whatHerwhatappearancewhatwillwhatalsowhatbenefitwhatcharitieswhatinwhatthewhatregionwhatandwhatthewhatSwisswhatstarwhatwillwhatdonatewhatherwhatprizewhatmoney.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tennis star Kim Clijsters will make her return from a career-threatening injury at the Antwerp WTA event in February.",
    "id": "N_442",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tennis",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "make",
        "adjective": "career-threatening",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tennis star Kim who will make her return from a career-threatening injury at the Antwerp WTA event in February.?",
        "answer": "Clijsters"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I felt like I was striking the ball much better,\" said Johansson.",
    "id": "N_443",
    "features": {
        "noun": "ball",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "felt",
        "adjective": "much",
        "adverb": "\"I"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"I felt like I was striking the ball much better,\" said who.?",
        "answer": "Johansson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Serena Williams has angrily rejected claims that she and sister Venus are a declining force in tennis.\r\nI don't know many who have done that.\" While Serena is through to the Australian Open semi-finals, Venus went out in the fourth round, meaning she has not gone further than the last eight in her last five Grand Slam appearances.\r\n\"She played a player (Alicia Molik) that just played out of her mind and Venus made some errors that she probably shouldn't have made.\" Serena also said people tended to forget the impact the 2003 murder of sister Yetunde Price had had on the family.",
    "id": "N_444",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Serena",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "sister",
        "adverb": "angrily"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "SerenawhoWilliamswhohaswhoangrilywhorejectedwhoclaimswhothatwhoshewhoandwhosisterwhoVenuswhoarewhoawhodecliningwhoforcewhoinwhotennis.\r\nIwhodon'twhoknowwhomanywhowhowhohavewhodonewhothat.\"whoWhilewhoSerenawhoiswhothroughwhotowhothewhoAustralianwhoOpenwhosemi-finals,whoVenuswhowentwhooutwhoinwhothewhofourthwhoround,whomeaningwhoshewhohaswhonotwhogonewhofurtherwhothanwhothewholastwhoeightwhoinwhoherwholastwhofivewhoGrandwhoSlamwhoappearances.\r\n\"Shewhoplayedwhoawhoplayerwho(AliciawhoMolik)whothatwhojustwhoplayedwhooutwhoofwhoherwhomindwhoandwhoVenuswhomadewhosomewhoerrorswhothatwhoshewhoprobablywhoshouldn'twhohavewhomade.\"whoSerenawhoalsowhosaidwhopeoplewhotendedwhotowhoforgetwhothewhoimpactwhothewho2003whomurderwhoofwhosisterwhoYetundewhoPricewhohadwhohadwhoonwhothewhofamily.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Top seed Lindsay Davenport booked her place in the last 16 of the Australian Open with a convincing 6-2 6-4 win over Nicole Vaidisova of the Czech Republic.\r\nThe American had too much power for her 15-year-old opponent, breaking twice in the first set and once in the second.\r\n\"I was fully expecting a tough opponent and was able to play well enough to get through it,\" said Davenport.\r\npowered her way into the fourth round with a straight sets win over Anna Smashnova.\r\nThe 10th seed equalled her best performance at a Grand Slam event when she beat unseeded Russian Nadia Petrova 6-3 6-2 to reach the fourth round.\r\n\"I played pretty well and it was nice to get through in straight sets.\" \"We were destined to meet, I guess,\" Williams said referring to her match with Molik.",
    "id": "N_445",
    "features": {
        "noun": "seed",
        "pronoun": "her",
        "verb": "booked",
        "adjective": "Top",
        "adverb": "too"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Top seed Lindsay who booked her place in the last 16 of the Australian Open with a convincing 6-2 6-4 win over Nicole Vaidisova of the Czech Republic.\r\nThe American had too much power for her 15-year-old opponent, breaking twice in the first set and once in the second.\r\n\"I was fully expecting a tough opponent and was able to play well enough to get through it,\" said who.\r\npowered her way into the fourth round with a straight sets win over Anna Smashnova.\r\nThe 10th seed equalled her best performance at a Grand Slam event when she beat unseeded Russian Nadia Petrova 6-3 6-2 to reach the fourth round.\r\n\"I played pretty well and it was nice to get through in straight sets.\" \"We were destined to meet, I guess,\" Williams said referring to her match with Molik.?",
        "answer": "Davenport"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Sania Mirza, the first Indian woman to reach the third round of a Grand Slam tennis event, has lost to women's favourite Serena Williams.\r\nThe 18-year-old Mirza, who got a wild card entry into the Australian Open in Melbourne, lost to Williams 1-6,4-6 in the third round.\r\nThe only other Indian woman to win a match at a Grand Slam is Nirupama Vaidyanathan.",
    "id": "N_446",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Sania",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "reach",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Sania who, the first Indian woman to reach the third round of a Grand Slam tennis event, has lost to women's favourite Serena Williams.\r\nThe 18-year-old who, who got a wild card entry into the Australian Open in Melbourne, lost to Williams 1-6,4-6 in the third round.\r\nThe only other Indian woman to win a match at a Grand Slam is Nirupama Vaidyanathan.?",
        "answer": "Mirza"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "US Open champion Svetlana Kuznetsova has tested positive for a banned drug, according to Belgian authorities.\r\nBelgian sports minister Claude Eerdekens said that the Russian world number five tested positive for the stimulant ephedrine on 19 December.\r\nShe can ask for it to be tested again.\" The situation remains unclear as the tournament was not commissioned by the World Anti-Doping Agency (Wada), the International Tennis Federation (ITF) or the Women's Tennis Accosiation (WTA).\r\n\"I have not been notified of any positive test, and I think it is unfair that it's come out the way it did.\" Eerdekens said that confirmation of the findings was sent last Friday to the player's address in Spain, as well as to the Belgian prosecutors' office and the Belgian and Russian tennis federations.",
    "id": "N_447",
    "features": {
        "noun": "US",
        "pronoun": "She",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "positive",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "US Open champion Svetlana who has tested positive for a banned drug, according to Belgian authorities.\r\nBelgian sports minister Claude Eerdekens said that the Russian world number five tested positive for the stimulant ephedrine on 19 December.\r\nShe can ask for it to be tested again.\" The situation remains unclear as the tournament was not commissioned by the World Anti-Doping Agency (Wada), the International Tennis Federation (ITF) or the Women's Tennis Accosiation (WTA).\r\n\"I have not been notified of any positive test, and I think it is unfair that it's come out the way it did.\" Eerdekens said that confirmation of the findings was sent last Friday to the player's address in Spain, as well as to the Belgian prosecutors' office and the Belgian and Russian tennis federations.?",
        "answer": "Kuznetsova"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tim Henman's decision to quit Davis Cup tennis has left the British team with a gargantuan void to fill.\r\nThe Yugoslavian-born Bogdanovic, though, is 184 places below Henman in the world rankings and has played just two cup ties - winning one and losing the other.\r\nHe said: \"Now we've dropped down to the Euro-Africa zone, the time was right for him to step down and let the young guys come to the fore.\" Britain's next opponents, Israel, are hardly likely to be quaking in their boots ahead of the 4-6 March match against a likely trio of Bogdanovic, Murray and the 187th-ranked Arvind Parmar.\r\n\"He has an enormous amount of self-confidence, judging by what he's said in the past.\" Bogdanovic, three years Murray's senior, has had a more troubled time under Britain's Davis Cup umbrella.",
    "id": "N_448",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tim",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "quit",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tim Henman's what to quit Davis Cup tennis has left the British team with a gargantuan void to fill.\r\nThe Yugoslavian-born Bogdanovic, though, is 184 places below Henman in the world rankings and has played just two cup ties - winning one and losing the other.\r\nHe said: \"Now we've dropped down to the Euro-Africa zone, the time was right for him to step down and let the young guys come to the fore.\" Britain's next opponents, Israel, are hardly likely to be quaking in their boots ahead of the 4-6 March match against a likely trio of Bogdanovic, Murray and the 187th-ranked Arvind Parmar.\r\n\"He has an enormous amount of self-confidence, judging by what he's said in the past.\" Bogdanovic, three years Murray's senior, has had a more troubled time under Britain's Davis Cup umbrella.?",
        "answer": "decision"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Lleyton Hewitt gave himself the perfect preparation for next week's Australian Open with victory over Ivo Minar in the final of the Sydney International.\r\n\"I've only played this tournament four times and I've won it four times.\" Hewitt went into the final as a short-priced favourite to clinch his 24th career title after dropping only one set all week.\r\nMinar, ranked 158th in the world, was forced to pull out of the Australian Open qualifying draw to play in his first ATP final.",
    "id": "N_449",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Lleyton",
        "pronoun": "himself",
        "verb": "gave",
        "adjective": "perfect",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Lleyton who gave himself the perfect preparation for next week's Australian Open with victory over Ivo Minar in the final of the Sydney International.\r\n\"I've only played this tournament four times and I've won it four times.\" who went into the final as a short-priced favourite to clinch his 24th career title after dropping only one set all week.\r\nMinar, ranked 158th in the world, was forced to pull out of the Australian Open qualifying draw to play in his first ATP final.?",
        "answer": "Hewitt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Moya confirmed afterwards: \"I'm donating my prize money from this tournament for the tsunami victims, hoping it makes some difference to their lives.\r\nHis contribution follows pledges by four other players to donate their prize money from the tournament, which went ahead after the 26 December disaster which has so far claimed at least 150,000 lives.",
    "id": "N_450",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Moya",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "confirmed",
        "adjective": "afterwards:",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Moya confirmed afterwards: \"I'm donating my prize money from this tournament for the tsunami victims, hoping who makes some difference to their lives.\r\nHis contribution follows pledges by four other players to donate their prize money from the tournament, which went ahead after the 26 December disaster which has so far claimed at least 150,000 lives.?",
        "answer": "it"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Rochus made the semi-finals at the Australian hardcourt championships in Adelaide last week and is naturally delighted with his form.",
    "id": "N_451",
    "features": {
        "noun": "semi-finals",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "made",
        "adjective": "Australian",
        "adverb": "Rochus"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Rochuswhomadewhothewhosemi-finalswhoatwhothewhoAustralianwhohardcourtwhochampionshipswhoinwhoAdelaidewholastwhoweekwhoandwhoiswhonaturallywhodelightedwhowithwhohiswhoform.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Second seed Joachim Johansson won his second career title with a 7-5 6-3 win over Taylor Dent at the Australian hardcourt championships in Adelaide.",
    "id": "N_452",
    "features": {
        "noun": "seed",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "won",
        "adjective": "Second",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Second seed Joachim who won his second career title with a 7-5 6-3 win over Taylor Dent at the Australian hardcourt championships in Adelaide.?",
        "answer": "Johansson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The former world number one will play at the Volvo Women's Open in Pattaya, which starts on 31 January, as part of her charity work in the region.",
    "id": "N_453",
    "features": {
        "noun": "world",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "play",
        "adjective": "former",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "which"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Dominik Hrbaty, who had not lost a set in his three singles matches in the group stages, then upset world number seven Guillermo Coria 6-4 6-1.\r\nWorld number 31 Hantuchova, ranked two places above Dulko, looked nervous as she dropped the first four games of the match.\r\n\"I was so nervous because I really wanted to win for the team and for Dominik as he played so well all week,\" she said.",
    "id": "N_454",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Dominik",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "had",
        "adjective": "upset",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "who"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Elena Dementieva swept aside defending champion Venus Williams 6-3 6-2 to win Hong Kong's Champions Challenge event.\r\nI was trying to play my best and I really did it,\" said Dementieva.",
    "id": "N_455",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Elena",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "swept",
        "adjective": "6-3",
        "adverb": "aside"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Elena who swept aside defending champion Venus Williams 6-3 6-2 to win Hong Kong's Champions Challenge event.\r\nI was trying to play my best and I really did it,\" said who.?",
        "answer": "Dementieva"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Number one men's seed Lleyton Hewitt begins his quest for a fourth Sydney title on Tuesday when he plays Karol Beck.",
    "id": "N_456",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Number",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "begins",
        "adjective": "fourth",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Number one men's seed Lleyton Hewitt begins his quest for a fourth Sydney title on Tuesday wwhon who plays Karol Beck.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I felt like I was striking the ball much better,\" said Johansson.\r\n\"When you've been number one in the world for a couple of years and won a couple of slams, you look at the big picture and what motivates you,\" said Hewitt.",
    "id": "N_457",
    "features": {
        "noun": "ball",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "felt",
        "adjective": "much",
        "adverb": "\"I"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"I felt like I was striking the ball much better,\" said who.\r\n\"When you've been number one in the world for a couple of years and won a couple of slams, you look at the big picture and what motivates you,\" said Hewitt.?",
        "answer": "Johansson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Swiss world number one reeled off a series winners to outclass the Spaniard and set up a semi-final match against Russian Nikolay Davydenko.\r\nFederer, who lost in the quarter-final in his last Qatar appearance in 2003, was happy with his form.",
    "id": "N_458",
    "features": {
        "noun": "world",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "reeled",
        "adjective": "Swiss",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThewhatSwisswhatworldwhatnumberwhatonewhatreeledwhatoffwhatawhatserieswhatwinnerswhattowhatoutclasswhatthewhatSpaniardwhatandwhatsetwhatupwhatawhatsemi-finalwhatmatchwhatagainstwhatRussianwhatNikolaywhatDavydenko.\r\nFederer,whatwhowhatlostwhatinwhatthewhatquarter-finalwhatinwhathiswhatlastwhatQatarwhatappearancewhatinwhat2003,whatwaswhathappywhatwithwhathiswhatform.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I just really wanted to make sure my right knee was going to be able to really withstand all the rigours of the whole year coming up,\" she said.",
    "id": "N_459",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"I",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "wanted",
        "adjective": "sure",
        "adverb": "just"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"I just really wanted to make sure my right knee was going to be able to really withstand all the rigours of the whole year coming up,\" who said.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greg Rusedski has criticised the governing body of men's tennis for not releasing contamination-free supplements in time for the new season.\r\n\"This event comes in the hottest period of the year, so you would hope the stuff would be available for it.\" The British number two escaped a possible ban last year when he persuaded a tribunal that a positive doping test was the result of contaminated ATP supplements.",
    "id": "N_460",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Greg",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "men's",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Greg who has criticised the governing body of men's tennis for not releasing contamination-free supplements in time for the new season.\r\n\"This event comes in the hottest period of the year, so you would hope the stuff would be available for it.\" The British number two escaped a possible ban last year when he persuaded a tribunal that a positive doping test was the result of contaminated ATP supplements.?",
        "answer": "Rusedski"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Navratilova, who made a comeback after retiring in 1994, will play doubles and mixed doubles events in 2005.\r\nI'm still that good.\" Navratilova has won three Grand Slam mixed doubles titles since she came out of retirement.",
    "id": "N_461",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Navratilova,",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "made",
        "adjective": "mixed",
        "adverb": "still"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "French prodigy Gael Monfils underlined his huge promise by beating French Open champion Gaston Gaudio 6-4 7-6 (7-4) in the first round of the Qatar Open.",
    "id": "N_462",
    "features": {
        "noun": "prodigy",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "underlined",
        "adjective": "French",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "French prodigy Gael who underlined his huge promise by beating French Open champion Gaston Gaudio 6-4 7-6 (7-4) in the first round of the Qatar Open.?",
        "answer": "Monfils"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Former world number one Jimmy Connors is planning a long-term relationship with the Lawn Tennis Association to help unearth the next Tim Henman.\r\nThe kids will ask: 'What am I doing there?'\" LTA chief executive, John Crowther, added: \"The relationship that Jimmy's already started to develop with the coaches and the players has said to us that we'd like some more of it.\r\n\"We want to use Jimmy for a number of weeks a year and we hope this is the beginning of a good long-term relationship.\"\r\nSpeaking from La Manga, LTA performance director David Felgate told BBC Sport: \"Jimmy was fantastic with the players and the coaches, and very humble considering what he's achieved.",
    "id": "N_463",
    "features": {
        "noun": "world",
        "pronoun": "'What",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "Former",
        "adverb": "already"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Former world what one Jimmy Connors is planning a long-term relationship with the Lawn Tennis Association to help unearth the next Tim Henman.\r\nThe kids will ask: 'What am I doing there?'\" LTA chief executive, John Crowther, added: \"The relationship that Jimmy's already started to develop with the coaches and the players has said to us that we'd like some more of it.\r\n\"We want to use Jimmy for a what of weeks a year and we hope this is the beginning of a good long-term relationship.\"\r\nSpeaking from La Manga, LTA performance director David Felgate told BBC Sport: \"Jimmy was fantastic with the players and the coaches, and very humble considering what he's achieved.?",
        "answer": "number"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Justine Henin-Hardenne lost to Elena Dementieva in a comeback exhibition match in Belgium on Sunday for her second defeat in two days.\r\n\"But I think there'll be less pressure than last time even if I am champion.\" Henin-Hardenne was speaking after a 6-2 5-7 6-2 loss to world number six Dementieva in Charleroi, Belgium, on Sunday.\r\n\"My body has to get accustomed again to the stress, the rhythm.\" Henin-Hardenne slid down the world rankings in the second half of 2004 after contracting the illness in April.",
    "id": "N_464",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Justine",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "lost",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": "there'll"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Justine who lost to Elena Dementieva in a comeback exhibition match in Belgium on Sunday for her second defeat in two days.\r\n\"But I think there'll be less pressure than last time even if I am champion.\" who was speaking after a 6-2 5-7 6-2 loss to world number six Dementieva in Charleroi, Belgium, on Sunday.\r\n\"My body has to get accustomed again to the stress, the rhythm.\" who slid down the world rankings in the second half of 2004 after contracting the illness in April.?",
        "answer": "Henin-Hardenne"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Spain won the Davis Cup for the second time in their history when Carlos Moya beat the USA's Andy Roddick in the fourth rubber in Seville.\r\nMardy Fish beat Tommy Robredo 7-6 (8-6) 6-2 in the final dead rubber to cut Spain's winning margin to 3-2.\r\nAnd the home fans gave vociferous support to their players, with 18-year-old Nadal and Moya winning both Friday's singles rubbers.\r\nWild celebrations followed, with an emotional Moya congratulated by his team-mates, including Nadal, who at 18 years and 187 days becomes the youngest ever victor in Davis Cup history.",
    "id": "N_465",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Spain",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "won",
        "adjective": "second",
        "adverb": "when"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Spain won the Davis Cup for the second time in their history when Carlos who beat the USA's Andy Roddick in the fourth rubber in Seville.\r\nMardy Fish beat Tommy Robredo 7-6 (8-6) 6-2 in the final dead rubber to cut Spain's winning margin to 3-2.\r\nAnd the home fans gave vociferous support to their players, with 18-year-old Nadal and who winning both Friday's singles rubbers.\r\nWild celebrations followed, with an emotional who congratulated by his team-mates, including Nadal, who at 18 years and 187 days becomes the youngest ever victor in Davis Cup history.?",
        "answer": "Moya"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jennifer Capriati has become the third leading lady to withdraw from the Australian Open because of injury.",
    "id": "N_466",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jennifer",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "third",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jennifer who has become the third leading lady to withdraw from the Australian Open because of injury.?",
        "answer": "Capriati"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tim Henman opened his 2005 campaign with a 6-1 7-5 victory over Argentine David Nalbandian at the Kooyong Classic exhibition tournament on Wednesday.\r\nHenman made an impressive start to the year, only faltering against Nalbandian when serving for the match at 5-4.\r\n\"I'm not the most flexible and at the end of the year I was pretty exhausted and wanted to have a couple of weeks where I didn't do anything,\" said Henman.\r\n\"I liked the way the match played out and, maybe excluding a few second serve returns, I felt like I was doing most things pretty darn well for the first match.\"",
    "id": "N_467",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tim",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "opened",
        "adjective": "6-1",
        "adverb": "only"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tim who opened his 2005 campaign with a 6-1 7-5 victory over Argentine David Nalbandian at the Kooyong Classic exhibition tournament on Wednesday.\r\nwho made an impressive start to the year, only faltering against Nalbandian when serving for the match at 5-4.\r\n\"I'm not the most flexible and at the end of the year I was pretty exhausted and wanted to have a couple of weeks where I didn't do anything,\" said who.\r\n\"I liked the way the match played out and, maybe excluding a few second serve returns, I felt like I was doing most things pretty darn well for the first match.\"?",
        "answer": "Henman"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Carlos Moya described Spain's Davis Cup victory as the highlight of his career after he beat Andy Roddick to end the USA's challenge in Seville.\r\n\"What I have lived today I do not think I will live again.\" Spain's only other Davis Cup title came two years ago in Valencia, when they beat Australia.\r\n\"Some people have said that I am obsessed but I think that it is better this way.\r\n\"He had been waiting years to be in this position.\" Spain's victory was also remarkable for the performance of Rafael Nadal, who beat Roddick in the opening singles.",
    "id": "N_468",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Carlos",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "described",
        "adjective": "other",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Carlos Moya described Spain's Davis Cup victory as twho highlight of his career after who beat Andy Roddick to end twho USA's challenge in Seville.\r\n\"What I have lived today I do not think I will live again.\" Spain's only otwhor Davis Cup title came two years ago in Valencia, wwhon twhoy beat Australia.\r\n\"Some people have said that I am obsessed but I think that it is better this way.\r\n\"He had been waiting years to be in this position.\" Spain's victory was also remarkable for twho performance of Rafael Nadal, who beat Roddick in twho opening singles.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Carlos Moya described Spain's Davis Cup victory as the highlight of his career after he beat Andy Roddick to end the USA's challenge in Seville.\r\n\"What I have lived today I do not think I will live again.\" Spain's only other Davis Cup title came two years ago in Valencia, when they beat Australia.\r\n\"Some people have said that I am obsessed but I think that it is better this way.\r\n\"He had been waiting years to be in this position.\" Spain's victory was also remarkable for the performance of Rafael Nadal, who beat Roddick in the opening singles.",
    "id": "N_469",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Carlos",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "described",
        "adjective": "other",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Carlos Moya described Spain's Davis Cup victory as twho highlight of his career after who beat Andy Roddick to end twho USA's challenge in Seville.\r\n\"What I have lived today I do not think I will live again.\" Spain's only otwhor Davis Cup title came two years ago in Valencia, wwhon twhoy beat Australia.\r\n\"Some people have said that I am obsessed but I think that it is better this way.\r\n\"He had been waiting years to be in this position.\" Spain's victory was also remarkable for twho performance of Rafael Nadal, who beat Roddick in twho opening singles.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Jennifer Capriati has become the third leading lady to withdraw from the Australian Open because of injury.",
    "id": "N_470",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Jennifer",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "third",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Jennifer who has become the third leading lady to withdraw from the Australian Open because of injury.?",
        "answer": "Capriati"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The United States kept the Davis Cup final alive with victory in Saturday's doubles rubber, leaving Spain 2-1 ahead going into the final day.\r\nMasters Cup champions Mike and Bob Bryan thrashed Juan Carlos Ferrero and Tommy Robredo 6-0 6-3 6-2 in front of a partisan crowd in Seville.\r\n\"It feels good to give those guys another shot, and Spain has to go to sleep on that.\" Bob Bryan added: \"I'm really confident in Andy winning that first match, and then anything can happen.\" Spain coach Jordi Arrese chose to rest 18-year-old Nadal in the doubles after his epic singles win over Roddick on Friday.",
    "id": "N_471",
    "features": {
        "noun": "United",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "kept",
        "adjective": "final",
        "adverb": "ahead"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "States"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Roger Federer - nice bloke, fantastic tennis player - the ultimate sportsman.\r\nHewitt, at times in Houston, showed form which easily matched his Grand Slam-winning efforts of 2001 and 2002.\r\nI am dominating the game right now and I hope it continues!\" The number one player in the world is also the main man for promoting the sport off court.\r\n\"If I can promote tennis and the sport then that is good for me.\r\nNow he just needs to find a way of winning the French Open, the one Grand Slam to so far elude him.",
    "id": "N_472",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Roger",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "showed",
        "adjective": "nice",
        "adverb": "easily"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": ""
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Amelie Mauresmo and Maria Sharapova won their opening matches at the Tour Championships in Los Angeles.\r\nMauresmo spent five weeks at number one after the US Open before injury ushered Davenport back in front.\r\n\"She got mad a little bit and I played some great tennis,\" said Mauresmo, who was runner-up to Kim Clijsters in last year's final.\r\nBut I was fighting.\" Sharapova, who lost 6-2 6-2 to Kuznetsova in Beijing in September, said: \"In Beijing, she was coming off such a big winning streak [14 matches] and she was unstoppable.",
    "id": "N_473",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Amelie",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "won",
        "adjective": "little",
        "adverb": "back"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "AmeliewhoMauresmowhoandwhoMariawhoSharapovawhowonwhotheirwhoopeningwhomatcheswhoatwhothewhoTourwhoChampionshipswhoinwhoLoswhoAngeles.\r\nMauresmowhospentwhofivewhoweekswhoatwhonumberwhoonewhoafterwhothewhoUSwhoOpenwhobeforewhoinjurywhousheredwhoDavenportwhobackwhoinwhofront.\r\n\"ShewhogotwhomadwhoawholittlewhobitwhoandwhoIwhoplayedwhosomewhogreatwhotennis,\"whosaidwhoMauresmo,whowhowhowaswhorunner-upwhotowhoKimwhoClijsterswhoinwholastwhoyear'swhofinal.\r\nButwhoIwhowaswhofighting.\"whoSharapova,whowhowholostwho6-2who6-2whotowhoKuznetsovawhoinwhoBeijingwhoinwhoSeptember,whosaid:who\"InwhoBeijing,whoshewhowaswhocomingwhooffwhosuchwhoawhobigwhowinningwhostreakwho[14whomatches]whoandwhoshewhowaswhounstoppable.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Andre Agassi's involvement in the Australian Open was put in doubt after he pulled out of the Kooyong Classic with a hip injury.\r\nAgassi, who has won the Australian Open four times, will have an MRI scan to discover the extent of the damage.",
    "id": "N_474",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Andre",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "Australian",
        "adverb": "out"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Andre Agassi's involvement in twho Australian Open was put in doubt after who pulled out of twho Kooyong Classic with a hip injury.\r\nAgassi, who has won twho Australian Open four times, will have an MRI scan to discover twho extent of twho damage.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "British number one Tim Henman will face France's Cyril Saulnier in the first round of next week's Australian Open.\r\nGreg Rusedski, the British number two, is in the same quarter of the draw and could face Andy Roddick in the second round if he beats Swede Jonas Bjorkman.\r\nLocal favourite Lleyton Hewitt will meet France's Arnaud Clement, while defending champion and world number one Roger Federer faces Fabrice Santoro.\r\nHenman came from two sets down to defeat Saulnier in the first round of the French Open last year, so he knows he faces a tough test in Melbourne.\r\nThe seventh seed, who has never gone beyond the quarter-finals in the year's first major and is lined up to meet Roddick in the last eight, is looking forward to the match.\r\n\"We had a really tight one in Paris that went my way so I'm going to need to play well from the outset because he's a dangerous competitor.\" Switzerland's Federer, seeded one, is the hot favourite having won three of the four grand slam titles in 2004.\r\n\"The most important thing, though, is to get used to playing five-set matches and winning them.\" The 23-year-old could meet four-time champion Andre Agassi in the quarter-finals before meeting Russian Marat Safin, the player he beat in last year's final.\r\nEighth-seeded American Agassi is set to play a qualifier in round one if he can shake off a hip injury which ruled him out of the Kooyong Classic.\r\nSecond seed Andy Roddick will open his campaign against Irakli Labadze of Georgia.\r\nThe American could meet Rusedski in the second round, seventh seed Henman in the quarter-finals and Hewitt in the last four.\r\nSafin, seeded four, opens his campaign against a qualifier with 16th seed Tommy Haas, the player he beat in the semi-finals in 2002, a possible fourth-round opponent.\r\nIn the women's draw, Davenport could encounter eighth-seeded Venus Williams in the quarter-finals and third-ranked Anastasia Myskina, the French Open champion, in the semi-finals.\r\nBronchitis ruled Davenport, the 2000 Australian Open champion, out of her Sydney quarter-final on Thursday.\r\nVenus Williams, who lost to younger sister Serena in the Melbourne final two years ago, opens against Eleni Daniilidou of Greece.\r\nSerena Williams, who won her fourth consecutive grand slam at the 2003 Australian Open, was drawn in the bottom quarter with second seed Amelie Mauresmo, a runner-up in 1999.\r\nSerena will open against another Frenchwoman Camille Pin, while Mauresmo plays Australia's Samantha Stosur.\r\nWimbledon champion Maria Sharapova, seeded fourth, drew a qualifier in the first round but could meet fellow Russian Svetlana Kuznetsova, the US Open winner, in the last eight\r\n31 Jelena Kostanic (Croatia)",
    "id": "N_475",
    "features": {
        "noun": "number",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "face",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "British number one Tim who will face France's Cyril Saulnier in the first round of next week's Australian Open.\r\nGreg Rusedski, the British number two, is in the same quarter of the draw and could face Andy Roddick in the second round if he beats Swede Jonas Bjorkman.\r\nLocal favourite Lleyton Hewitt will meet France's Arnaud Clement, while defending champion and world number one Roger Federer faces Fabrice Santoro.\r\nwho came from two sets down to defeat Saulnier in the first round of the French Open last year, so he knows he faces a tough test in Melbourne.\r\nThe seventh seed, who has never gone beyond the quarter-finals in the year's first major and is lined up to meet Roddick in the last eight, is looking forward to the match.\r\n\"We had a really tight one in Paris that went my way so I'm going to need to play well from the outset because he's a dangerous competitor.\" Switzerland's Federer, seeded one, is the hot favourite having won three of the four grand slam titles in 2004.\r\n\"The most important thing, though, is to get used to playing five-set matches and winning them.\" The 23-year-old could meet four-time champion Andre Agassi in the quarter-finals before meeting Russian Marat Safin, the player he beat in last year's final.\r\nEighth-seeded American Agassi is set to play a qualifier in round one if he can shake off a hip injury which ruled him out of the Kooyong Classic.\r\nSecond seed Andy Roddick will open his campaign against Irakli Labadze of Georgia.\r\nThe American could meet Rusedski in the second round, seventh seed who in the quarter-finals and Hewitt in the last four.\r\nSafin, seeded four, opens his campaign against a qualifier with 16th seed Tommy Haas, the player he beat in the semi-finals in 2002, a possible fourth-round opponent.\r\nIn the women's draw, Davenport could encounter eighth-seeded Venus Williams in the quarter-finals and third-ranked Anastasia Myskina, the French Open champion, in the semi-finals.\r\nBronchitis ruled Davenport, the 2000 Australian Open champion, out of her Sydney quarter-final on Thursday.\r\nVenus Williams, who lost to younger sister Serena in the Melbourne final two years ago, opens against Eleni Daniilidou of Greece.\r\nSerena Williams, who won her fourth consecutive grand slam at the 2003 Australian Open, was drawn in the bottom quarter with second seed Amelie Mauresmo, a runner-up in 1999.\r\nSerena will open against another Frenchwoman Camille Pin, while Mauresmo plays Australia's Samantha Stosur.\r\nWimbledon champion Maria Sharapova, seeded fourth, drew a qualifier in the first round but could meet fellow Russian Svetlana Kuznetsova, the US Open winner, in the last eight\r\n31 Jelena Kostanic (Croatia)?",
        "answer": "Henman"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Fifth seed Carlos Moya was the first big name to fall at the Australian Open as he went down to fellow Spaniard Guillermo Garcia-Lopez on Monday.\r\nGarcia-Lopez, ranked 106 in the world, dominated from the outset and withstood a third-set rally from Moya to hang on for a 7-5 6-3 3-6 6-3 victory.\r\nNow I feel I can beat all these players.\" Moya said: \"I was playing well before I came here.",
    "id": "N_476",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Fifth",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "down"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Fifth seed Carlos Moya was twho first big name to fall at twho Australian Open as who went down to fellow Spaniard Guillermo Garcia-Lopez on Monday.\r\nGarcia-Lopez, ranked 106 in twho world, dominated from twho outset and withstood a third-set rally from Moya to hang on for a 7-5 6-3 3-6 6-3 victory.\r\nNow I feel I can beat all twhose players.\" Moya said: \"I was playing well before I came whore.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kim Clijsters has denied reports that she has pulled out of January's Australian Open because of her persistent wrist injury.\r\nBut if there's the least risk she will stay away.\" Despite being absent from the WTA entry list for the tournament, which begins on 17 January, Clijsters would be certain to get a wild card if she requested one.",
    "id": "N_477",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kim",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "persistent",
        "adverb": "away.\""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kim Clijsters has denied reports that who has pulled out of January's Australian Open because of her persistent wrist injury.\r\nBut if there's the least risk who will stay away.\" Despite being absent from the WTA entry list for the tournament, which begins on 17 January, Clijsters would be certain to get a wild card if who requested one.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Kim Clijsters has denied reports that she has pulled out of January's Australian Open because of her persistent wrist injury.\r\nBut if there's the least risk she will stay away.\" Despite being absent from the WTA entry list for the tournament, which begins on 17 January, Clijsters would be certain to get a wild card if she requested one.",
    "id": "N_478",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Kim",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "persistent",
        "adverb": "away.\""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Kim Clijsters has denied reports that who has pulled out of January's Australian Open because of her persistent wrist injury.\r\nBut if there's the least risk who will stay away.\" Despite being absent from the WTA entry list for the tournament, which begins on 17 January, Clijsters would be certain to get a wild card if who requested one.?",
        "answer": "she"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Andre Agassi put in an erratic display before edging into the fourth round of the Australian Open with victory over Taylor Dent.\r\nThe 34-year-old American, seeded eighth, made a poor start, dropping serve early on and later needing two chances to serve out the set.\r\nThe Russian turned his right ankle in the third game of the fourth set and called for treatment immediately.\r\n\"I try to stay calm because if you go crazy against players like Ancic, you might never come back because he's a tough opponent,\" he said.\r\nHrbaty defeated the 10th seed 7-6 (7-5) 6-7 (8-10) 6-7 (3-7) 6-1 6-3 in a match lasting four hours and 21 minutes.\r\nHrbaty will now play 2002 champion",
    "id": "N_479",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Andre",
        "pronoun": "you",
        "verb": "put",
        "adjective": "erratic",
        "adverb": "eighth,"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Andre who put in an erratic display before edging into the fourth round of the Australian Open with victory over Taylor Dent.\r\nThe 34-year-old American, seeded eighth, made a poor start, dropping serve early on and later needing two chances to serve out the set.\r\nThe Russian turned his right ankle in the third game of the fourth set and called for treatment immediately.\r\n\"I try to stay calm because if you go crazy against players like Ancic, you might never come back because he's a tough opponent,\" he said.\r\nHrbaty defeated the 10th seed 7-6 (7-5) 6-7 (8-10) 6-7 (3-7) 6-1 6-3 in a match lasting four hours and 21 minutes.\r\nHrbaty will now play 2002 champion?",
        "answer": "Agassi"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"The decision to not re-hire Brad Gilbert for the 2005 season is based on what I think is best for my game at this time,\" said Roddick.\r\n\"Any more on this situation's a private matter between coach and player.\" Roddick won 121 of his 147 matches while working with Gilbert, and said he had enjoyed their time together.",
    "id": "N_480",
    "features": {
        "noun": "decision",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "re-hire",
        "adjective": "\"The",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"The decision to not re-hire Brad Gilbert for the 2005 season is based on what I think is best for my game at this time,\" said who.\r\n\"Any more on this situation's a private matter between coach and player.\" who won 121 of his 147 matches while working with Gilbert, and said he had enjoyed their time together.?",
        "answer": "Roddick"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Andy Roddick is reportedly close to confirming US Davis Cup assistant Dean Goldfine as his new coach.",
    "id": "N_481",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Andy",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "close",
        "adverb": "reportedly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Andy who is reportedly close to confirming US Davis Cup assistant Dean Goldfine as his new coach.?",
        "answer": "Roddick"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Home favourite Lleyton Hewitt came through a dramatic five-set battle with Argentine David Nalbandian to reach the Australian Open semi-finals.\r\nHewitt eventually grabbed the vital break in the 17th game and served out to win 6-3 6-2 1-6 3-6 10-8 and set up a meeting with Andy Roddick.\r\nNinth seed Nalbandian had never come back from two sets down to win a match, and there was no indication he would do so as Hewitt dominated the first two sets.",
    "id": "N_482",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Home",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "favourite",
        "adjective": "dramatic",
        "adverb": "eventually"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Home favourite Lleyton who came through a dramatic five-set battle with Argentine David Nalbandian to reach the Australian Open semi-finals.\r\nwho eventually grabbed the vital break in the 17th game and served out to win 6-3 6-2 1-6 3-6 10-8 and set up a meeting with Andy Roddick.\r\nNinth seed Nalbandian had never come back from two sets down to win a match, and there was no indication he would do so as who dominated the first two sets.?",
        "answer": "Hewitt"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Olympic champion Justine Henin-Hardenne will return to action in January's Sydney International tournament.",
    "id": "N_483",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Olympic",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "return",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Olympic champion Justine who will return to action in January's Sydney International tournament.?",
        "answer": "Henin-Hardenne"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "He said, \"A three-month ban would mean that I not only will miss the Australian Open, but also the Davis Cup in Australia.\"",
    "id": "N_484",
    "features": {
        "noun": "ban",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "said,",
        "adjective": "\"A",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Hewhosaid,who\"Awhothree-monthwhobanwhowouldwhomeanwhothatwhoIwhonotwhoonlywhowillwhomisswhothewhoAustralianwhoOpen,whobutwhoalsowhothewhoDaviswhoCupwhoinwhoAustralia.\"?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Lleyton Hewitt kept his dream of an Australian Open title alive with a four-set win over Andy Roddick in Friday's second semi-final.\r\nHe certainly made a sluggish start, dropping his opening service game, and Roddick dominated with his huge serve as he took the first set.\r\nThe Australian was not to be denied and a disheartened Roddick made little impact in the fourth set as Hewitt raced to victory, sending the Melbourne crowd wild and ensuring the final will be a huge occasion.\r\n\"I've always said I'd do anything to get in the first night final at the Australian Open.",
    "id": "N_485",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Lleyton",
        "pronoun": "He",
        "verb": "kept",
        "adjective": "Australian",
        "adverb": "certainly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Lleyton Hewitt kept his what of an Australian Open title alive with a four-set win over Andy Roddick in Friday's second semi-final.\r\nHe certainly made a sluggish start, dropping his opening service game, and Roddick dominated with his huge serve as he took the first set.\r\nThe Australian was not to be denied and a disheartened Roddick made little impact in the fourth set as Hewitt raced to victory, sending the Melbourne crowd wild and ensuring the final will be a huge occasion.\r\n\"I've always said I'd do anything to get in the first night final at the Australian Open.?",
        "answer": "dream"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Australian tennis' top official has defended the Australian Open courts at Melbourne Park after criticism of the playing surface by Lleyton Hewitt.\r\nHewitt said he had had a \"gutful\" of trying to persuade them to make the surface faster but Tennis Australia's Geoff Pollard rejected his comments.",
    "id": "N_486",
    "features": {
        "noun": "tennis'",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Australian",
        "adverb": "faster"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Australian tennis' top what has defended the Australian Open courts at Melbourne Park after criticism of the playing surface by Lleyton Hewitt.\r\nHewitt said he had had a \"gutful\" of trying to persuade them to make the surface faster but Tennis Australia's Geoff Pollard rejected his comments.?",
        "answer": "official"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Serena Williams staged a remarkable recovery to beat Lindsay Davenport and win her second Australian Open title.\r\nDavenport took advantage to race through the opening set and held six break points in game five of the second.\r\n\"I kept thinking to myself 'I'm not losing this game,\" said Williams afterwards.",
    "id": "N_487",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Serena",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "staged",
        "adjective": "remarkable",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "SerenawhoWilliamswhostagedwhoawhoremarkablewhorecoverywhotowhobeatwhoLindsaywhoDavenportwhoandwhowinwhoherwhosecondwhoAustralianwhoOpenwhotitle.\r\nDavenportwhotookwhoadvantagewhotowhoracewhothroughwhothewhoopeningwhosetwhoandwhoheldwhosixwhobreakwhopointswhoinwhogamewhofivewhoofwhothewhosecond.\r\n\"Iwhokeptwhothinkingwhotowhomyselfwho'I'mwhonotwholosingwhothiswhogame,\"whosaidwhoWilliamswhoafterwards.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newly-crowned Australian Open champion Marat Safin has ruled out any chance of winning Wimbledon in the future.\r\nAfter losing in round one last year, Safin said he had \"given up\" on Wimbledon and winning his second Grand Slam title has not changed his mind.\r\nMe, I can't play on grass.\" However, Safin is hopeful that winning the Australian Open will give him the belief he needs to win more Grand Slam titles.\r\n\"I didn't expect that (to win the 2000 US Open) - it was against Sampras, I wasn't the favourite so I had no pressure whatsoever,\" he said.\r\nAnd after losing the first set 6-1 to Lleyton Hewitt in Sunday's final, Safin said he began to doubt himself again.",
    "id": "N_488",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Open",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Newly-crowned",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Newly-crowned Australian Open champion Marat who has ruled out any chance of winning Wimbledon in the future.\r\nAfter losing in round one last year, who said he had \"given up\" on Wimbledon and winning his second Grand Slam title has not changed his mind.\r\nMe, I can't play on grass.\" However, who is hopeful that winning the Australian Open will give him the belief he needs to win more Grand Slam titles.\r\n\"I didn't expect that (to win the 2000 US Open) - it was against Sampras, I wasn't the favourite so I had no pressure whatsoever,\" he said.\r\nAnd after losing the first set 6-1 to Lleyton Hewitt in Sunday's final, who said he began to doubt himself again.?",
        "answer": "Safin"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Newly-crowned Australian Open champion Marat Safin has ruled out any chance of winning Wimbledon in the future.\r\nAfter losing in round one last year, Safin said he had \"given up\" on Wimbledon and winning his second Grand Slam title has not changed his mind.\r\nMe, I can't play on grass.\" However, Safin is hopeful that winning the Australian Open will give him the belief he needs to win more Grand Slam titles.\r\n\"I didn't expect that (to win the 2000 US Open) - it was against Sampras, I wasn't the favourite so I had no pressure whatsoever,\" he said.\r\nAnd after losing the first set 6-1 to Lleyton Hewitt in Sunday's final, Safin said he began to doubt himself again.",
    "id": "N_489",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Open",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Newly-crowned",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Newly-crowned Australian Open champion Marat who has ruled out any chance of winning Wimbledon in the future.\r\nAfter losing in round one last year, who said he had \"given up\" on Wimbledon and winning his second Grand Slam title has not changed his mind.\r\nMe, I can't play on grass.\" However, who is hopeful that winning the Australian Open will give him the belief he needs to win more Grand Slam titles.\r\n\"I didn't expect that (to win the 2000 US Open) - it was against Sampras, I wasn't the favourite so I had no pressure whatsoever,\" he said.\r\nAnd after losing the first set 6-1 to Lleyton Hewitt in Sunday's final, who said he began to doubt himself again.?",
        "answer": "Safin"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Roddick holds serve to force Nadal to serve for the match but the American surely cannot turn things around now.\r\nA couple of stunning points follow, one where Nadal chases down a Roddick shot and turns into a passing winner.\r\nNadal saves a Roddick set point then earns his own with a drive volley - and a crosscourt passing winner sends the crowd wild.\r\nNadal tries to up his aggression and he passes Roddick down the line to go 15-40 and two set points up.\r\nNadal enjoys another straightforward hold and Roddick must once again serve to stay in the set.\r\nRoddick hangs in on his serve to level matters but Nadal is making him fight for every point.\r\nNadal could be suffering a disappointment hangover from the previous game as he goes 0-30 down and then has to save a break point after a tremendous rally in which he is forced into some brilliant defence.\r\nRoddick still looks a bit sluggish but he attacks the net and is rewarded with a break point, which Nadal saves with a good first serve and the Spaniard goes on to hold.\r\nRoddick saves the break point and then bangs down his ninth ace before clinching the game with a service winner.\r\nThe game passes the two-hour mark as Nadal holds serve to edge ahead in the third set.\r\nNadal puts the American under pressure and Roddick saves a break point with a superb stop volley before going on to hold.\r\nRoddick double-faults to concede the first mini-break and then Nadal loops a crosscourt winner to seize advantage in the tiebreak.\r\nNadal comes up with a down-the-line winner but then nets tamely on Roddick's next set point.\r\nOn the very next point, Nadal blasts a forehand service return from right of court that passes Roddick and even the American is forced to applaud.\r\nNadal manages to hold again despite Roddick piling the pressure on his serve.\r\nNadal takes the next point but Roddick breaks again with a sharp volley at the net.",
    "id": "N_490",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Roddick",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "holds",
        "adjective": "turn",
        "adverb": "surely"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "RoddickwhoholdswhoservewhotowhoforcewhoNadalwhotowhoservewhoforwhothewhomatchwhobutwhothewhoAmericanwhosurelywhocannotwhoturnwhothingswhoaroundwhonow.\r\nAwhocouplewhoofwhostunningwhopointswhofollow,whoonewhowherewhoNadalwhochaseswhodownwhoawhoRoddickwhoshotwhoandwhoturnswhointowhoawhopassingwhowinner.\r\nNadalwhosaveswhoawhoRoddickwhosetwhopointwhothenwhoearnswhohiswhoownwhowithwhoawhodrivewhovolleywho-whoandwhoawhocrosscourtwhopassingwhowinnerwhosendswhothewhocrowdwhowild.\r\nNadalwhotrieswhotowhoupwhohiswhoaggressionwhoandwhohewhopasseswhoRoddickwhodownwhothewholinewhotowhogowho15-40whoandwhotwowhosetwhopointswhoup.\r\nNadalwhoenjoyswhoanotherwhostraightforwardwhoholdwhoandwhoRoddickwhomustwhooncewhoagainwhoservewhotowhostaywhoinwhothewhoset.\r\nRoddickwhohangswhoinwhoonwhohiswhoservewhotowholevelwhomatterswhobutwhoNadalwhoiswhomakingwhohimwhofightwhoforwhoeverywhopoint.\r\nNadalwhocouldwhobewhosufferingwhoawhodisappointmentwhohangoverwhofromwhothewhopreviouswhogamewhoaswhohewhogoeswho0-30whodownwhoandwhothenwhohaswhotowhosavewhoawhobreakwhopointwhoafterwhoawhotremendouswhorallywhoinwhowhichwhohewhoiswhoforcedwhointowhosomewhobrilliantwhodefence.\r\nRoddickwhostillwholookswhoawhobitwhosluggishwhobutwhohewhoattackswhothewhonetwhoandwhoiswhorewardedwhowithwhoawhobreakwhopoint,whowhichwhoNadalwhosaveswhowithwhoawhogoodwhofirstwhoservewhoandwhothewhoSpaniardwhogoeswhoonwhotowhohold.\r\nRoddickwhosaveswhothewhobreakwhopointwhoandwhothenwhobangswhodownwhohiswhoninthwhoacewhobeforewhoclinchingwhothewhogamewhowithwhoawhoservicewhowinner.\r\nThewhogamewhopasseswhothewhotwo-hourwhomarkwhoaswhoNadalwhoholdswhoservewhotowhoedgewhoaheadwhoinwhothewhothirdwhoset.\r\nNadalwhoputswhothewhoAmericanwhounderwhopressurewhoandwhoRoddickwhosaveswhoawhobreakwhopointwhowithwhoawhosuperbwhostopwhovolleywhobeforewhogoingwhoonwhotowhohold.\r\nRoddickwhodouble-faultswhotowhoconcedewhothewhofirstwhomini-breakwhoandwhothenwhoNadalwholoopswhoawhocrosscourtwhowinnerwhotowhoseizewhoadvantagewhoinwhothewhotiebreak.\r\nNadalwhocomeswhoupwhowithwhoawhodown-the-linewhowinnerwhobutwhothenwhonetswhotamelywhoonwhoRoddick'swhonextwhosetwhopoint.\r\nOnwhothewhoverywhonextwhopoint,whoNadalwhoblastswhoawhoforehandwhoservicewhoreturnwhofromwhorightwhoofwhocourtwhothatwhopasseswhoRoddickwhoandwhoevenwhothewhoAmericanwhoiswhoforcedwhotowhoapplaud.\r\nNadalwhomanageswhotowhoholdwhoagainwhodespitewhoRoddickwhopilingwhothewhopressurewhoonwhohiswhoserve.\r\nNadalwhotakeswhothewhonextwhopointwhobutwhoRoddickwhobreakswhoagainwhowithwhoawhosharpwhovolleywhoatwhothewhonet.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Scotland's Andrew Murray was named young player of the year after winning the US Open juniors, as well as a Futures event in Italy.\r\n\"I'll be able to acclimatise while practising before the event and then will be guaranteed matches against the best players in the world.",
    "id": "N_491",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Scotland's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "young",
        "adverb": "as"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Scotland'swhoAndrewwhoMurraywhowaswhonamedwhoyoungwhoplayerwhoofwhothewhoyearwhoafterwhowinningwhothewhoUSwhoOpenwhojuniors,whoaswhowellwhoaswhoawhoFutureswhoeventwhoinwhoItaly.\r\n\"I'llwhobewhoablewhotowhoacclimatisewhowhilewhopractisingwhobeforewhothewhoeventwhoandwhothenwhowillwhobewhoguaranteedwhomatcheswhoagainstwhothewhobestwhoplayerswhoinwhothewhoworld.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "These are the questions Jimmy Connors will be asking of Britain's brightest tennis hopes in the months, and possibly years, to come.\r\nThe American legend swept into London on Thursday to announce a \"long-term\" relationship with the Lawn Tennis Association after spending three days at the Elite Performance winter camp in La Manga.\r\n\"You know, everybody hits the ball well and there's a very fine line between number one and number 100,\" said Connors.\r\n\"Britain has a different attitude, the right attitude, in taking the game forward and finding the next Wimbledon champion,\" said Connors.\r\nThere's only one number one spot and it's lonely up there, but it's got the best view.\" In the year that has seen Andrew Murray emerge as Britain's great new hope, Connors rejected suggestions that the Scot might be put under too much pressure too soon.\r\nThat's what we play for.\" Despite the emphasis on hard work, training and preparation, Connors does admit that the desire required of a champion has to come from within.",
    "id": "N_492",
    "features": {
        "noun": "questions",
        "pronoun": "what",
        "verb": "are",
        "adjective": "brightest",
        "adverb": "possibly"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "ThesewhoarewhothewhoquestionswhoJimmywhoConnorswhowillwhobewhoaskingwhoofwhoBritain'swhobrightestwhotenniswhohopeswhoinwhothewhomonths,whoandwhopossiblywhoyears,whotowhocome.\r\nThewhoAmericanwholegendwhosweptwhointowhoLondonwhoonwhoThursdaywhotowhoannouncewhoawho\"long-term\"whorelationshipwhowithwhothewhoLawnwhoTenniswhoAssociationwhoafterwhospendingwhothreewhodayswhoatwhothewhoElitewhoPerformancewhowinterwhocampwhoinwhoLawhoManga.\r\n\"Youwhoknow,whoeverybodywhohitswhothewhoballwhowellwhoandwhothere'swhoawhoverywhofinewholinewhobetweenwhonumberwhoonewhoandwhonumberwho100,\"whosaidwhoConnors.\r\n\"Britainwhohaswhoawhodifferentwhoattitude,whothewhorightwhoattitude,whoinwhotakingwhothewhogamewhoforwardwhoandwhofindingwhothewhonextwhoWimbledonwhochampion,\"whosaidwhoConnors.\r\nThere'swhoonlywhoonewhonumberwhoonewhospotwhoandwhoit'swholonelywhoupwhothere,whobutwhoit'swhogotwhothewhobestwhoview.\"whoInwhothewhoyearwhothatwhohaswhoseenwhoAndrewwhoMurraywhoemergewhoaswhoBritain'swhogreatwhonewwhohope,whoConnorswhorejectedwhosuggestionswhothatwhothewhoScotwhomightwhobewhoputwhounderwhotoowhomuchwhopressurewhotoowhosoon.\r\nThat'swhowhatwhowewhoplaywhofor.\"whoDespitewhothewhoemphasiswhoonwhohardwhowork,whotrainingwhoandwhopreparation,whoConnorswhodoeswhoadmitwhothatwhothewhodesirewhorequiredwhoofwhoawhochampionwhohaswhotowhocomewhofromwhowithin.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Australian tennis coach Tony Roche has turned down an approach from Roger Federer to be the world number one's new full-time coach, say reports.",
    "id": "N_493",
    "features": {
        "noun": "tennis",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "Australian",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "reports"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "And after Anastasia Myskina became the first Russian woman to win a Grand Slam at the French Open, two more followed at Wimbledon and the US Open.\r\nFederer began the year as world number one and holder of the Wimbledon and Masters Cup titles, and set about conquering new ground.\r\nAndy Roddick was the only player to put up any real resistance at Wimbledon, and Federer's performance against Lleyton Hewitt in the US Open final was breathtaking.\r\nFederer again got the better of Hewitt in the season-ending Masters Cup. His victory in Houston proved to be his 13th successive win in a final, an Open era record.\r\nThe Russian women finally delivered on their long-recognised promise in 2004, with Myskina, Maria Sharapova and Svetlana Kuznetsova winning Grand Slams, before taking the season-ending Fed Cup. But while the young Russians were on the way up, it was a different story for the Belgians and the Williams sisters.",
    "id": "N_494",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Anastasia",
        "pronoun": "it",
        "verb": "became",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "again"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Mark Philippoussis is almost certain to miss the Australian Open after suffering a groin injury during the Hopman Cup loss to the Netherlands.\r\n- Former world number two Tommy Haas is also a doubt for the Australian Open after picking up a thigh injury playing for Germany in the Hopman Cup. The 26-year-old had treatment on his left thigh while leading Argentine Guillermo Coria 7-5 2-2.",
    "id": "N_495",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Mark",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "is",
        "adjective": "certain",
        "adverb": "almost"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Mark Philippoussis is almost certain to miss the Australian Open after suffering a groin injury during the Hopman Cup loss to the which location.\r\n- Former world number two Tommy Haas is also a doubt for the Australian Open after picking up a thigh injury playing for Germany in the Hopman Cup. The 26-year-old had treatment on his left thigh while leading Argentine Guillermo Coria 7-5 2-2.?",
        "answer": "Netherlands"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Slovakia will play Argentina in the final of the Hopman Cup after beating Group B rivals the Netherlands 3-0.\r\nBlake and Shaughnessy then beat Molik and Baccanello in a tense mixed doubles contest to take the win.",
    "id": "N_496",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Slovakia",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "play",
        "adjective": "final",
        "adverb": "then"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who will play Argentina in the final of the Hopman Cup after beating Group B rivals the Netherlands 3-0.\r\nBlake and Shaughnessy then beat Molik and Baccanello in a tense mixed doubles contest to take the win.?",
        "answer": "Slovakia"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"It feels like home for me, because Jaslyn lives here,\" said Johansson.",
    "id": "N_497",
    "features": {
        "noun": "feels",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "lives",
        "adjective": "\"It",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"It feels like home for me, because Jaslyn lives here,\" said who.?",
        "answer": "Johansson"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Moya led Spain to victory over the USA but wants to focus on the Grand Slams in 2005, although insists he will return to the Davis Cup in 2006.",
    "id": "N_498",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Moya",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "led",
        "adjective": "",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Moya led Spain to victory over the which location but wants to focus on the Grand Slams in 2005, although insists he will return to the Davis Cup in 2006.?",
        "answer": "USA"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Tim Henman has retired from Great Britain's Davis Cup team.\r\n\"I've really enjoyed playing in front of the thousands of British fans both home and abroad and would like to thank every one of them for their unwavering support over the years.\" Henman leaves Davis Cup tennis with an impressive record, having won 36 of his 50 matches.\r\n\"Tim has quite simply had a phenomenal Davis Cup career and it has been an absolute privilege to have captained the team with him in it,\" said Bates.",
    "id": "N_499",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Tim",
        "pronoun": "them",
        "verb": "has",
        "adjective": "British",
        "adverb": "really"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Tim who has retired from Great Britain's Davis Cup team.\r\n\"I've really enjoyed playing in front of the thousands of British fans both home and abroad and would like to thank every one of them for their unwavering support over the years.\" who leaves Davis Cup tennis with an impressive record, having won 36 of his 50 matches.\r\n\"Tim has quite simply had a phenomenal Davis Cup career and it has been an absolute privilege to have captained the team with him in it,\" said Bates.?",
        "answer": "Henman"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Serbia's Ana Ivanovic captured her first WTA title with a straight-sets victory over Hungarian Melinda Czink in the final of the Canberra Classic.",
    "id": "N_500",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Serbia's",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "captured",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Serbia's Ana who captured her first WTA title with a straight-sets victory over Hungarian Melinda Czink in the final of the Canberra Classic.?",
        "answer": "Ivanovic"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "The Belgian sports minister at the centre of the Svetlana Kuznetsova doping row says he will not apologise for making allegations against her.\r\nEerdekens said he made the statement in order to protect the other three players that took part in the tournament, Belgian Justine Henin-Hardenne, Nathalie Dechy of France and Russia's Elena Dementieva.\r\n\"How can you be happy when you see your face on the cover page and talking about doping?\" Dechy said.",
    "id": "N_501",
    "features": {
        "noun": "sports",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "doping",
        "adjective": "Belgian",
        "adverb": "not"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Twho Belgian sports minister at twho centre of twho Svetlana Kuznetsova doping row says who will not apologise for making allegations against whor.\r\nEerdekens said who made twho statement in order to protect twho otwhor three players that took part in twho tournament, Belgian Justine Henin-Hardenne, Nathalie Dechy of France and Russia's Elena Dementieva.\r\n\"How can you be happy wwhon you see your face on twho cover page and talking about doping?\" Dechy said.?",
        "answer": "he"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"I was nervous and I couldn't play tennis,\" said Safin.\r\n\"You get huge confidence because Roger is a great player,\" said Safin.",
    "id": "N_502",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"I",
        "pronoun": "I",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "nervous",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "\"IwhowaswhonervouswhoandwhoIwhocouldn'twhoplaywhotennis,\"whosaidwhoSafin.\r\n\"YouwhogetwhohugewhoconfidencewhobecausewhoRogerwhoiswhoawhogreatwhoplayer,\"whosaidwhoSafin.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "\"It feels really good,\" said Martinez, who is playing her last season on the Tour.",
    "id": "N_503",
    "features": {
        "noun": "\"It",
        "pronoun": "who",
        "verb": "said",
        "adjective": "last",
        "adverb": "really"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "?",
        "answer": "who"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "A change in approach from fourth seed Stepanek in the second set paid dividends as he took it on a tie-break, but Soderling's superior power proved too much in the third.",
    "id": "N_504",
    "features": {
        "noun": "change",
        "pronoun": "he",
        "verb": "paid",
        "adjective": "fourth",
        "adverb": "too"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "AwhochangewhoinwhoapproachwhofromwhofourthwhoseedwhoStepanekwhoinwhothewhosecondwhosetwhopaidwhodividendswhoaswhohewhotookwhoitwhoonwhoawhotie-break,whobutwhoSoderling'swhosuperiorwhopowerwhoprovedwhotoowhomuchwhoinwhothewhothird.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Greg Rusedski was forced to withdraw from the Open 13 in Marseille on Thursday with a rib injury.",
    "id": "N_505",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Greg",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "was",
        "adjective": "Open",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Greg who was forced to withdraw from the Open 13 in Marseille on Thursday with a rib injury.?",
        "answer": "Rusedski"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Top-seeded Americans Andy Roddick and Andre Agassi survived minor scares to reach the last eight of the SAP Open.\r\nAnd world number three Roddick dropped a set to Korean player Hyung-Taik Lee, before pulling out a 6-3 3-6 6-2 win in San Jose, California.",
    "id": "N_506",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Americans",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "survived",
        "adjective": "Top-seeded",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Top-seededwhoAmericanswhoAndywhoRoddickwhoandwhoAndrewhoAgassiwhosurvivedwhominorwhoscareswhotowhoreachwhothewholastwhoeightwhoofwhothewhoSAPwhoOpen.\r\nAndwhoworldwhonumberwhothreewhoRoddickwhodroppedwhoawhosetwhotowhoKoreanwhoplayerwhoHyung-TaikwhoLee,whobeforewhopullingwhooutwhoawho6-3who3-6who6-2whowinwhoinwhoSanwhoJose,whoCalifornia.?",
        "answer": " "
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Nadal, playing in the outdoor clay event for the first time, hit some powerful forehands to oust Starace in a match delayed over an hour by rain.",
    "id": "N_507",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Nadal,",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "hit",
        "adjective": "outdoor",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who, playing in the outdoor clay event for the first time, hit some powerful forehands to oust Starace in a match delayed over an hour by rain.?",
        "answer": "Nadal"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Melzer shocks Agassi in San Jose\r\nSecond seed Andre Agassi suffered a comprehensive defeat by Jurgen Melzer in the quarter-finals of the SAP Open.\r\n\"I didn't want him to play his game.",
    "id": "N_508",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Melzer",
        "pronoun": "him",
        "verb": "suffered",
        "adjective": "comprehensive",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Melzer shocks who in San Jose\r\nSecond seed Andre who suffered a comprehensive defeat by Jurgen Melzer in the quarter-finals of the SAP Open.\r\n\"I didn't want him to play his game.?",
        "answer": "Agassi"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Teenager Sania Mirza completed a superb week at the Hyderabad Open by becoming the first Indian in history to win a WTA singles title.\r\nMirza eventually lost the point but to the relief of the crowd, she broke Bondarenko again in the next game to clinch the title.",
    "id": "N_509",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Teenager",
        "pronoun": "she",
        "verb": "completed",
        "adjective": "first",
        "adverb": "eventually"
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "Teenager Sania who completed a superb week at the Hyderabad Open by becoming the first Indian in history to win a WTA singles title.\r\nwho eventually lost the point but to the relief of the crowd, she broke Bondarenko again in the next game to clinch the title.?",
        "answer": "Mirza"
    }
}{
    "sentence": "Roddick to face Saulnier in final\r\nAndy Roddick will play Cyril Saulnier in the final of the SAP Open in San Jose on Sunday.",
    "id": "N_510",
    "features": {
        "noun": "Roddick",
        "pronoun": "",
        "verb": "face",
        "adjective": "final",
        "adverb": ""
    },
    "qa": {
        "question": "who to face Saulnier in final\r\nAndy who will play Cyril Saulnier in the final of the SAP Open in San Jose on Sunday.?",
        "answer": "Roddick"
    }
}